General de Gaulle i en recent speech in the Paris region with the winter in its most severe spoke frank words.
Victory is assured at the end of our labors, but at this moment nature herself seems to have turned against us.
Five months after liberation, life in France is unbelievably hard through lack of all normal facilities.
On top of this have come floods to ravage and isolate vast areas.
A frost to stop even the barges bringing coal along the canals.
Kommunikationen var mer än minskad med tanke på den krigsbrytande situationen i landet.
Men den här vädret har gjort det här rådet omöjligt.
Grazingslandet har en thick white carpet.
Kropparna är beredda i snö.
The railway points are frozen hard.
The engines have no coal.
And the people of Paris as a result have nothing to heat their homes and less food.
The markets, the famous isle, are empty.
Through lack of transport, the riches of the earth cannot be brought even a score of miles to feed the hungry mouths of the population.
To run transport you need coal or petrol.
But to get coal or petrol you need transport.
And so the vicious circle goes round.
Men även i sina egna tragiska situationer, minskar pariserna de större misslyckanden av normandens folk, som fortfarande hade att existera i den här röda staden och byn, för här har monsterna av krig gått mer nära.
Det som är kvar i sin väg är en tragisk travesti av moderna livet.
Very often families have not even a roof over their heads.
And yet they live on and hope on and think of their sons or friends or allies who are fighting, maybe dying, in the mud and the snow of the front.
Here in their homes they have no heat, no light, even no water.
The oil in the wheels of civilization has dried up.
And the wheels will only start to turn again when all this is over.
When the war is won.
And the greatest duty of everyone is not just to wait for that day, but to hasten its coming.
In the mining country in northern France, derelict flying bomb launching ramps.
Today the playground of children who've known no toys.
An ironical comment on our age.
In the now quiet countryside, the layers from which these infernal machines took their course serve to remind us that another stage has been reached in the development of civilization.
An automaton can bring hell itself to human beings living 200 miles away.
The immediate danger from V1s may have largely passed, but it is a sobering thought to think of the effect its very invention could have on the future strategy and political decisions of the nations of the world.
People in southern England know only too well the sound and appearance of this monstrous weapon.
Den som visar sig i den här otroliga bilden har aldrig nått sitt mål, för där uppstår snabbt sin död.
Hunt är över chaneln, och det är inte lång tid innan en människa har skjutit ett dödsblås till sin robotadvokat.
Throughout the occupation the Berlier factories worked for the Germans and suffered severe damage by allied bombardment.
The French minister of industrial production recently visited the factories to see for himself the results of an interesting experiment.
Immediately after the liberation Monsieur Berlier was arrested.
But that didn't in any way stop work in the factories.
Far from it.
In the proprietors enforced absence the business has been directed by the staff and they've shown that they're prepared to take the responsibility.
Under the new regime the engineers, the overseers and the rest of the staff are working side by side in perfect harmony.
First of all to repair the damage to the repair shops and the machines.
And they've given up their Saturday afternoons and Sundays in order to get output started with the minimum delay.
This is a bold idea and its development will be watched with interest.
The collective effort of these men, working in a common cause for the common good, with the skilled experience behind them, has achieved great things and surmounted great obstacles.
For today, the Berlier factories, without Monsieur Berlier, are again in full production and contributing under their new management to Francis' war effort.
Frans har dyr behov av allt som hennes fabriker kan producera.
Och successen av Berlier-experimentet visar hur ett av de stora problemen av politisk och ekonomisk förändring kan förändras genom kärlek och determination.
I stället för de svårigheter som den möter varje gång, är det franska regeringen som inte förlorar sin stora koloniska mission.
Världens regerande regeringschef avgör öppningsceremonin för en ny väg som kommer från Tunis till Casablanca.
Det har gjorts under kriget och är en enorm tillgång till kommunikationen i Nordafrika.
Från Morocco kommer nyheter om en annan stor franska uppgift.
General Katrou attends a ceremony at the new Afud dam about 60 miles from Casablanca in the presence of his majesty the sultan Sidi Mohammed.
This was one of General Katrou's last public acts on African soil before taking leave for Moscow where he's been appointed French ambassador.
Det franska regeringen är stolt över det här stora arbetet, vilket visar ett annat steg i utvecklingen som Frans har tillverkat till Marokko.
De natala arbetarna är justerbart stolt över att de undersöker resultaten av deras arbete.
This immense dam, completed in spite of the innumerable difficulties of wartime, will create electrical supply for a great part of Morocco and permit irrigation of vast tracts of territory.
Frans hjälper sin krig och den kommer med hjälp av Frans, som skickar meddelande till västerfronten.
The resident general of France in Morocco recently visited his men, the famous Moroccan goons, at the front in Alsace, where their fabulous reputation as tough fighters has been clearly upheld.
The soldiers of the French Empire are today making an invaluable effort, fighting at the side of their French and allied comrades.
Great countries have a right to be proud of their empires.