In the garden of number 10 Downing Street, the Prime Minister says goodbye to his old war cabinet and at the same time welcomes the ministers of his new caretaker government.
The French nation showed its gratitude to Field Marshal Montgomery during his recent visit to Paris, where General de Gaulle decorated him with the Grand Cross of the Legion of Honour.
At a small house at Lüneburg, Heinrich Himmler, Gestapo chief and once the terror of Europe, lies dead by his own hand shortly after being captured by our troops.
The veteran Lancaster bomber Ares is home again after a hazardous polar flight to locate the true position of the magnetic north pole involving a round trip of more than 17,000 miles.
Congratulations to the RAF on a splendid piece of air navigation.
Ever since flying began, the airmen's greatest enemy has been fog.
That deadly menace which at one time was responsible for more losses over British airfields than were caused by flak over Germany.
The Prime Minister was gravely concerned at these casualties and immediately went into action.
He instructed Mr. Jeffrey Lloyd of the Petroleum Warfare Department to put in hand every possible experiment to keep airfields free from fog.
Resultatet var operation FIDO, som betyder Fog Intensive Dispersion.
Agenten använde var att bränna petroleum, och FIDO-systemet gjorde det möjligt att hålla hela aerodromen klart för operationer, även i den djupaste foggen.
Vid slutet av året har många liv, amerikansk och brittisk, redan blivit rädda av FIDO, men testtiden har fortfarande att komma.
Christmas 1944, Brunsteds breakthrough in the Ardennes, a desperate offensive which might change the whole course of the war.
A pall of fog lay heavily over Britain at a time when every bomber was urgently needed to smash the German lines of supply.
Operation Fido had already proved its value, but this was its greatest task.
Heavily laden bombers must be able to take off in great numbers in one of the worst fogs known for years.
Pathfinders must leave their bases to guide the bombers to their targets.
They did take off and very soon tons of high explosive were helping to shatter Germany's last great offensive.
Still flying blind through the fog, the bombers returned home.
The morale of their crews is high in the knowledge that their mission will end in a safe landing guaranteed by Fido.
Plane after plane comes in between the long lines of flame which have meant all the difference between life and death for so many pilots and their crews.
Like its counterparts, Mulberry and Pluto, Operation Fido is another triumph for its British creators and for the stimulating drive of Mr. Churchill.
On the aerodrome where Fido was first installed, Mr. Jeffrey Lloyd visits the Pathfinder chief, Air Vice Marshal Bennett, who pays tribute on behalf of the Royal Air Force.
And now, as you see, the public are being told the secret of Fido.
And I think the public should know that Fido, in this war, has saved over 10,000 aircrew lives.
Moreover, Fido has made it possible to carry out operations in base weather which would have
stopp.
En exempel av det var när Rundstedt försökte bräcka igenom den offensiva idén.
Bommaruppgången var nödvändig, hård uppgång, och rådgivarna behövdes markera.
Men rådgivarnas grundläggande väder var färdiga.
Rådgivarna var rädda eftersom Fido gjorde det möjligt för rådgivarna att ta sig ut och landa
in spite of this thick fog.
Moreover it's been of tremendous value to crews returning from operations to know that they could get down at their bases regardless of the weather.
Bomber Command are extremely grateful to the Ministry of Petroleum Warfare for having produced such a magnificent British invention.
The pathfinders in particular who have mastered
Target Weather, I'm very grateful to you for having made it possible for them to master base weather.
This is the most thrilling and satisfactory job I've handled during the war because it saves the lives of our airmen, especially the pathfinders who are the spearhead of bomber command.
Mr. Churchill started it all.
And we could never have done the job without his powerful backing right through.
And gentlemen, if any of you are flying civil planes after the war, it will mean a good deal to you and your passengers then.
Out of the needs of war has come a masterly invention which will ensure the safety of our future air routes throughout the world.