May the 8th, 1945.
The day of victory in Europe and scenes of thankful rejoicing in the heart of the Empire's capital which have been echoed throughout the world.
Trafalgar Square is a rallying point for many of the happy thousands who come to welcome peace.
Hickory Circus var bara ett stort stort stjärn av facer.
Från morgonen till klockan på natten är det många som åker till Buckingham Palace– –för att berätta om vår kring och kvinna– –som har deltagit med deras folk om kriget.
They stand on the bomb-scarred balcony of their home, which has suffered like so many thousands of others in this our land.
From number 10 Downing Street the Prime Minister makes the momentous announcement for which the world had been waiting.
Yesterday morning at 2.41 a.m.
at General Eisenhower's headquarters General Jodl the representative of the German High Command and of Grand Admiral Dönitz the designated head of the German state signed the act
of unconditional surrender of all German land, sea and air forces in Europe to the allied expeditionary forces and simultaneously to the Soviet high command.
Hostilities will end officially at one minute after midnight tonight Tuesday the 8th of May.
We may allow ourselves a brief period of rejoicing.
Today is victory in Europe day.
Tomorrow will also be victory in Europe day.
But let us not forget for a moment the toils and efforts that lie ahead.
Japan with all her treachery and greed remains unsubdued.
The injuries she has inflicted upon Great Britain, the United States and other countries and her detestable cruelties call for justice and retribution.
We must now devote all our strength and resources to the completion of our tasks both at home and abroad.
Advance Britannia.
Long live the cause of freedom.
God save the king.
I det här momentet av tackgivningen talar hans majestätare till hans folk och hans krigsforcer runt om i världen.
I dag ger vi tack till Gud för en stor belöning.
Från vårt empat, den äldsta kapitalstaden, var vi alla bättrade och var aldrig för en moment skämtade eller förvånade.
Speaking from London, I ask you to join with me in that act of thanksgiving.
Germany, the enemy who drove all Europe into war, has been finally overcome.
In the Far East, we have yet to deal with the Japanese
Det är ett bestämt och kraftfullt krig.
Till det ska vi vända oss med all möjlighet och med alla våra resurser.
Men vid den här tiden, när den drömmande mörkret av kriget har gått långt från våra händer och hem i de här isländerna,
We may at last make one pause for thanksgiving and then turn our thoughts to the tasks all over the world which peace in Europe brings with it.
First, and let us remember those who will not come back.
Their constancy and courage in battle
Deres sacrifice and endurance in the face of a merciless enemy.
Let us remember the men in all the services.
The women in all the services who have laid down their lives.
We have come to the end of our tribulation.
And they are not with us at the moment of our rejoicing.
En större och större kraft rör sig runt paletet.
Och på balkonet kommer familjen med vår prime minister själv.
The skies over London are lit by the joyous lights that work so hard and so long.