Kriget i Europa fortsätter genom en serie av rådgivande känslor.
Efter den största invasningen av Europa, förberedde allmänheten i väst den stupendösa kriget på Holand.
Den starkaste armén som kunde flytta på luft var att bygga upp i Britannien.
Paratrooper och glidertrooper.
Den här aktionen var också en av de bäst hållbara sekreterna i kriget.
Den visade sig till invandrarna i Holand när det var för tidigt att göra dem något bra.
Den här ljuset tippade en annan skala mot de germanska armén i Europa.
Den geniösa av allierade militära strategi uppstår en annan masterström.
Nu på grunden.
En annan fjäll öppnas upp till allierade arm.
Nya tröjor utvecklas på den norska och belgiska grunden.
Armerna av de vänsterdemokraterna släpper in på den kraft som försöker rulla världen med kraft.
Våra soldater mötte unga norska som också kämpade för tyskarna.
De allierade arméerna har tagit Maastricht.
Detta namn minskar den ominösa kriget av den germanska armén i maj 1940.
När vi förväntade oss att flöden i Holmland skulle återkomma för att hålla kriget tillbaka.
Men ingen sån lucka var vår portion i 1940.
Detta är bombningen av Boulogne, sedan tagit av Royal Air Force Bomber Command.
Den germanska high command-strategin förlorade sin briljantis när krigsforskningen förlorade initiativet i kriget.
Men utifrån konfusionen har Wehrmacht försökt att hänga på till de tillgängliga porten i Holland, Belgien och Frankrike.
Men en på en, de porten faller till våra armar.
Och nu, för alla som har soffit i handen av tyskarna och Tyskland, det här är det du väntat dig i fem långa år.
Allied Soldiers enter Hitler's Germany.
This is one more place where the railway was bombed before the Germans pulled out.
It is a Belgian border town annexed by Germany in her days of victory.
Inhabitanten här är germanska.
Det finns ingen väg av blås och smil som vägen till Paris och Brussel.
Vi måste förstå att de här människorna har varit nöjda med att bli regerade av Hitler och hans nazister.
Nöjda med att se honom plunga världen i smärta i sin bidrag till att regera världen.
De har inte försökt att rädda sig av Hitler.
Det här är Rötgen, den första staden i Tyskland.
Inside the German frontier the camera brings us to the first fortifications of the Siegfried Line.
One pillbox bears a notice saying that Hitler has personally inspected it.
His intuition told him not to stop in it.
Nearby is the German town of Wallendorf.
When American troops entered Wallendorf they saw white surrender flags on every building.
Then suddenly shots were fired and some of the American soldiers fell.
The Americans therefore burned Wallendorf to the ground.
This is the kind of language that Germans understand.
The story of a small American patrol which accepted the surrender of a German general and 20,000 of his men with all their weapons supplies our conclusion to this edition of Go More British News.
Lieutenant McGill var beredd att förlora sig och han gick in i de germanska linjerna för att hitta ut vad det var om.
Av alla de fantastiska historierna av den här fantastiska kriget, den här är högst rankad.
Om den hade varit berättad, så trodde du inte på det.
Men här är den.
Reproduced by the war correspondents movie camera as it took its place in war history.
General Eric Elster.
He and his men have been making their way towards Germany from the south of France.
Harassed by the Mackie.
They decided to seek out an American unit and surrender.
The size of the unit they found was approximately only a score.
And the amazing scene of formal surrender through an interpreter to an American general is now recorded.
General Alster, has surrendered the units remaining with him because with the means in his hands, he had not the ability to break through to the German frontier.
Accordingly, he surrendered his command, these marching groups, the foot troops, and the service elements to the United States Army.
General Alster,
Acting for the commanding general of the 9th United States Army, Lieutenant General William H. Simpson, and on behalf of the Army of the United States, I accept your surrender.
You, your officers and men will be given treatment in accordance with the principles of the Geneva Convention.
They were allowed to approach with their arms and ammunition because they said they feared the vengeance of the Mackie if they left themselves defenseless on the way.
They're losing the war.
They've had enough of it.
And so they surrender and get out of it.
No such easy course lay open to the millions of innocent men and women who didn't want a war when the Germans started it.
They had to live through five years of fury.
Countless thousands of innocent people had to die in agony.
But Europe's bullies have had enough of their war until next time they feel they're strong enough to win.
Even amid the satisfaction we feel in these days of our victory we must ask ourselves what they may do in the future.
And remember what they have done in the past.