Making his first public appearance in London since VE Day, Field Marshal Montgomery receives a great welcome when he visits the Mansion House for the Diamond Jubilee meeting of the Gordon Boys School.
Among the many German leaders now in the Allied Net is Field Marshal von Rundstedt, whose ill-fated offensive in the Ardennes was one of the last counterblows of the Wehrmacht in the West.
Field Marshal Kesselring, whose forces were beaten back slowly but surely from Sicily to the Brenner Pass.
Vi har marshal från Klajst, hos Pantzer Divisions, som begann den germanska Blitzkriegen 1939.
Saj Sinkwart, regeringschef i Polen 1940, och den hatade kommissionären i Holland till 1945.
En av Hitlers chefpuppet, Admiral Horthy, den skiftiga ex-regenten av Hungary.
Och den rikaste plumpen som faller från den nazistiska trädet, Hermann Göring, den bulkiga wolfen av den tredje riksdagen, som redan ser ut att komma in i några utsida skivor.
The jovial curves and innocent expression of this chief Nazi criminal will deceive no one at his forthcoming trial.
Troops of the New Zealand Division played a big part in the liberation of Trieste, that awkwardly placed Adriatic port.
In Trieste itself, men of the Eighth Army and of Marshal Tito's partisans get together in the friendliest fashions.
Mr. Molotov impresses the conference with his great sincerity in the issues that lie ahead.
Mr. Eden was elected joint president of the conference with the American Secretary of State.
As the news of peace in Europe comes to the Great Assembly, the thoughts of all peoples turn to San Francisco as the first avenue to a broader and firmer understanding between those who have proved such unshakable allies in war.
Operation Pluto.
P-L-U-T-O.
ställning på pipeline under det.
Det är där det var flexibel pipeline av basis av en submarin.
Cable var först önskast i 1942.
Det finns en jämförelse med en ministerin charge av Petroleum Warfare Departement.
En blodlöj man fattade den chief av Combined Operations.
Resultatet var en experimental pipeline med det ledde på ett speciellt flexibla covering.
Någon annars var hejs.
A trial length of the Hayes pipeline was then laid across the Bristol channel by combined operations personnel.
The experiment worked in spite of difficulties and petrol was delivered successfully from Swansea to North Devon and Cornwall.
Another type of pipeline, the Hamel, was also being tried out.
Engineering firms had a scheme for welding steel pipe into any given length with enough flexibility to enable it to be wound onto a large floating drum.
Men i sådant sekret jag begänt att det följde tre kvartomar längs av dessa mänskliga flexibla stjärnpajp.
All ready to be väldigt kontinuerligt längs av målen färdiga maj.
HMS Persephone var specifikt för att hugga fram för att vända pipeline direkt från miljard.
Tänk på det farsightedness av premier vårdade absolut prioriterade för att värda för fantastisk skinn hade väl upptäckt en du av mig till plan.
D-Day 1944, invasningen av Frankrike och den stora testen för operationen Pluto.
Anledningen till att lägga den stora längden av pip var skapad av Royal Navy, hans pipläggande drömmar, kallade HMS Conundrums, var snart engagerade i att lägga den första petroliumsuppgiften över den engelska kanalen.
Speciellt anställda varger var använda för att röra på sidorna av linjerna på sjön för att bli sammanfattade med en pumpningsstation.
I sekreta platser på engelska sjön var dessa högpressurstationer konstruerade och kamuflagrerade i de mest omöjliga byggnaderna, som plångränser och sjövillor.
Musik Musik Musik Musik Musik
Hjälpt av flamtrådarna av Petroleum- och kärleksverksamheten fanns Boulogne harbord och ännu fler pipeline kom tillbaka till de viktiga siffrorna av olja, som snart flöjde på en miljon galloner per dag från Mersey till Rhineland.
Den stora operationen var slut, och runt omkring oss rullade de mekanisera massorna fram till vänster.
Varje tidsmönster var på rädslan för att köra ut ett briljant och därende beteende, utan vilket kriget fortfarande skulle råda över continenten i Europa.
Across Europe in 1940 the triumphant Nazi legions march for the glory of their Führers new order which was to be a model to the world.
Country after country fell to the advancing hordes until the shattering collapse of France.
The hand of God brought about the miracle of Dunkirk and Britain stood alone.
With hardly a pause Hitler unleashed his Luftwaffe on his greatest objective, Britain herself.
For the people of our land the battle of Britain had become a crusade against the powers of evil.
The prime minister's words proclaim the true meaning of the Hitler creed.
What tragedies, what horrors, what crimes has Hitler and all that Hitler stands for brought upon Europe and the world.
The concentration camps are overcrowded.
Every dawn the firing parties are at their work.
If Germany had tried to invade the British Isles after the French collapse in June 1940, and if Japan had declared war on the British Empire and the United States at about the same date, no one can say what disasters and agonies might not have been allotted.
In the sunlit skies over Britain in 1940, providence and the matchless courage of our airmen gave the vital breathing space required by the forces of freedom before they could strike back.
The torch that was kindled then was carried in the great offensive which began at Alamein and Stalingrad and which has now swept the enemy back along every front in Europe.
Den senaste bilden visar Leipzigs stad som är skadad när kriget kommer till en krisen.
I mitten av den svåra stridskriget blev kameran död efter att ha tagit den här bilden.
Leipzig has fallen and to the accompaniment of white flags the allied forces occupy the city.
In the town hall the mayor of Leipzig together with his wife and daughter had chosen death by poisoning rather than face the consequences of the hideous crimes discovered at the nearby camp.
In to the city of Nuremberg, once sacred to the meetings of the Nazi party, our advance sweeps on.
The Adolf Hitler Stadium, where the Fuhrer shouted his threats and defiance at the world, is now a deserted battlefield.
Trains of the American 8th Air Force and the RAF give the enemy no rest as he desperately tries to reorganize and regroup.
A burning enemy plane spirals to earth in a last slow dive.
Bomberkommand Lancasters in a heavy raid on Schwinemunde have knocked out Germany's last pocket battleship Lützow.
12,000 pounders take toll of the fourth German battleship to be sunk by Bomberkommand.
Magdeburg kommer också under en hård attack från luften efter att den tyska kommandoren förvandlade sig.
Efter bombarderingen börjar den första vändningen av tankar slå in.
De fiskar när de förväntar sig på den skrämmande bestämda staden.
Dags efter dag såg det ut som att nazi-prisoner var på högsta nivå.
Fler och fler av Hitlerens ungdomar, några av dem mindre än 12 år, följde med de veteraner i staden.
All these boys have fought in the field and all of them have been brought up with a fanatical belief in their destiny as a master race.
Every German child must have this poisonous doctrine eliminated from its mind.
The doctrine of racial superiority which twice in our lifetime has plunged Europe into darkness and desolation.
For the sake of our own children we must not allow ourselves to be deceived a third time.
Humanity cries out that the atrocious deeds committed in the name of Germany must never again desecrate the earth.