Den finländska flygkraften har haft den mest välkomna tjänsten att ta ut den officiella libereringen av de upprättade länderna av Skandinavien, började med Danmarks kapital, Copenhagen.
När flygplanen tog sig ner på Kastrup-flygplatsen har det varit en lycklig rörelse framöver av den danska patrioten, som sedan den germanska ockupationen har väntat och hoppats på den här stora momenten.
Framför processen med sitt varje med de andra stränga av avbrevet om nationen och tillbaka med hälflöst victim av avbrytande av passivt över färdigt rätt.
In the harbour of Copenhagen, the navy is represented by the cruisers Dido and Birmingham, accompanied by four destroyers.
The crowds on the quayside give their crews an overwhelming reception.
In another part of the harbour lie two of the last remaining surface ships of the German navy, the cruisers Prinzeugen and Nuremberg, whose destiny is now in the hands of the Allies.
Back in the town, the chairs of the crowd change to chairs as one of the few Danish quizlings is led away to await his trial.
Amid the festivities, the first contingent of German servicemen and women begins the long march back to German soil.
Kopenhagen trillade av nyheterna om deras hero av tiden, Field Marshal Montgomery.
Field Marshal inspecterar en regering av Royal Marines, som kompisar spelade en så fin del i att göra det möjligt att krossa rigen.
Field Marshal Montgomery
Sex miles of caring people gave a tumultuous and heartfelt welcome to the allied leader who had helped to relieve their country of nearly 300,000 invaders.
King Christian is on his way to the opening of the first Danish parliament to be held since 1943.
With thankfulness to her deliverers, Denmark steps forward along her own path once again.
The day of victory in Europe was the day of freedom for Norway, isolated from our allies since 1940.
The first British party to enter Oslo is greeted by the chief of the German ground forces, putting up an oily show of friendship which is coldly rejected.
Vår kameramän kunde inte filma välkomstscenen så stor var den deliriska receptionen.
I fem år har frihetsspiriten i Norge aldrig falterat.
De norska patrioterna fortsatte med att sabotera, medan hela nationen höll på med att lyssna på radiovisning från London.
Vi glädjer oss för de galna människorna i Norge i denna utsträckning av frihetsfortressen.
Från en alpine villa söderutom Brenna pass har allieringarna fått individuell frihet till noterbara fängare från nästan varje land i Europa.
En tysk, hållbar av de tyskarna, Pastor Niemöller, som stod ständigt i sin tro, i förhållande till det nazistiska partiet.
General Papagas, som var regeringschef av den grekiska armén, tills att Axis-kraften steg på sitt land.
De fria brittiska kvinnorna av kriget innehåller lieutenant Michael Alexander, en kvinna av fieldmarschall, kapten John Elphinstone, fru av kvinnan, och Lord Lascelles, fru av kriget.
Folk i de brittiska islarna glömmer att primärministerns vikteriproclamation om att våra äldsta Channelsjärnor skulle bli fri på sistone.
På kvartalet av Destroyer Bulldog var regeringens regeringen Heiner som regerade.
With the unconditional surrender complete, British troops go ashore.
As they march through the streets of St.
Peter Port our troops receive the concentrated welcome of a people who have suffered five years of misery in the only part of the United Kingdom ever to be overrun by Germany.
Our men give their own cigarettes to the islanders who have been without such a luxury since June 1940.
The Nazi invader ran very true to form but his weapons are now surrendered and stolen Jersey cattle restored to their rightful owners.
The people of the islands forget their starvation in the joyful knowledge that their home is now back in the family circle from which it had been absent for so long.
They continued and well deserved prosperity and happiness followed the return of the Union Jack to the sunlit islands of the English Channel.