Det är klart att det är en del av minen.
Det är en del av minen.
And the next job is to remove the detonator cap.
Here it is, the heart of a modern mine.
Now we can take things more easily.
By stage they take the mine to pieces.
They remove the horns.
And the whole detonating mechanism comes out.
Han är det ekallt.
Det är inte det.
Det är det.
Fortunately many of these seeds failed to grow into a harvest of tragedy and destruction.
But they serve to remind us again of the inhuman methods of the Nazis.
They are also a sign of our own strength.
The instruments of Germany's blitzkrieg have become playthings on the beach.
Don't look now, but I think it reminds me of somebody.
And here's your chance of seeing the inside of a mind.
Just like our radio after fathers mended it.
Det här är en del av det.
Tack så mycket.
All members of all crews at all times wear life belts.
And certainly these men with hearts of oak know that it's a wise precaution.
Long low ships of the Royal Navy keep up a constant patrol in and out of our lines.
Watchdogs on the alert for our safety.
Throughout day and night we are in constant touch with the escorting warships by semaphore and radio.
While the captain keeps the course carefully checked to the nth degree.
All this time we have the additional comforting knowledge that the naval air arm is watching over us.
The air still rules the waves.
A warning of hostile aircraft is passed from ship to ship.
But we assume we are short by the escorting warships and we breathe again.
Another bit of excitement came our way.
One of the destroyers, a Milor, dropped a death charge.
Just on suspicion, as our skipper said.
However, all is well that ends well.
And soon our convoy approaches harbor with never a casualty to report.
Over 100,000 tons of goods delivered to schedule by the grandest navy in the world.
As we drop anchor, the warships bid us farewell.
They are all ready, all for another job.
Every week that passes, more British ships are being equipped to defend themselves from attack.
At dockyards all over the world, new and secret anti-submarine guns are being mounted.
Gun crews are being trained from the merchant seamen.
And when the attack comes... These men have had only a few hours training.
Their job is to carry Britain's trade through the dangers of war at sea.
Nu kommer de också att bli framgångsfattare i norra och norra Paris.
Och det finns ingen änglighet mellan dem och Jack Frost.
I verkligheten, en av de pojkarna säger att de inte vill upprätthålla för en förhållande.
Och när de når en sjö har de alla förhållanden.
Förra gången är det U-böck-kommander som tar hand om förhållandet.
Någon kallar ut, är du inte glad att få av dig allt?
Det är inte för Britten att svara på det.
Inte för staden i Downing Street, inte för Black Cat, inte för Mr Greenwood, som är ledare av oppositionen, inte för medlemmarna av kabinettet när de lämnar en annan momentös mötning.
Ansvaret är med en man över sjön.
Our mind is made up, our position is clear.
That must surely be the gist of the message which Ambassador Sir Neville Henderson takes back with him to Germany.
And the solid mass of the crowd surging round his car are a symbol of the fact that the British people are more firmly of one mind today than at any other time in our history.
In the crisis a year ago, when Mr Chamberlain flew east as Sir Neville is flying now, Germany, in spite of her violent methods, still claimed the right to bring her own people within her own boundaries.
She dropped that principle when she marched into Czechoslovakia and our ranks were united in one solid anti-aggression front.
So Neville Henderson also takes the knowledge of that unity with him as he starts back on his momentous journey.
The women of Britain stand with the men.
Her Majesty the Queen brings a lesson to us all as leaving her children in Scotland she returns to London and we are glad to see her.
As workers evacuate the hoods and records of business into the country, what are they saying and thinking on the street corners?
Nowhere is there any wild patriotic excitement, but everywhere there is a deep hatred of war.
There is complete confidence in British power, if it should be brought to the test, but there is no confidence in the power of violence and slaughter to make the world a better place to live in.
En brittisk brottsforskare bortspridnings till mål av arbetet för att förbättra.
Men det är inte bara för mig, för mig, för mig, för mig, för mig, för mig.
Det här är en av de flesta av de flesta av de flesta av de flesta
och gick i full sped så snabbt som vi kunde för att försöka döda honom.
Vi skickade ut en SOS och snart efter tog vi till båten eftersom stjärnorna var för nära.
Och snart efter det såg vi en av flygplatserna som vi tog till att vara en av våra egna och de tog ut en stål.
De här personerna från flygplatsen kom ner på ytan
Och så tog vi oss alla med.
Jag tackar Gud att vi har en så effektiv service.
Och vi har inget att oroa oss för.
Och piloten av RAF Flygbåten, hans namn måste fortfarande vara en sekret.
Ja, kapten.
Jag är väldigt glad att vi var i vägen på den tiden.
Och att vi kunde ge dig och din kropp lite hjälp.
Jag tackar dig väldigt mycket för den skönt sätt som du räddade min kropp och mig själv.
Tack.