It's morning at Drottningholm.
The swans are taking their morning swim and the kings sheep are grazing in the soft meadows.
The beautiful castle, the summer residence of the king of Sweden, glistens in the morning sun.
It's a little after nine, and the king's already at breakfast, making his own tea to be sure it's just the right strength.
The rest of his breakfast consists of soft boiled eggs and toast.
The king is a busy man, with a busy day ahead of him, so he needs a reasonably early start.
Even if he has kept late hours the night before,
He's always punctual at breakfast.
And if he's going hunting or fishing, he gets up at six in order to spend as much of the day as possible in the open.
He's a great sportsman.
But today is an ordinary work day.
And the valet de chambre, when he comes in with the morning papers, finds his royal master at his desk.
A businessman always reads the news carefully enough in his favorite newspaper.
But think how much more carefully a king must read the news in all the papers to get a clear picture of current events, which, as we know, can change from one hour to the next.
After he has finished, he and his attendants, the Lord Chamberlain and an aide, get into his car to drive to Stockholm, about 12 miles away, where further duties of state await him, among them a cabinet meeting.
The palace guard comes to attention in honor of the army's commander in chief as the royal car drives through the park.
The king will be coming very shortly through these handsomely carved and painted doors in the royal palace in Stockholm on his way from his own apartment to the council chambers.
It's a long walk through many beautiful rooms and halls.
Here he enters the gallery of the Bernadotts where his ancestors looked down upon him out of their heavy gilt frames.
He has been through these rooms many times before and as always, precisely at the appointed hour, his majesty, King Gustav V, passes the bowing secretaries in the ante-room to enter the council chamber where the cabinet is assembled.
With a friendly smile and nod, he strides into the room and shakes hands with his cabinet ministers.
Bagge, Dumö, Eriksson, Sköld, Wigfors, Ramstorp, and the prime minister.
They exchange a few words before the meeting is convened.
Someone inquires perhaps about his majesty's health.
Another his hunting luck.
Someone else may mention a recent game of tennis.
But there's business to take care of.
So the members of the cabinet take their places around a large table laden with books of law, statute rolls and important papers.
The crown in council.
Den högsta administrativa kraften i landet, regeringen och rådgivarna börjar jobba.
Medan de jobbar är regeringens lunch förberedd.
Låt oss se vad som krävs i regeringens klocka.
There's Monsieur Robert, the king's French chef, hurrying in his own gallic way to get the lunch ready.
The king likes fish, and Monsieur is putting the finishing touches to a delicious dish called Baltic Herring a la Herningsholm.
Mmm, it's too bad the taste film hasn't been invented yet, because to judge from the chef's contented look, it must be good.
Yes, it's ready.
And there it goes, off to the king's apartment.
But wait a minute, where's the music coming from?
Oh yes of course it's the changing of the guard in the outer courtyard of the palace.
Let's join the other spectators and watch for a moment.
Kort efter lunchen är det tid som kringen ger publiken.
Det finns alltid en stadig ström av besökare som går upp på den stora staden och alla har samma ärende.
Att prata med kringen.
Today there are so many, they will have time to see only a few.
For instance, there's the foreign secretary, and in conversation with him, the governor general.
Och här är Lord Chamberlain i väntan, för att förklara att hans majestät ska få till regeringssekreteraren.
Han visar hans excellens till skrivboken.
Som ni kan föreställa er, har regeringssekreteraren mycket att säga till kungen, för en av sina tjänster är att hålla kungen informerad om den förändrade politiska situationen utomlands.
Regeringssekreteraren, som också är Sveriges högsta politisk officiell,
has many things to discuss too, and judging from appearances, the conversation interests both of them.
Here's another visitor, the first commissioner of Sweden, and incidentally a fine poet, Gunnar Maskall Silverstolpe.
He has a rare find to show the king, who is an enthusiastic collector of silver, and who especially likes the large, massive tankards.
The King, known to sports fans as Mr. G, is almost as famous in the tennis world as Bill Tilden.
He is and has been for many years the white sports Swedish ambassador.
He still plays a good game and is an excellent subject for his footman's 16mm film camera.
How many of you think you'll be able to do this at the age of 85?
I'm only asking.
The King is light on his feet and he drives the ball over the net with plenty of force.
Mellan spel, en mörk, men undervisande ungdom, frågar för sin autograf.
Och får den!
Vänta tills barnen i skolan ser det.
Kringen ser ganska glad ut för det också.
När kringen kommer hem efter en timme hård spel, hittar han räddning i bränsle.
He has done this sort of handwork for many years, perhaps because while he works the Venetian pattern, his favorite, he has time and leisure to think.
At the moment he's probably thinking of the things he would like to discuss with the crown prince and princess today.
He's expecting them for tea.
The crown prince and princess arrive from their castle in Ulriksdal and pass through the blue room to the drawing room where the tea table is set.
Där meeting is a cheerful one father and son shake hands heartily and the crown prince inquires.
How are you, dad?
No servants are present at tea time, as this is a family gathering, and they wish to speak of personal matters without being disturbed.
The crown princess always acts as hostess and passes the cakes Monsieur Robert has baked.
Head of the family sits and speaks of family affairs with his oldest son and successor.
A lot of things are bound to happen in any large family, and so it is with the kings.
If father and son come up against a problem, they turn to the crown princess who smiles and answers quite to their satisfaction.
The Crown Prince describes some recent military exercises, and while the Crown Princess is telling an amusing story about the King's great-grandchildren, the camera shows us the portrait of the King's beloved wife, the late Queen Victoria.
The King enjoys the stories about his great-grandchildren, and his eyes shine with interest as he listens and comments.
Yes, he's a fine great-granddad.
But there are still official duties to be fulfilled.
This one is the opening of a national defense show.
Upon his arrival, he shakes hands and salutes the numerous officials and representatives of different organizations.
Jag vill tala om en tacksamhet för er vänlighet att anmåla mig att förrätta detta i den här invigningen.
under uttalande och ta min uppriktiga glädje över att denna utställning nu blivit denna besvarsutställning nu blivit anordnad och öppnad samt med mina bästa velönsningar för den samma.
Nu förklarar jag nu utställningen öppnad och invigd.
Evening has come
När kingens returnen drottningholm.
Aftonrad är det mänting dig.
Varje dag ens.
Det får på en lajt så fara det var spred vånt en tjej.
Men det kan ju inte sveit kan man inte det blir ju brun.
Vad är det här kom på tjejer som fanns i öppen färgplats.
Och nu har kungen en stund att prata med de kvinnorna på kvällen, titta på kvällens avsnitt, smaka en cigarett,
En vänkisk koffej.
Men hans jobb är inte slut ännu.
Många dokument måste sänkas för att bli valida.
Enligt en gammal custom är krigets signaturer alltid gröna med sand.
Några av beslutna är resultatet av morgons säsong av crown council.
Och när kriget har skrivit sin namn till dem börjar han dem på deras väg.
All these documents together represent everyday life in Sweden.
They are the nations pulse.
And with the completion of this last duty, the father of the people brings his day to a close.
I.