You, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, do solemnly swear that you will faithfully execute the office of President of the United States and will, to the best of your ability, preserve, protect and defend the Constitution of the United States.
So help you God.
I, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, do solemnly swear...
That I will faithfully execute the office of President of the United States and will to the best of my ability preserve, protect and defend the Constitution of the United States.
So help me God.
Jag.
Och då.
Där finns din ägarej, var är sparska älskar sig?
Var vill du se på min älskar, du är snabb i dina grejer.
Du är sin egen älskar, du är så där förbättrad.
Tack till elever och personer som hjälpte med videon!
Varsågod.
Qabira Yamala, Qabira Yamala Qabira Yamala, Qabira Yamala Qabira Yamala, Qabira Yamala
Excella.