Andel!
Vär god insats säger jag tack för idag.
Vissa öjeblickar har vi upplevt samman.
Men aldrig har så två tider vilat överlagas som nu.
Det infördes sammanhåll.
Och icke blev uttidigt ställningstegeningen.
uppnår vi något här hemma.
Så förenar vi oss i ett livet, vårt gamla och eviga unge väderna.
Danmark!
Leve!
Japanese bombers over New Guinea.
ACAC guns manned by American gunners go into action.
But the enemy scores a hit on a fuel dump.
There's 100 octane aviation spirit and high grade lubricating oil in that smoke.
And there's no point in pretending that this kind of thing doesn't happen.
Australian infantrymen set to work to remove the untouched barrels from the danger zone.
Minimizing the damage.
Ensuring continuation of the blitz in the Pacific.
And here is the task force of the United States Pacific Fleet north of Guadalcanal.
The first round in the battle of the Philippines is over.
Allt som är kvar för en film att visa är den smärta utrymme- av en enkla och enklare grupp island.
Även om Corregidor håller ut- och ändå minnen om Bataan aldrig dör- så är det verkligheten idag.
Japan har tagit tillbaka tillbaka- till de lyckliga platserna i Pacifik.
För fyra månader fanns amerikansk och filippinansk armé i rörelse.
Bomber från hög nivå och låg nivå.
De förtjänade mer än vi trodde.
Även i de här åren av en värld som vet för mycket om människan.
Det här var staden på Luzon.
De var bostäder av en kraftfull kraft.
De tog i krig när det krävs, och tog krigarna tillbaka.
MacArthurs namn är säker bland heroerna av åren.
Det namnet av alla soldater som kämpade med honom på Patan.
is worthy of an equal place in the roll of fame.
But against the overwhelming odds that Japan flung into the scale they could not keep the balance.
What next?
Canada, another surprise for all concerned.
A mass production plant in the Great Dominion turning out mosquitoes.
One of the fastest aircraft in any sky, whether bomber or fighter.
Made of plywood, light but reliable.
Det är säkert en av de dödligaste armarna som allmänna har.
De har en användbar bombardering och tillräckligt kraftig kraft för att göra det en farlig motståndare.
De var moskéter som skickade ut Berlin vid morgonen när Goebbels och Göring försökte utreda.
De kommer att bli moskéter som kommer att stänga de tyska i de mest skrämmande ställen.
Allt du vill köpa idag är svårt att få och kostnadsfullt.
Bladet som var för att skapa byggnader går nu in i de här bombarderingarna.
Men det fungerar bra.
The wood that is going to make these bombers will keep Hitler awake at night.
And the bride who has to do without a bed can get some sleep on the floor.
The last story in our American dispatch for the week.
The passing out of RAF cadets in a camp in the USA.
Nearly two years ago America started giving instruction to air crews for Britain's Royal Air Force.
When Empire airfields and training camps were strained to the very limit.
This good service by good neighbors is now ending.
This is the last class to be trained within Uncle Sam's friendly shores.
Very friendly.
Thanks for the help you gave us.
America's own growing air forces now need all the training grounds they can get.
And Empire RAF schools have expanded to train all the air crews we need.
So America says goodbye.
And soon Berlin will be saying hello.
Till Kalifornien.
Filippinerna som har blivit amerikanska medlemmar formar nu USAs första filippiniska regimens.
Det här är den rörelse som har gjort en så bestämd ställning i Filippinerna under general MacArthur.
Företagande japoniska inch by inch på Batan-peninsulan.
En värdig tillgänglighet till allierade krigspower.
Now to the Pacific.
Somewhere above that vast ocean, land and seaplanes are searching for the crew of a lost bomber.
And among the survivors that they hope to find is an American general, Brigadier General Twining.
They had been forced down by lack of petrol whilst out on what is called a combat mission.
The lookout spots two tiny rafts containing 15 men in all.
They had lived on those rafts for six days with only a little water, a bar of chocolate and a tin of sardines to sustain them.
They also managed to shoot two seabirds.
In peacetime this would have been a headline story.
Today in the welter of every conceivable kind of hardship and horror it's just a story.
But it's a story that can't be told too often if it reminds us of what others are doing.
Ullhid äpulta Dunan medvänjel, ahol 1938-ban a felvidéki területek visszachatolásakor honvédeink elősör lépték át a fojamot.
Hållet, som följer Danmark, är fortfarande i fritid.
Varga József, minister för handels- och kommunikation, berättade historien om hållet.
A hatalmas uj alkotást Magyarország kormányzója adta át a forgalomna.