In the night of Tuesday and before Wednesday's daylight a multitude of little ships was stealing through the darkness of the English Channel headed for the French seaside resort of Dieppe.
A hail of gunfire tore apart the stillness.
När de första gröna sträckorna av morgonen började släcka ner mörkret, såg det ut som om det var dyrt.
Oerhört utsläppande, grimmigt intressant.
Började göra den första stora rörelsen på franska regeringar.
Combined operations.
Operational aerodroms in Britain had preparations well advanced.
Ready to fit into a timetable where seconds are more precious than pearls.
This is not a world of time divided into day and night.
It is an endless day split into light and darkness.
Zero hour for bomber and fighter and coastal command.
Be proud as they roar towards the rising sun.
Blood brothers of the gods of thunder.
Below them on the sea those angular forms are taking shape.
The lifting haze reveals them.
A hostile sea alive with impertinent little boats.
For two years the Nazis have been building Dieppe defenses and they are going to find out how tough they are.
För första gången sen 1940 tar vi tankar till Frankrike och kringar svenskar.
Den röda navn tar med sig trupperna, men alla tre anställda arbetar tillsammans.
Och här går den första småskärmen, som drar cirklar av ovislighet runt rådgivarna.
Vi är på sjön nu.
Detta är Dieppe.
The force is composed mainly of Canadians.
The rest, commandos, marines and infantrymen of the United Nations, including a force of American commandos called Rangers.
Highly trained, superbly daring and confident.
But no one has underestimated the fearful hazards they're facing.
Never a minute must pass without that screen of Royal Air Force in the sky.
And the battles that developed equaled the Battle of Britain.
That ball of flame is one German plane shut down.
Våra rådgivare landade på olika byggnader.
Alla våra bilder kommer från båten eller från luften.
Det är en annan parti som släpper in.
Oppositionen är tuffa.
Nu släpper en annan relä av den ständiga luftuppståndaren ut.
Fyrs mer krig och en annan krig är släppt ner.
Off the French coast the minutes slowly tick away, each one a century.
The German propaganda machine had immediately set to work to pretend that this was a second front, the long talked of invasion of Europe.
Men avsnittet från Britannien var klart från början att det var inget sådant.
Det var en rekommendation i kraft, skjutsning på en gigantisk skala.
Att hitta viktiga information om naziens försörjning av Europa som de håller i släveri.
Försörjning från libereringen, de torsdagade med brunt passion.
Mer styrning för luften.
Över deras händer har en annan skattekombat slutats.