I cannot help but reflect it.
That if my father had been American and my mother British instead of the other way around I might have got here on my own.
Then of course he had a new word for the Duce.
The boastful Mussolini had crumpled already.
He is now but a lackey and a circus
The merest utensil of his masters will.
For many months we devoted ourselves to preparing to take the offensive in Libya.
The very considerable battle which has been proceeding there for the last six weeks in the desert has been most fiercely fought on both sides.
For the first time we have made the unfeel, the sharp edge of those tools with which he has enslaved Europe.
I am so glad to be able to place before you, members of the Senate and of the House of Representatives, at this moment, when you are entering the war, the proof that with proper weapons
and proper organization we are able to beat the life out of the savage Nazi.
What Hitlerism is suffering in Libya is only a sample and a foretaste of what we have got to give him and his accomplices wherever this war should lead us in every quarter of the globe.
The prime minister next turn to Japan.
What kind of a people do they think we are?
Is it possible they do not realize that we shall never cease to persevere against them until they have been taught a lesson which they and the world will never forget?
As the premier spoke we received these pictures from Canada.
Our great dominion on the American continent is on the alert against this new threat from Japan.
Along the Pacific coast, Canadian infantry, artillery and the Royal Canadian Air Force are ready to meet and attack if it comes.
In America, Colonel Knox attended the annual graduation of US Navy cadets.
But this year the ceremony was charged with greater significance.
The attack without warning on the American Navy at Pearl Harbor has welded the United States into closer unity.
A great surge of patriotism has swept the American continent.
ARP has come to life.
In every city and town in the danger zone they are applying the lessons already learnt in Britain.
Where there's light, there's life.
And to the axis where there's life is a good place to drop bombs.
In a world at war we receive from the corners of the earth evidence of the growing brotherhood of the free men who fight tyranny.
For the reason we must go back to Mr. Churchill in Congress.
If you will allow me to use other language I will say that he must indeed
Havar a blind soul.
Who cannot see that some great purpose and design is being worked out here below.
Of which we have the honor to be the faithful servants.
It is not given to us to peer into the mysteries of the future.
Still I avow my hope and faith.
Sure and inviolate.
Det är inte det.
This is the second part of the story of our prime minister's war conference in the new world.
Following his stirring speech to congress in Washington, Mr. Churchill attended the Senate and House of Commons in Ottawa.
He was welcomed there by a Canadian guard of honor.
Mr Churchill was introduced by Prime Minister Mackenzie King and received a tremendous ovation from the combined houses of Canada's government.
We have been concerning the united pacts and resolves of more than 30 states and nations to fight on in unity together and in fidelity one with another without any thought except the totals
And final extirpation of the Hitler tyranny of the Japanese frenzy and the Mussolini flop.
As a fitting tribute to French Canadians, Mr. Churchill also spoke in French.
...dans la grande compagnie des nations libératrices et victorieuses.
The peoples of the British Empire may love peace.
They do not seek the lands or wealth of any country.
But they are a tough and hardy lot.
We have not journeyed all this way across the centuries, across the oceans, across the mountains, across the prairies, because we are made of sugar candy.
Look at the Londoners, the Cockneys.
Look what they stood up to.
Grim and gay.
With their cry, we can take it.
And their wartime mood.
What's good enough for anybody, good enough for us.
We'll not ask that the rules of the game should be modified.
If any, we shall never descend to the German and Japanese level.
But if anybody likes to play rough we can play rough too.
The premier then referred to a discussion with the French government before the fall of France.
When I warned them that Britain would fight on alone whatever they did their generals told their prime minister and his divided cabinet in three weeks England
We'll have a neck wrung like a chicken.
Some chicken.
Some neck.
För resten lämnar vi beskrivningen till Mr. Eden.
Vi måste arbeta tillsammans för att vinna varje farm och fjäll.
Nu har tiderna stigit.
Vi såg vad som säkert har varit en scen av ganska tuff kämpning.
Några mil norr av Klint.
Russiska och germanska tankar blev knackade ut på vägen.
I en dödlig, människa-suffering av den här kriget.
En hållbar frihet för alla deras människor.
Journalbilderna från ryska fronten visar bara förödelse och förödelse i det oändliga.
Men här är det motsatsen, här är det uppbyggnad.
Ej långt från stridszonen, det är vid Volga.
Det är ryssarna som här bygger ett av världens väldigaste kraftverk.
Man frågar sig, ska det kunna rädda det undan krigets förödelse eller ska det väldiga och imponerande kraftverket söndersmulas?