Japanese police gather by the hundreds on the outskirts of Tokyo as the expansion of the US air base brings renewed opposition.
US planes continue to fly overhead as tense farmers and police below approach open conflict.
The arrival of surveyors touches off the explosion.
Rice straw is set afire and the smoke fanned toward the surveyors in an attempt to halt the survey.
Den infurierande mobbningen, med omkring 500 vänsterländska organisationer, skapar en tråkig krig, men blir snabbt flyttad tillbaka av den japanska polisen.
Och USA-flöden fortsätter att flytta över huvudet, symboliskt för Airforces betydelse för att uppnå den här försäkringslänken mot kommunistisk aggression.
Prehistoric Monsters in Calgary's Municipal Zoo.
Every variety of the huge animals that roamed the world some 50 million years ago stand here in life-sized replicas.
The youngsters of the Canadian city have the world's largest paleontology garden to play in.
There's nothing more gentle than a concrete dinosaur.
The animals were built by John Canerva, every one sculptured with scientific exactness.
Outdoor fun and lessons in prehistoric history all at the same time.
On September 23, President Eisenhower enjoyed his favorite sport at a Denver country club.
Examined only a few days previously by his personal physician, he was considered to be in the best of health.
Just back from four days of relaxation at his mountain retreat, the chief executive, soon to be 65, gave the appearance of a man in tip-top shape.
En sannolik lirat i smådörren Lars Holm.
Vi måste ta en del av vad vi först dägnat oss att det är just det varpset.
Kort tid efter hittills transferd till Fitsimmons Armehospital.
Efter hittills admission to a suite av de ett flera av det här.
Det var först för en beskockning ljuset i en så för den mild coronary thrombosis.
Från Washington kring presssekretär Hagerty interrupterade vacation.
En krono Thomas Mattingly, en hartspecialist från Walter Reed Hospital.
En annan tillgänglighet var presidentens enda son, Major John.
Redan då var presidenten i lugn och John gick upp till hans mamma för att dela rum med henne.
Från Boston kom Dr. Paul Dudley White, en av nationens högsta kardioexperter.
Hans prognos var en som unga miljoner ville höra, eftersom det tyckte ut att vara en förhoppning.
Mr. Haggerty berättade pressen om resultatet av den hårda examineringen.
The doctors found the president's condition improving, that complete recovery is possible, and that after two months of rest he might resume his full duties once more.
To a world that considers the president the foremost champion of international friendship, this was welcome news.
Meanwhile in Washington, Vice President Richard Nixon, on whose shoulders the burdens of heavier responsibility have already fallen, comments on the course to be followed during the president's illness.
Jag har blivit frågad många frågor kring den politiska och andra utmaningarna av presidentens sjukdom.
Min ansvar till alla dessa frågor är att uttrycka den oro som jag delar med alla amerikanska människor för den tidiga och kompletta förbättringen av presidenten.
Jämfört med detta, alla andra frågor är inte värda att kommentera.
I stället har jag
The business of government will continue as usual under an administration which has been organized by the president to operate effectively in his absence.
And the people of America, the people of other countries, can be sure that the United States will continue to go forward under the Eisenhower foreign and domestic policies.
Jag har en fyrtio.
President!
Presidiet över.
Mr Vice President, my very dear friends.
I am deeply honored that so many of you should come down to welcome Mrs Eisenhower and I back to Washington.
It's been a little longer stay than we had planned, but the circumstances you will understand.
I am happy the doctors have given me at least a parole, if not a pardon.
and I expect to be back at my accustomed duties although they say I must ease my way into them and not bulldoze my way into them.
To each of you who have come down of course we would like to speak personally and thank you for the honor you have done us.
That is impossible and so possibly in just saying
Thank you.
We are grateful.
You will understand what we would like to do and you will let the wish take the place of the deed.
Thank you very much indeed.