All-star-basketball på Kaliforniens Marienland.
Här är öppningen och saker börjar röra sig när den spediga Porpoise-kvintetten rör den.
Det är en flippa-dippa av ett spel från början till slut.
Och när det kommer till sharp shooting för basketet, så här.
Sealen älskar det när deep-sea-champen går in i en annan skrämning.
De tar på sig det här spelet som undergrader på Old Siwash.
Slik, deceptisk spel här.
Ingen dribbling.
De skjuter för fiskar som de skjuter för fiskar.
Det måste vara en dolphin i staden.
Men spelet fortsätter med entusiasm.
Porpoisen är en av de lyckligaste gamstörerna i djupet, särskilt när varje fisk betyder nåt trevligt.
Skål, en annan herring!
A blast that is heard throughout Cape Canaveral.
And in the Florida night the man-made meteor soared to launch in orbit America's first satellite.
To break a Soviet monopoly on the road to the moon.
With the explorer circling the earth the Pentagon rejoices.
And Defense Secretary McElroy tells of the...
Kom igen, kom igen!
A whole new town is resettled on Formosa by refugees of the Tachans.
It was just a year ago that 18,000 Chinese, young and old, evacuated those offshore islands before they were swallowed up by the reds.
Nearly 300 families will live here and earn their living by farming and fishing.
Their village is but one of 40 others built with the help of the nationalist government and USA.
A good start for these people who cast their lot for freedom and now begin new lives.
Sozusagen en klingendes hobby hat Herr Johannes Liese in Berlin.
Från japaniska kässelgångar och kultglockor samlade han allt till det minsta kvällsglöcket.
260 klockor från fyra delar av jorden är samlarnas stolthet.
Jag kan lämna mig, men vad upphära päls, tända, kämpen, simba, lion, kapp, the peacock and all the other residents at the zoo can't understand how they could be buddies.
Att sända en tända.
Då var jag bara enig om de så old fashioned prejudices.
Jag gav honom grejt till Geller most of the time.
Jag.
In their spacious apartment at the World Jungle Compound at Thousand Oaks, California, they indulge in roughhouse to their hearts content, just like any pair of kids their age.
A lion, even at Simba's age, can be a rugged playmate, but Tamba is a smart cookie who knows how to take care of himself.
And when things get too hectic, tambour can always take to safer, higher altitudes.
Strange playmates.
The moral?
Things always turn out for the best when you take the proverbial lion by the tail.
200 mil norr om Tokyo, den japanska staden Tokomachi, håller sitt traditionella show av skulpturer.
En verkligen utmärksammad utställning.
Besökare kommer från milen runt omkring för att se denna vinterverk av kunskap.
Kassapriser gör för kraftig konkurrens.
The winning entry portrays an Antarctic expedition, a timely subject in a perfect medium, south polar etchings in ice.
Danford University radiologists take a giant step in the ever expanding war against cancer.
Their weapon is an x-ray gun of unparalleled construction, a 6 million volt electronic accelerator.
In this demonstration a laboratory assistant plays the part of the patient as the sensitive two ton mechanism is moved like a toy by remote control.
The virtue of this new machine is that doctors can now use economically high energy x-rays that can safely attack cancerous growths in the deepest structures of the body.
Within a radiation proof chamber it can be beamed at interior tumors while the patient sits in a power driven revolving chair.
Scientists have high hopes for this new cancer gun, one of the most effective yet devised.