nr		tel
12	tg
FI		AR
ATL	URVUOL UT
COR Or ERE Sod	Lake Mälar and grew up on the	city isle in the confines of the	os
It was a thriving centre of the	Baltic trade and the church of	St. Nicholas in the heart of the	"City Between the Bridges” was	dedicated to the seafarer.
Even today traces of the mediaeval	atmosphere of Hanseatic times	may be discerened in the city's	narrow alleys around the church	and the Stortorget.
A period of prosperity set in	with the opening of the 17th	century. Between 1610 and 1650	the population rose from 8 000 to	40 000. The city was finding its	ancient narrow boundaries too	confined.
Norrmalm was cut up into a	regular network of  rectilinear	ER TOM	plan round about 1640.
The merchant houses and shipping	UN 3 EI TT	of the festive activity of the	YA
Stockholm became the centre of	the kingdom. High officials built	un to themselves mansions and	the noble estate towards the	middle of the 17th century received	its assembly place in the shape	of the House of the Nobility.
The capital of Gustavus Adolphus	attracted foreigners of ability.	Louis de Geer, "the Father of	Swedish Industry”, built for him-	EST TTT ert NS	in classic Dutch style.
Charles XII's ideals of sovereignty	found their expression in the	new royal palace, built 1697 —	1755 to drawings by Nicodemus	Tessin the younger.
7108 TS RTR	BEST ET EN Tas Ng	ert de NE NS TT I		EG Ev g
The modest dwellings of the	workers formed a strong contrast	to the mansions of the gentry.	In the rocky portions of the south	city picturesque cabins of the	| E17 Tas ET ST RO TS	as relics of proletarian charm.
In 1866 the general town plan	of Albert Lindhagen was presen-	ted: the Haussmann Parisian mo-	numental scheme in a Stockholm		version.
The rectangular lines of middle	17th century streets were re-	lieved by star-chaped junctions	and boulevards.
Counting 91000 in 1850, the	population of Stockholm had	increased by 1890 to 246 000.
Massive baroque style marked the	blocks of flats which sprang up	on the outskirts at the close of	the 19th century, particularly on	Ostermalm.
With the opening of the new	century English town-planning ideas	gained ground: detached houses	with charming gardens were	built about romantically irregular	Fr
In the older sections, howewer,	the disadvantages of excessive	ground exploitation began to be felt .
Narrow alleys and dark unhealthy	backyards were threatening to	degenerate.
Since 1930 the authorities have	been working out clearing plans	for large parts of old Stockholm.
BLOCK WITH REBUILDING	PLAN APPROVED BY THE	TOWN PLANNING - BOARD	AND SANCTIONED BY HIS	MAJESTYS GOVERNMENT		BLOCK WITH REBUILDING	PLAN ONLY APPROVED BY	THE TOWN PLANNING BOARD.
A beginning has been made with	the widening of streets and the	back yards are being cleared up	in the blocks of old buildings.
In the City Between the Bridges	ITE BETET TTT	demolishing rear buildings, histo-	rical but of no value.
Green spaces, fountains and re-	creation grounds have given the	threatened slums a smiling charm.
But the mediaeval atmosphere is	preserved in the network of streets	and the old bare facades.
In 1915 Stockholm had 392 000	inhabitants, and by 1930 the	number had grown to 502 000.
Traffic problems of modern Stock-	holm have arisen through the	construction of office blocks in	the old centre and new residential	CLS TS ST
FSC eta 0 Teg	ETT ETT ERE et dd Bio	north to south by the reconstruc-	tion of Slussen, completed in 1934.
A little later still another north-	south artery was opened: Väster-	bro and a lofty bridge was also	built to link up the garden suburbs	LR: TA
Around 1930 modern town-plan-	ning ideas were applied to Norr	Mälarstrand. New blocks being	opened to the south with its	sunshine and water-front.
Since 1930 modern town planning	principles have been adopted.	Rocky heights and pine clad	slopes have been crowned wiht	blocks of flats and outstanding	buildings. In the last decade	some 80 000 dwellings have been	Luna
UTG ETT ES TT	skirts attract families with children.	The city has built 21 schools in	40 years.
Open air life has been ensured	for the children by the creation	ofparks with games and recreation	grounds, paddling pools and sunny	ee
Open air baths must be laid out	"inland".  Vanadis Baths are	situated on an open, sunny rocky	Sa
Unspoiled areas, partly virgin land,	have been purchased by the	municipality and thrown open to	the inhabitants as nature parks	ONE		The village of Old Tyresta lies some	15 miles to the south of Stockholm
To provide for future housing the	municipality has been acquiring	ET AEA Tar	of the city. A start was made in	1899 with Enskede Estate at	Brännkyrka.
There arose about 1910 at En-	skede a well-laid out suburb with	rows of cottages and villas.
Since the world war large garden	suburbs have been created on the	city estates, chiefly to the west and	south. Here some 60 000 Stock-	holm inhabitauts are housed. The	leasehold principal is applied here.
On the cottage estates, laid out	for the working class, families	have built their homes by their	own labour.
ISEN ESO ET LEDD I	vagsH” oi insinoa 10 19792 od	NOSA
The city is building cheap dwellings	at Bromma and Brännkyrka,	designed = especially for large	Ert
New ground is being ear-marked	year by year for the city's needs. In	1938 some 12 000 dwellings were	constructed and the population	of the city was 570 000 and of	Great Stockholm 720 000.
Stockholm is growing outwards	to take in ancient farmlands and	extensive woods. The surveyor's	pe among the	lowing cattle and the startled elk.