BCG-MASS-	VACCINATION	AGAINST	TUBERCULOSIS
Each year millions of people	die of tuberculosis and count-	less others fall ill of the disease.	Systematic vaccination with	BCG can reduce ihe new cases	of tuberculosis by about four-	fifths and, in the long run, save	a great number of lives.
(Untied Nations International	Children's Emergency Fund)	INSE: ESKO	IDA NRA	Swedish Red Cross	Me	(World Health Organization).		The purpose is	tuberculin testing of all children
FSC Sent EE SET:	consists of a doctor and 2	nurses. In some countries	Danish, Norwegian, and	Swedish instructors are	Ca
As: far as possible a room	with at least 2 doors should	JEN
The work — in particular, the	reading of the reactions —	requires ample light.
FCC CBE	for each individual.
Mavat Skola		= Palkorice	= MISTER		EEE ad ER	= MARIE
USS En är		before the team arrives. It is		necessary to have cards for		all members of the group		which is to be examined —		including those who do not	appear.
> Hlavas Skole	Palkovice	"MISTER
UTI CERT:	tuberculin — the toxin of the	tubercle bacillus. It must be	kept in a cool place and will	then keep for 2-4 weeks. For	LE USER	solution is used: 1 TU (inter-	national tuberculin unit) per	ES
The syringes must be sterilized	before the day's work starts,	if possible the previous	evening.
ERE: NS gets stor	cooled, they are assembled	and made ready.
The syringes for weak tuber-	culin, the syringes for strong	tuberculin, and the syringes	for vaccine must be easy to	distinguish.
The needle must be passed		quickly through the flame —		not made red-hot. Then press		out a drop of the contenis io	cool it off.
Mantoux test. For this injection	[ER ESS LEN ST	should not be washed.
The injection is given in the	middle third of the dorsal	side of the left forearm.
NS SS UV EST vu	Ipnoitomoetni) UT I ot pribrog	Klinta ELng
IX LETS RATE US	patch test is used. The strength	of the ointment is three times	the intemational standard of	Old Tuberculin. Kept in a cool	place it will keep for one year.
WERE TONEE Sa	cleaned with alcohol, ether	or ihe like.
The plaster must be kept on	for 24 hours and then	FOTEN
All tests are read after	three days.
The Mantoux-reaction is con-	sidered positive when the dia-	meter of the infiltration is 6	millimeters or more. Redness	alone does not constitute a	positive reaction.
The Moro reaction is conside-	red positive when there are	at least 3 typical papules.
No reaction to Mantoux test.	No infiltration. Measuring is	therefore unnecessary.
No reaction to Moro-patch	SA
A doubiful reaction to tuber-		culin must be considered no		reaction, but should be mea-		sured and recorded just the	same.
2 VW 3 srhvo	musug?	[EA UT! oa omm	V = ue	bijuxso SS RR		 		 		 		län muse.
If there is no reaction to the	first Mantoux test, or if the	reaction is doubtiful, the test	is repeated with a tuberculin-	dose ten times as strong.
ESS ES	berculin may cause disagree-	able consequences (Koch	phenomena), and should	therefore be avoided.
stil ETEN ETT NO	BoRS g
The BCG culture was deve-	IST:	AN ReR
The BCG laboratory at the	State Serum Institute in Copen-	hagen. Only persons who	have been X-rayed and found	free of contagious tuberculosis	CSC INS
For the vaccine, a 14-day old	[ACES RESTE	IEC
72: C CSE.	always be used.
Dp fi tqox od bluode onioopv odT	.osoot ton tevm tud soplq bloa	apdt 1etol bee od tom tara tl	sipb odt 10tto 2ypb nestiol	sd bluode slugmn odT .beqmnie	noitupasrq yrsvs dtiw belband	nedxpde od bluodea tl .ytilirete 101	.oey aroled
The injection is made as super-	ficially as possible and very	slowly. Too deep an injection	may cause complications.	PERS
When the work is finished, all	vaccine left in open ampules	should be destroyed.
Normal appearance of the	vaccination after four weeks.
SLR	vaccine is checked by a new	tuberculin-test about two	BLT EIS Ed TAR Stort	The same test and the same	[RE EG	vaccination.
Not a single case of tuberculous	disease has been reported as	a consequence of BCG
Proper information and perso-	nal discussion can persuade	parents who are unwilling to	[BERO NE OR	Meet
One of the team members	should be responsible for	order and quiet. Avoid scar-	ble MSC	allow fright to spread. Posters	and notices in the waiting	FEN
The Health Department of the	Govemment is responsible for	the BCG campaign in this	couniry. Remember that the	effect of the BCG vaccination	is limited (about 80 percent	protection), and that BCG is		only part of the fight against	tuberculosis.