Airfields communications and enemy troops were straffed and blasted.
Every bridge over the Seine between Paris and the coast was wrecked.
This was air power on a scale to dwarf even the grandeur of Nazi dreams.
And all the time the sea and beaches were alive with the activity of Anglo-American invasions.
Wider and wider grew the scene.
The beachhead grew in depth and width.
From the beaches spearheads struck out and pressed inland.
Through the villages towards Caen, Essini and Carantan.
And Montbourg and Saint-Mère-Église in the north towards Cherbourg.
Fighting over open country and in the streets.
Destroying the German conquerors of France.
Capturing their supply dumps and taking prisoners.
Airborne units fought an engagement here close to the gliders in which they had landed.
Här ut av aktion kommer de germanska soldaterna i förlängning.
De första rika frukterna av vikten för USA.
And from each village recaptured from Hitler come the people of France.
Bordet mineras snart efter att invasionen började.
Supremekommander Eisenhower tittade på progressen med Admiral Ramsey.
And that other familiar figure whose name has spelled victory more than once.
Efter fyra år stannar kommandoren av de allierade fieldforcerna på franska gränsen.
General Montgomery har sagt att han inte såg någon Atlantiska vägg, men han såg ett vackert effektivt system av stål- och stål- och stålplatser.
Skälet och kärleken av våra krigsmän överkom dem, vackra som de var.
And now the reinforcements of men and armor came into the towns.
The Normandy names have become famous in a week because of their battles on the road to Berlin.
Från alla sektorer kom prästnaderna i hundratals, grävande i tusentals.
De kom ut till skogen, förbjudna för Britannien.
Allt redan över det här stödet var det inget att evakuera.
Nusset har blivit övrig.
Det fick flaskor i det fjälls av Norrbotten.
While they were waiting for the patients with whom they flew back to Britain.
Over in Britain also the prisoners are arriving.
The men who expected to march in triumph through the streets of our London.
Now they come instead in captivity.
Churchill told them four years ago that we would fight on the beaches.
It turns out to be their beaches.
Light and medium bombers are now over the Dieppe target.
Those sticks of white are tracer machine gun bullets from German fighters at the camera plane.
Over the land between the Seine and the Somme, the air is thick with battling warplanes.
Those cups of cotton wool that drift so lazily in the picture are bursts of cannon fire.
But the planes go on.
It's too high to see clearly the action on the ground.
But down below the tanks have penetrated the town.
Commanders have blown up ammunition dumps.
Infantry are driving a knife into the giant body of Hitler's machine turned army.
The RAF is bombing his strong points.
Den här scenen av lilla båtar minns du av Dunkirk.
De mörka dagarna i vår historia, när hela världen trodde att den brittiska kriget stannade överallt.
Hela världen, utom oss själva.
Det här är början på att få oss själva tillbaka.
Männen som har räddat Dieppe kommer tillbaka på bordet.
Inte som när de kom till Dunkirk, utsatt, utsatt och förlorad.
Den här gången kommer de tillbaka som en boxare som vänder sitt arm efter en vänsterpågång, redo att stänga igen.
Planerna landar nu i många olika områden.
En del av den här krävande kraften var amerikansk.
Fusillaget är märkt med en stjärna som blir mer och mer förmiddag över Europa.
These are the Rangers, the first Americans to see fighting on French soil since 1918, but not by any means the last.
It's difficult for us to assess the value of this raid on Dieppe.
Guns were silenced, prisoners were taken, radio location station destroyed, many Germans killed and scores of Nazi planes shot to bits.
But our losses too were heavy.
How should we feel as we look at the return of these tough men who've dared so much?
Hur kan vi berätta om att våra förhållanden uttryckte förlossningarna?
Kanske materiellt var förhållandet inte så stort.
Men information om krig är en av de vinnande faktorerna.
Träffar som möts i Dieppe kan bli tacklade nästa gång utan tro.
Styrka och svårighet av de germanska krigsförsäkringarna kommer att bli kända.
Och varje battaljon som en dag kommer att landa på kontinenten kommer att få tillgång till den erfarenhet som de fått av den här vanguarden av heroer.
Förstår du, Dunkirk?
Förstår du hur de trodde att vi hade blivit tillbaka?
Vi kom upp, och vi grinnade, och vi är fortfarande krigande, är vi inte?
Kanalskärlet är fortfarande mörkt med Royal Air Force-flöden.
Se på det här.
En av våra krigare skjuts ner av DF.
Watch the parachute that comes down to the sea with its pilot.
A sergeant pilot being picked up out of the drink in the nick of time.
It happens every week.
It's Britain and Dunkirk all over again.
Shot down, nearly drowned.
But if you think he's finished, you're as crazy as Hitler.