Making nets to carry		I ISTSTEN STAN
CTS		£ 26 nwoml yånommoa		en
Glass floats to support		floating nets.
FRIES ERIKSEN		BEEN
BUENA SN a	detonators to Electrical		Contact Mines - A task	fraught with extreme	danger.
ETTER na SEN	EL LA STEN		into them while they are	submerged. Bubble of air	will indicate a leak.
ERNER		On board ready for the		catch.
Getting ground chain		ready for placing on	[EN
Fully loaded drifters		[IS a NT		SAST TE
A belated "passenger.”		AES
Mine sweepers setting	ICEA ERT DTS	a	Nation owes a vast debt	of gratitude.
They are about to depart, a few	Iles T IAN EN	to assist the Monitors,		accompanied by Destroyers and	Motor Launches (known as	Movies,” on account of	[rt
The Forecastle, Conning Tower,	Wheelhouse and Superstructure		destroyed in the röce
Splicing a rope.	A nap - "all out.”		SNR	innocence.		LäcnOa
The Ship's Company.	H.M.S. "Broke” about to go		AGES		TSE ENS I	FR EN	SRS
Stokers and seamen		FSE erssral BTR		a RNNTNS EN
"Brip” of H.M.S. "Broke,”		who was in action at the		Battle of Jutland, and the	[NG Raid in April.	+
A Bell made from the	Lip of a Torpedo tube,		[el STREET	Destroyer G. 42” sunk	ELEKTRA
Scenes on H.M.S. Swift”	(known as "The Boy	Scout,” on accouut of her	class and size.)
How it all appears to the |		man in the "Crow's Nest.”
Looking after the		BAGAR
The youngest member of		the Crew.
EN		The Crew of H.M.S.	VS	"Merry and Bright.”
Officers with the ship's	Bull Terrier	"William the Hun.”
Dias kn AA	Re		KT LRA VENT TENENE:	AIG TS-d5 150 = — bisA lannsdd	AY CSE n ETS RS
ANNE		 		ju MÅNG NN
IAEA		NATT
KR	BEU
AR
Brittiske kryssaren Vindictive	[OTO LEN CURT CO TITT	varvid försök gjordes att spärra	hamnarna i Ostende och Zeebrägge.		LETEN GETT CST TETTE ET CE	framgång, men vid spärrandet av	[ETC UNGT GES Ant TO		[UTI
Havet ligger lugnt, och vädret	är gott för mindre fartyg.	Motorbåtar göra förberedelser	för avfärden.
Modärna moterjagare, som	göra en fart på 45 knop. De äro	utrustade med rökapparater för		att kunna dölja sig.
Dunkirken kan skönjas i diset	på Flanderns avlägsna kust.
En avdelning engelska destroyers	med order att hålla utkik.
En rökskärm för att dölja	framryckningen.
PITT LEOR STR OTINET	EN ORP EI CPC	Ta
Dessa små krigsfartyg	”i fickformat” äro mästare i	att åstadkomma rök.
Det ser ut,som om en tät dim-	ma dreve in från havet.
Ett lasarettsfartyg håller	sig redo.
Monitorer ligga i eldberedskap	långt till sjöss i väntan på order.
Belgiska soldater.
31300 Or	KTV ET
OENETECRSCPE EE	EI TERO CE CARE EU ICEA	OEI
URLS GODE ORO	KDETÄGE TELE TES RTL OED