192	4U
THE	RE-CAPTURE OF KUT.		Unloading Field Artillery.
LONDON'S GIFT	TO SOUTH AFRICA.		 		 		Lieut..Gen. "Smuts  receives an	YES TATE ST	ol South Africa		[RE LOL
ES Ho 640.		 		"FLY SAFELY!”		Mrs. Schreiner christening	the "South Africa.”
Lord Desborough presents a	souvenir casket to General		Krang		ES No. 640.
SUBMARINE  AGROUND.		 		 		A similar fate unfortunately	[TSE RY SSR Ta
Fo	USING	een jam fer Tommy ät AE	LOTTE a betory.	Topping and Tailing Gooseberriss.
e		ST EE EST Ti GG		RniqgsrW bas apnillsdet	KRIn er vg		EU PT
S		lg	SEA AND LAND.		The DUKE OF CONNAUGHT	presents Medals on Plymouth	CN	ET No. 692,
NV		ke:		Lä		CÅ T		OD
S GVA
JU
GENERAL FIELDING NEW	GENERAL OFFICER	COMMANDING LONDON	DISTRICT, INSPECTS		VOLUNTEERS IN HYDE	PARK.		Spirited march past of	Citizen soldiers enrolled	for Home Defence.
600 ENGLISH	AUTOMOBILES CON-	SIGNED TO FRANCE.		Paul Cambon, Veteran	French Ambassador,	inspects Ambulance Unit	presented by British Com-	mittee of Frenct Red Cross.
He is delighted with his		latest proof of how Britain	helps her Allies,
2 Vietorious and Satisle	peac
ALLIES ANSWER	-GERMANYS NEW	CHANCELLOR PRINCE MAX	OF BADEN'S REICHSTAG		3 SPEECH.		Trafalgar Square s packed with		eagér purchasers of War Bonds		to enable Britain to participate	in a Victorious and Satisfactory		peace.
TRIBUTE TO SCOTTISH	OVERSEAS HEROES.		Sir R. Borden, among distinguished	congregation at St. Columba's (London)	Commemeration Service.		355-1
Universal Cuyront Events	KC SE Ra ET EE Sn [SL		(SKA MONT:	WILL RAISE MORE SHEEP	And We'll Know Where to Find ”Em—The	Wool to France in Shirts and Pants —		So that Sammies, Warm Clad, Will	Make Wilhelm Dance!		[ER
Universal Current Events	ARTEN		MEDICAL NEEDS OF	OUR BOYS WILL BE	PROPERLY CARED FOR		3,000 in One Unit Are About Ready To	Join Pershing and His Fighters.		Fort Ethan Allen, Vt.
President Poincare, General	Pershing, Marshall Joffre, War	Minister Briand and Other	Notables Inspect Our Fighters.		[ES
Universal Current Events		SANTA FE TRAINS IN	LU DKONK CORE		One Life Lost as Switch Engines Collide on	Curve in Railroad Yards.		 		 		LET VT
Ed Cd		KRIS R TNT		wind-swept barren Grounds.	The Musk Ox		STIAN
HUSSAIN		PASSET REST		captive Musk Ox in the	world.		 		PEST SAN
REKESNSSRVE EE	foot of wool and flowing		hair to resist ghastly cold	and frightful winds.		 		TA SON
MLS EL		UUNE TEST TRES		 		EVER
Sullen and dangerous.		 		FAT
Autos Have Not Entirely Taken	the Place of the Old Army Mule.		EEE
EVE S		ERE ET
South  Carolina's Famous	"Chain Gang” Are Working	for Uncle Sam Now.		INVERSAL. CURRENT EvENIS.
[LUC EET OST TT S ST	GIRL MUNITIONS MAKERS	[EARL TA	HE VISITS THEM AT WORK	In Great Plant, Where France's Women Make		KET EET TI 0 Tatl TTT	[SST TN		 		 		Somewhere-in-France,
Really American, He Bows	Gallantly to France's Loyal	Women Workers.		[ES