Hur lång är den?
Jag vet inte.
I'm starting off from here, flying to Newfoundland.
I'll refuel there then go on to London.
Well I hope to do the ocean cropping in something like 15-16 hours.
That's from New York all the way to London and it should be the fastest time.
This is my fourth ocean cropping so I'm becoming more or less used to it.
People have suggested it's rather late in the year but I think I'll be flying so high that I should be out of any ice or bad weather.
Anyway...
I'll know in about a week's time whether that is so or not.
I'm starting off from New York, flying to Newfoundland.
I'll retool there quickly then go on to London.
I don't quite know how long it will take from New York to London but I suppose something in the nature of 16 hours which would be the fastest time as yet.
This is my fourth ocean cropping so I'm getting quite used to it.
I've got a very fast aeroplane.
It's got a top speed of over 270 miles an hour.
And I've great confidence in it.
When I get to London, I'll probably stay there too.
Then I'll go right on to the Cape to try and beat the existing time to visit.
Which was put up in the South African Air Race last month.
I expect to be at the Cape something like 40 hours after...
I'm starting off from New York, flying to Newfoundland, refueling there quickly.
Jag väntar mig att åka till London om 15 timmar.
Jag har en väldigt snabb helikopter som inte flyttar mer än 250 km i en timme.
Det är en hel del speed.
Efter att jag kommer till London
Så, hej då!