Tack.
I.
He was left with provisions for only five months in one of the loneliest spaces in the world.
Nine thousand feet up on the ice cap without any hope of getting into touch with other human beings until the spring.
Den långa vinteren har gått, och i mars har en räddningsparty gått ut för att åka de 150 milen till den här herrn i Arktis.
Men de blev drivna tillbaka av räddande blizzar, och nu är våra dramatiska bilder, tagna av lieutenant Martin Lindsay, och presenterade i sammanhang med The Times, kommer att ta upp threaden i historien.
Planeet, som var med i utredningen, var snabbt samlat.
Det är det vi provisjons och sett av från det bäst kämpe i en attempt to reach the marooned Explorer.
Det är det som ska kämma igen.
Fast landing and the planer räck.
En SOS var lasten.
Kapten Arnberg, en svensk skärmen, flöde kross i Atlantik by way of Iceland och röjde på det bäst.
Här hittills med hans mekanik en vals operatör med hjälp av nätet Eskimos.
Vi andra karriärer på planen var alltid det kärre skis.
Stacks of seal meat and other provisions were put aboard.
It is impossible for us here in civilization to realize the appalling conditions under which this flight was made.
Weather changes without the least warning.
Clouds dropping from 2,000 feet to less than 100, making visibility almost nil.
Grave danger is run whilst flying over the ice field in a single-engined machine.
A forced landing means almost certain death from exposure.
But the airmen made light of their task and so set off without delay into the arctic wastes.
Fresh supplies of oil were taken by sled to the landing ground.
And members of the expedition fed the burning oil into baths to keep up a constant smoke signal for the return of the searchers.
As time wore on, their anxiety grew.
But at last a speck was seen in the sky, and Captain Arnberg made a perfect landing.
He had sighted the rescue party, led by Watkins, and with them was Courtauld, fit and well, 120 miles from the base.
And there he is with his rescuers.
What a wonderful moment for the young explorer, after five months alone in the Greenland snows, to be with companions again.
To see the sun after weeks of darkness in a snowed up tent.
And his first pipe for tobacco ran out many weeks before.
There's Chapman with him, one of the rescue party.
There's Watkins, the leader.
And the other member was Reinhold.
What a difference a real wash makes.
Now I bet that cigar tasted good.
And there he is, shaven of his locks and beard, but a lot thinner.
Then, goodbye to Captain Orenberg.
And thanks, old man, for your help.