Sweden and Swedish	EUS	IR		RES	pss NE RET eg
Aktiebolaget Bofors	AR Ltd). Founded in	1646, makers of guns,	munitions, armourplate, etc.	sa ATG		NURKA AR	ARE ER
rn		The Bofors Ordnance and		Steel works make guns as a	TN		LKJOKE ES	PETER
LO TSRTA ORTER EEG		ER NES
Turning and boring.		EE
The guns are hardened in	OR		RTR era
2008 adt 10 gnivoord		LE
Mounting of the guns.
Manufacturing of shells.		ik
Manufacturing and		OTTO		FREGE KIA
FO TT	Bofors, Sweden (The Nobel	Gunpowder Works, Ltd).	Makers of gun powder.		FÅ SSR	HEAD A FIK.
Manufacture of nitro-	glycerine		Rae
Mixing of nitroglycerine		and guncotton.		FRE	FEAR
The powderparts are		moulded into tubes.		RÄDDA	PRESS
Swedish soldiers in the	barracks and on the	EDITS ILO		Kokt	Eli
The Commanding-general.	|		FIRE
A Swedish farm during the		LERA		FOKRIAA
The girls on the farm can		both bind the grain by hand		and drive harvesting	En		YET
RASET EIEO Gel CER TTT		ELER		3 UTA