AVE	IEEE		KUK L EE	[LITER TK Ke TT		Cinemagraph Committee.		KOLET
ST	EST da O otal
FINARE SS
SARAH BERNHARD	IN MEMORIAM.		De sista bilderna av den nu av-		lidna stora konstnärinnan under		FSS 3 SR
Sarah Bernhard som gäst vid	SYS eN IS
PARIS — France ...	Mme CURIE qui.en colla-	boration FR	IS EI SN COURIE,	découvritele "radium" ,	vient detre elue Membre		FS WEE CEST
NESS Ae!	-Blloa ma.iup IIAUDI AM	Mala n ol	3IAUI oral attongan ol		BP Tai) MIR NHL)	adma 1 suls antäb tnoiv		FRE SME JET LV ET	FYYYYYT)I
o	(J		BE KYLA IG	BJ ENT a [ED] MI	iyem noe vavs noifserod	JIAUI otvraid Sffargan EJ	.'muibst ol fiivuosåb	sidmalM suls ovtåb trnaiv		aniosbaM ETIK GAR El)
MADAME CURIE	har nyligen firat 25-årsjubiléet av	sin och sin mans upptäckt av	grundämnet radium.
ERE	FUSAEIAESS	4		 		Barthou.
Sd		FROSSA		 		  		Lord Curzon.
SKANDIA a		 		REVY.		 		SS		Lloyd George.
EE TEE		 		 		PEREN		-NOHNOCNOJI NÅSA	MEldekeg		 		BUTT EESK ERE far PT I	natnsbiesrgilsenod	LC
VIDERE	ESS		South Afriex's soldier-statesman	reviews Boys Brigade.		352-2
BRITISH AMBASSADOR	ARRIVES IN AMERICA		NEW YORK — Sir Auckland	Geddes and Lady Geddes arrive	aboard the Kaiserin Auguste Victoria		KINOGRAMS
belngtesd	Elnsng	REN		2MASIDOVIA
OUT Sent	Geddes		LINAN
EET VA eg		ISEN
UTEN EEG	De		KINOGRAMS
INTERNATIONAL		TISKT Fann		   		First picture of Archbishop Bonzano,		papal delegate to America, and the		Supreme Board of Directors of the	ERA GNNT		Washington, D. C.
INTERNATIONAL		Albert Thomas, noted Frenchman,	who has been named first chairman		of the League of Nations Labor		RNE
Ra		Va	ES	vor wo. 2 ”Q Ö issveno	(YC		LJ	REAR ADMIRAL a NS MI		A recent picture of the famous		discoverer of the North Pole.		PEST
INTERNATIONAL		The noted explorer (in civilian		clothes) looking over an airplane		intended for an arctic flight.
INTERNATIONAL		The man who carried the American		flag to the top of the world.
[AJOUTE		är general Obregon, som åter	har hyllats av amerikanarna	MPR RANE
1289ilttymsgagoviensibiev 190	.blaitnså alettidaensinit
Locatelli, Italian airman	who failed in flight,	and his aides are	NESS SSE		KINOGRAMS
SIR OLIVER LODGE		British scientist arrives in	New York on Lapland	to lecture on-immortality		LOI
THE TWENTY-NINTH	la D Va	UNITED STATES >		KINOGRAMS
NASA	Monaco arrives	on ”La France”		KINOGRAMS
Le Général Nivelle arrive		å la gare.
CHICAGO, ILL.	Need transports? Here's one	can safely cross the Atlantic!	Santa Maria, replica of Colum-		bus" flagship, is ready to dis-	cover new routes to Freedom.		ESS SVS
FNS TVR		 		The original anchor used by	Christopher.
FN TNA		The Nina and the Pinta - the	other two ships that made up	the party back in 1492.
Po äere	FALSE NINIA:	ENG ä	| Sad		5		ROR ö		APRIL 2nd, 1912. fö	KATT ODDA EE