QUEEN MARIE HELPS	HER: HUNGRY PEOPLE		Her Royal Highness of Roumania goes	to mountain town of TELEGA to aid	[SNS SS EN ASS		KINOGRAMS
EN KUNGLIG JOCKEY.		 		Prinsen av Wales som delta-	gare i en fashionabel steeple	NESS
Ers		 		Prinsen ledde i början . .
rr		 		 		...men red omkull vid andra	hindret ...
FRESTAS		« .. vilket inte hindrade honom	att komma in till målet som	FR
EN MINNESTAVLA ÖVER	DE I KRIGET FALLNA		har av prinsen av Wales av-		täckts i engelska parlamentet.
MAKING AN INDIAN	OUT OF A PRINCE		BANFF — The Canadian redskins	greet Prince of Wales in best native	manner and give him feather bonnet		KINOGRAMS
PRINCE VISITS LUMBER	LAND gf CANADIAN WEST		VANCOUVER. B. C.— His Royal High-	ness of Wales sees one of the biggest		saw mills of the country in operation		[INST
THE PRINCE OF WALES	IN SUNNY CALIFORNIA		SAN DIEGO — His Royal Highness	welcomed as he lands by Governor	Stephens, Mayor Wilde and officials		LINS
PRINCE &£ WALES	VISITS THE CAPITAL		WASHINGTON — Britian's heir	arrives to be greeted by Embassy	and Gen. Pershing at Union Station		LINS TN		| "SSE ene
nes	from the station		KINOGRAMS
cAt the Perry Belmont	NETA	lys ESC		[SIS
Kyss	EINE		KINOGRAMS
Leaving after	ERS		KINOGRAMS
FYFAN
En	Cres		BULEDleI
IVT	Ene Ol		KINOGRAMS