Uri Castle, picture plus card beauty spot in the hills of North Wales, became the focus of world sportsmen when Bruce Woodcock set up his training camp there to prepare for his World Heavyweight Championship fight with Lee Savold.
Nu har 18 månader av förväntan, förvaltning och förväntan gått igen, och Jack Solomons, som är bakom allt, räddar sig med pressböjorna.
Men bara lite.
Med en man i Wales och en annan i Skarborough, Jack kanske måste röra från en kamp till en annan vid en viss anledning.
Det är kriget av åldern för brittiska fans.
Om Bruce vinner blir han världens första brittiska heavyweight-kämpare sen Cornishman Bob Fitzsimmons.
En last minute hitch, en accident, kan rädda över natt månader av kostnadsförberedande.
Men den här gången ser det aldrig ut som om alla signaler är klara.
But if Jack Solomons was still worrying, Bruce didn't seem to have a care in the world as he dallied over tea with his hosts Leslie and Mrs. Saltz.
Bruce owes a lot to Mr. Saltz, who did everything possible to give him the finest training camp in Britain.
And Bruce has taken every advantage.
Those who know him say he's never been so ready for a fight.
More than any other, he's out to win this fight, if only to convince the nigglers who didn't like his win on a foul 18 months ago.
And now, the White City.
A record, excited crowd, searing floodlights and all that makes a Solomons night of nights.
It's a fantastic scene in the vast arena.
Ringside seats within handshake reach of the fighters and far in the distance the real fans perched high and looking hopefully at a shining pocket handkerchief with two fleas hopping on it.
Fight reporter Desmond Hackett punches out pre-fight impressions and is all set to report the big fight for you.
Bretons highly successful film producer Sir Michael Bolton chats with a smiling Jack Solomons.
No wonder he's smiling.
There is Sir Arthur Elvin and GRA boss Frank Gentle.
The preliminaries are over and excitement soars as the moment draws near for the fighters to enter the ring.
The spotlight picks up the stars and stripes as Lee Savold of America and his escort march into the arena.
Och nu en rådgivning för Britanniens Bruce Woodcock som visade oss hans väg genom staden.
Freddy Mils är där och brusar bruskligt mellan väggarna.
Det är ingen av de gamla kvaliteterna den här tiden.
Patsy Higgins.
En tjej i spetmöten.
And there they are, ready to decide who is the world's best.
It's seconds out and time.
Who's going to make the first move?
It may be the first slip.
Many experts thought it would be Savold, out to catch Bruce with a confidence wrecker before he got set.
Those who tipped a Woodcock win banked on his hair-trigger right.
But all agreed they'd be throwing punches from the word go.
New York fight experts Nat Fleischer and Lou Burstyn wonder if the title is going to cross the Atlantic.
Det var rätt, tre round rapid.
Det var inga powderpuff-puncher, de skickade nog Savold.
Ända av round one, och Woodcock går till en flygande start.
Round two, med vänstern jabbade hela tiden på Savold, och rätt kom över när det skulle göra mest skador.
Bruce tog round two hansomt.
Tack!
Här uppe i staden, kapten Ayers och medlemmar av hans Storbritanniska staff, håll kvar.
Rund tre.
Woodcock still throwing that shattering right, but he's not cashing in.
He's not following up.
He gives Savold a breather.
That one good breath is all that tough campaigner needs to get out of trouble.
Det var en överraskande paket, men inget stoppade Savold från att komma in och fråga om det.
Vid slutet av tredje rounden såg de sig oroliga i Savolds klocka.
Lees är långt bakom.
De första tre rounderna är brusar.
Och nu den dramatiska fjärde rounden.
There it is!
The punch that cut Bruce's eye.
It was the payoff punch, though we didn't know it at first till we saw blood streaming down his face and blinding him.
For the first time, Woodcock became a real fighting fury.
For him it was a quick KO win or the end.
Savold to knew that this was his chance and moved in savagely for the kill.
There's too much at stake for sentiment.
Så är det bra.
Dramatisk, unexpected change.
Till Ringsiders var det tydligt att Bruce var för hård att kämpa på.
Ta en titt på det där ögonen.
Det borde skada de som skrattade och trodde att Woodcock hade avslutat när Tom Hurst kallade det för en dag för att rädda Bruce från en mörk målning.
Det är ett och ett nu.
Låt oss hoppas att Bruce öppnar snabbt och bra.
För att ge honom en chans för beslutaren.
Som för Lee har han gjort många vänner här.
I dag är det hans dag.
I dag är han Lee Savold.
Hjärnvägskampion i världen.