My dear audience, you will easily understand if I begin my short address to you in my very imperfect English by addressing my warm thanks to the Mexican people and to the man who leads them with such merit and courage, President Cardenas.
When monstrous and absurd accusations were hurled at my and my family, when my wife and myself were under the lock and key of the Norwegian government,
Without being able to defend ourselves, the Mexican government opened the doors of this magnificent country and said to us, here you can freely defend your rights and your honor.
Naturally, it is not a sympathy for myself, my ideas, which has motivated President Cardenas, but a fidelity to his own ideas.
All the more meritorious then is this act of democratic hospitality the rarer his days.
Stalins trial against me is built upon false confessions extorted by modern inquisitorial methods in the interest of the ruling elite.
There are no crime in history more terrible in intention and execution than the Moscow trials of Zinoviev Kamenev and of Pyatakov Radek.
De här utsträckningarna utvecklades inte av kommunism, inte av socialism, utan från stalinism, det är från den ansvariga despotismen av byråkratin över människor.
Vad är nu min principiella jobb?
Att uppmärksamma verkligheten, att visa och demonstrera att de verkliga kriminella skyddar sig under klockan av förvånare.
Vad blir nästa steg i den här riktningen?
the creation of an American and European and subsequently also an international commission of inquiry composed of people who incontestably enjoy authority, public consideration and confidence.
I ändå tänkt att presentera sig till kommission om mig färg.
Tausend av personalen öppna lättare inriktade.
Välkomnens av mig så att den här aktionen är så att det blir bra att en ny gap.
Jag har nog inte att ha.
Dödsens av vittneses.
Vart är bra att ses invalidera färgs en dag kvinnens vilket vill se till att det måste vara främst.
Det var.
of the commission of inquiry must terminate in a great counter-trial.
A counter-trial is necessary to cleanse the atmosphere of the germs of deceit, calumny, falsification and frame-ups whose source is Stalin's police, the GPU, which has fallen to the level of the Nazi Gestapo.
Inquiry will confirm that there is not a stain on my honor, both personal and political.
Profoundly convinced that the right is on my side, I wholeheartedly salute the citizens of the new world.
Hold it, hold it, well.
Du har verkligen fått något nu.
Varsågod!
Tack för mig.