Never before have such solemn and dramatic pictures appeared on the screen.
The ceremony that has remained unchanged for a thousand years.
The procession of Her Majesty the Queen moves up the nave to be greeted after the anthem by the scholars of Westminster School with the Vivat Regina.
Stjärn!
Are you willing to do the same?
The king prepares to take the oath.
The archbishop asks him if he will solemnly promise to govern the people of Great Britain, Ireland, Canada, Australia, New Zealand and the Union of South Africa.
of your possessions and the other territories to any of them belonging or pertaining and of your empire of India according to their respective laws and customs.
I solemnly promise so to do.
Will you to your power cause law and justice in mercy to be executed in all your judgments?
I will.
The king signs the oath.
Men det var dess roll på det mest säkra part of the service.
Det är en anting med Holi och.
Den yttersta begata och bringa kanapé av kraft av Gould.
Det är ju alldeles magister.
Det blir kraftfärdiga.
The anointing.
Be thy breast anointed with holy oil.
I dag är han ojkigt med farliga.
Efter det anmärkning, det säkert en säkerhetssäkerhet av det karlnäschen med.
Super tunika och överdress av kraft av Gull is put upon the king.
Gödl är färdiga röntgen.
Låt Chamberlain tacks i sin hälsodåldern spärs av natt.
Från det åter.
The archbishop of Canterbury brings the jeweled sword of state.
Thus is symbolized the merging in the king of the temporal and divine power.
The armill, or collar, is placed on the king by the dean of Westminster.
The dean invests him with a mantle of cloth of gold, richly adorned with the eagle of empire, yet square, like the cope of a bishop.
His majesty takes the orb with the cross.
This imperial robe and all
And the Lord your God can show you with knowledge and wisdom, with majesty and with power from above.
The sovereign receives the ring, a great sapphire slashed with a cross of rubies.
The Lord of the Manor of Worksop presents the glove.
His Majesty takes the scepter with the cross.
And the scepter with the dove.
Där faras det kranning.
Den av Westminster bringsen det var det kan fästas kran från det åter.
Det är inte bäst att kanta berättelser.
Reset var förlämnade.
Det var sitt om det var bra.
Det kringes krav.
Det blev det kring det som.
His Majesty prepares to receive the homage to the throne.
In turn the Archbishop of Canterbury, the Duke of Gloucester, the Duke of Kent
En del marschall duk av Norfolk var ni över får hem touch the golden crown and kiss his right cheek.
His Majestys lifted in to the throne and the homage begin.
Her Majesty the Queen moves forward to be crowned.
Her Majesty receives the two scepters and makes her way to the throne to pay homage to the king.
Her train is borne by the mistress of the robes and six ladies in waiting.
As they reach the throne, they bow in homage to the king.
Thus crowned and consecrated, their majesties move through the nave and choir to leave the abbey.
The coronation is over.