Only once or twice in the life of each one of us comes such a day as this.
When we realize that we are watching history in the making.
When we know that generations of Englishmen to come will look back on this day.
For May the 12th, 1937 will be one of the dates in English history that the school children will learn maybe a thousand years from now.
Every moment the thrill of excitement increases.
Early in the day the vast crowd cheers their Royal Highnesses Princess Elizabeth and Margaret Rose.
And then their Royal Highnesses the Duchess of Gloucester and the Duchess of Kent.
Men det är det expektant mörma av vad man sköter i det här landet.
Men det är det här landet.
Det är det här landet.
Around the Victoria Memorial and down the Mall goes the roar of cheering, spreading like a slow fire.
And most brilliant in the glittering array is the gilded coach, surely the most beautiful vehicle in all the world.
A free translation into carved and gilded imagery of all the pomp and tradition of British royalty.
Från Admiralty archen och nedanför den stora njuren av Nilsson så går i stället glasskålarna som bär medlemmarna av Royal Family
Queen Marys procession.
And the royal cavalcade led by the army, navy and air force contingent.
The kings bodyguard of the yearmen of the guard.
The kings escort from the Indian army.
And finally the stake coach drawn by the eight Windsor Grey.
As it comes into Parliament Square, the procession enters the most historic part of the royal route to the Abbey, past Big Ben, past Westminster Hall and the Houses of Parliament, to the ancient Church of Westminster, which was first built in the days of Edward the Confessor, whose crown will before another hour has passed rest on the head of King George VI.
och kanske är det tillräckligt att i det här momentet, när statens coach drar upp på staden, att vi ska minnas andra koronationer som har gått.
Nu återigen kommer en kvinna till tronen, som byggs av karaktär och uppfattning för att hålla på med en stor tradition.
King George VI kommer in på Westminster staden för sin krona, i den magnifika formen av sin storfars.
På honom är kronan säker.
Långt kan den stanna där.
Med de mest solma och säkra bilderna som någonsin har tagits av en nyhetsrelaj,
Vi show you inside the Abbey the supreme moment when King George is crowned.
His Majesty is seated in the coronation chair of St.
Edward the Confessor.
The Dean of Westminster has brought St.
Edwards crown from the altar.
The Archbishop of Canterbury takes it.
He elevates it with solemnity, lowers it to rest upon the royal brow.
The King is crowned.
Det fjärde fjärde karinett han på dem om att krävning där Sovereign med det kraj.
God save the king.
Trumpets ringar.
Fanfare brings the news to a waiting world that another British king has ascended the throne in the abbey that for a thousand years has preserved the pomp of Royal Britain.
And outside an empire stands still to welcome its king and queen.
After the supreme moment of the crowning, and after the peers have paid homage to the new sovereign and the splendor of the abbey, comes the still greater homage of a nation and an empire to its king and queen.
Before leaving the abbey, his majesty has taken off the St.
Edwards crown and is wearing the imperial state crown and its priceless regalia.
The queen wears her new crown of platinum and diamonds.
Throughout the return drive, the king will carry the scepter with the cross in one hand, the orb with the cross in the other.
Däremot, med alla de utgående och visuella siffrorna av kvalitet runt omkring hans brittiska majestät, kring George VI och hans kvinna, lämnar byn, som rydde ljuset efter ljus genom ljuset över London.
This morning there were seven processions making their separate ways to the abbey.
Now they have joined into one amazing cavalcade.
So long that while the state coach moves along the embankment, the head of the procession is already at marble arch, more than two and a half miles ahead.
Among its glittering uniforms and waving plumes, not the smallest corner, not the least citizen of the empire is forgotten.
Not one branch of its life is unrepresented.
Han får det säkert en tajm till dig.
Det råkort krosses Trafalgar Square.
En hundratusen fysiskt att tänka på det.
En hundratusen flotts.
Vad istället.
En av de processen fattig som samarbetar med sprits av det city och västminster.
Palmele och James St.
Lundens klubbland har sprungit om i ashes av many a noble home of the past.
Men det fick inte det säkert.
Eros lukts ut från behind the safety of his hoarding looks out on a scene that would have brought joy to the heart of a Bo Brummel.
Det vore ju att rekommendera att den var den fick det i det säkert.
Det har stämt sig kompletterna i det lasta hundradet år.
Regen Street har stämt sig och Oxford Circus har blivit kompletterat.
Men varje ställe har samma glädje i hjärtat av folket.
Företaget av London förändras, men Londons lojalitet överväger åren.
Och processen vänder sig hemåt genom Hyde Park.
Och här får vi en sista glimt av primärministern, Mr Stanley Baldwin, för som denna dag marknade klimatet för en uppmärksammad karriär.
Och här har vi hennes rörelse, Duchess of Kent och bandet The Scots Grey.
Hyde Park Corner to revive memories of the last coronation procession as it wound its stately way 26 years ago.
And so back to the palace which their majesties left over five hours ago.
Five hours of terrific emotional strain with the solemnity of the service in the abbey and the fatigue of the long drive.
Once again our royal family stands on the most famous balcony in the world for the final climax of this glorious coronation day.
And we join with London, with the Empire, with the world, in crying God save our King and Queen.