Allt islam är krävet.
Från.
Det här är.
Nej!
You have a calling and it demands of you great holiness.
You are to be the messengers of Christ to men.
Go forth to propagate the seed of the adornment and to win many sons and daughters unto God and to the blessed virgin.
And that will require of you intimate union with Jesus Christ.
And Paul said when he went out to preach no longer I that live but Christ that liveth in me.
Christ shall come and dwell in you
Men det kräver på ditt sätt en stor fidelitet till Gud.
Du måste uppfölja Guds fader och göra hans vilja efter människan av Kristus.
Inger, min son, du kommer inte längre att bli kallad James, men Coleman.
Inger, det är däremot om de kommer tillbaka till historien.