Minehead har en historia som är så långt tillbaka till 13-talet.
Här är Norr...
Kör.
Scientist estimerar att den varma vatten kommer från en djupdjur.
Den här jävla kasmen som separerar Somerset från Gloucester är den berömda Avon Gorge.
En britt som är 245 meter lång från den gamla Hungersfors britt som stannade i tempeln.
En hård klipp med en beaksbädd och en bukkel på en varm dag.
Själven i Porlok, som är sammanfattad med poetin Sadi, som beskrivs av de vackra verserna som beskriver vattnet i västlandet.
Man av de lovligaste old towns in the county is Dunster, dominating the main street of the castle, one of the few in England which has only changed ownership once since the Norman conquest.
The yarn market, a relic of the days when Dunster was an important cloth weaving center, still shows signs of the damage inflicted during this beautiful bridge as one of the finest prehistoric monuments
It is 180 feet long and has 17 openings.
And listen to this, you modern builders.
There is not an atom of cement in the whole structure.
This old packhorse bridge at Allerford
is perhaps one of the best in the county.
Glastonbury, which is Avalon, provides that our forefathers first heard the news of these.
And here it was that our very first church was built.
The ruins of Glastonbury are exquisitely beautiful.
Rising straight from the close green turf.
To the arches can be seen the 14th century abbots kitchen.
Behind the kitchen is Wearyall Hill, the Cheddar Gorge and the famous Horseshoe Bend.
There is not a finer piece of cliff scenery in the British Isles and nothing to surpass it in Europe.
Fifteenth century Nunny Castle, through the ages the scene of many fights and storming, now at peace among the haystacks and fields.
Burrington Cool, a wild and lonely valley, where the reverent top lady,
While sheltering from a terrific thunderstorm in the cleft of this rock was inspired to write the well-known hymn Rock of Ages.
The beautiful old city of Wales.
Penniless porch.
In bygone days arms were distributed here.
The vicars close.
And the chain gate.
The chain gate.
The palace I, leading to the bishops palace.
The moat round the bishops palace upon which glides the famous Wells swans.
The first swan to accomplish this feat may be seen in Wells museum.
Wells cathedral stands like a stately sentinel over the tiny city.
Oh, it's quiet down here Oh, it's quiet down here If a bad note should break All the easygoing folk In the village would wake
Oh, it's quiet down here Oh, it's quiet down here And through the long day To the great God of peace
I feel I must pray.
Oh, it's quiet.