TS ES OA	waiting- place in the garden	to call the assembled guests	to the tea-room.
siodt sdjiw 229008 vå AT	TEST SES ES TS SS	[IST TS SES et EST SST TV
On the way they cleanse	their hands and mouth in	erystal water from a stone	basin.
BITAR T CA CRRESESN	through a low window- like	door. This is symbolic of	humility. OF course they kave	[UT SS ST i a
BUTTERS ENN	to the glowing embers and	cleans the brasier.
He next burns incense in		honour of his guests.
[OT IST pr [st	examine the incense-holder	This is a treasure, and its	admiration is essential to	[RSS NA
TTT TE	is prepared with great care	as it is indispensable to	STA
His guests gone, the host	replaces the hanging-scroll	by a vase of simple but	tastefully- arranged Flowers.
When the host is ready to	serve the tea he sounds a gong.
SUS SES TSV	SUS EST	.sonsliz Ivlbogest ni RnoR
NEVER Se	tea ceremony bogins.
The host ceremoniously makes	tho thick tea, mixing it with	a bamboo whisk.
BOTT Er ran	tea from a common bol,	which is passed round very	much as a loving-cup.
IS customary For guests to	admire the bowl From which the	tea is drunk, which is often of		Jäs CEN ET
It is nov time to leve.	The host accompanies his	guests to the gate of the	tea- house garden
ET ATT SITS TEVA	UTSES ESTATE STR En