Ja.
Her country must have great quantity of bread.
In transport, on trolleybuses, omnibuses, on locomotives, the Soviet woman has freed the men for a war to the death against the enemy.
Confidently, she operates a derrick.
För stål.
En viktorisk kanon och stål.
Våra kvinnor och syster har blivit stålsmältare, smittare, frimare, mekaniker och väldare.
En element av krig håller ingen terror för dem.
De vet vad man ska göra med kriget.
For their country, their freedom and happiness.
The fascist scoundrels have raised their hands against the art of Soviet women.
We shall remember.
We shall never forget that.
Never will the Nazi thugs turn our splendid sisters, wives and daughters into slaves and handmaidens of the generates.