General Satisfaction will be felt at the appointment of Lord Louis Mountbatten as Chief of Combined Operations.
Lord Louis has all the qualities of courage and brain needed for successful leadership in this war.
He has taken part in the hottest destroyer engagements of Norway and Crete.
He has been torpedoed twice and mined once.
He planned the raids on Vargso, Brunval and St.
Nazaire.
So at 41 he becomes Vice Admiral, Lieutenant General and Air Marshal.
And we wish him luck and good shooting.
...to the problems of land.
Detta är några av de nya M4-tankarna som rullar av produktionen i en stor flod.
Och ute på prövningar ser de bra ut också.
I krigsutvecklingar opererar de mot amerikanska infanterier.
Och de använder live ammunition.
Men när det börjar så blir det klart.
Efterallt, en hitt från en skärm är som en kick från en hår.
Det gör inte så mycket skillnad om man bara gör det för fun.
Det här är en del av en del av en del av en del av
Det här är en av de största av de största av de största av de största av
Out they go, and out goes our cameraman.
Pictures of floating grace and grandeur.
The deadly, deadly men of action, armed to the teeth.
HAPPY LANDING
Fortsättningarna och rörelserna omkring världen.
Det finns tal om nya krig som blåser i alla sidor av det.
Men navet står som en bestämning för hela empiren.
Inte tyskarna, inte italierna, inte någon annan kommer att bräcka en av dem.
Queen Gibraltar och Middle East War Front.
Välkomna!
Detta är den andra delen av storleken om den stora attacken på konvojen till Malta.
Kamerorna går direkt till Galland Island Fortress.
Och ni kommer att se utlöjningen av tillgångar.
Men först, se hur stor flott det var med escorten.
Inget understånd här om de skador som var möjliga att mötas.
Kapitalskip i fall av attack av Axis surfaceväsendet.
Och flera kraftkarrer.
Det mest viktiga objektet var att få de här förhållandena till Malta.
Därför, på ett visst punkt, flyttade kraften till mörkret för att flytta resten av jämförelsen.
Och så började attacken.
Attacken som fortsatte nästan incessant till slutet av voyagen.
En svår attack följde i kvällen.
Inget skadade sig.
Men vissa krigsflöden skjutsade ner och när man ser barraren så vet man ingenting.
The following day the struggle was renewed with awful intensity.
It is hardly possible to imagine the fearful strain of sailing under such continuous bombardment.
It is hardly possible to imagine how men can endure such a test and come through it ready for the next job.
It's as well to remember now that such experiences must eventually tell their tale.
After the war, only the best must be good enough for them.
Let's decide that now while they're right in the picture.
You can't come through this kind of thing and stay the same.
There'll be many faces with deep lines in them after the war.
There'll be young men with eyes that look as if they've seen too much.
Nearing the destination of Malta, the convoy was met by MLs that came out to assist in the escort work.
These little ships did a wonderful job, both against air attacks and in anti-submarine patrol.
A hit was scored by torpedo on the tanker Ohio.
A ship full of oil, most precious and most vulnerable.
She was next hit by a stuka.
Det låter otroligt, men kameran tog fläken ut och tog henne in i Malta.
Det var alltid en fara under sjön, men de här MLS rullade av deras djur och tog på sjön.
I de korta timmarna mellan attackerna tog kameran en snabb... I stället för att skydda ljuset kom konvojen snabbt mot Malta.
Deras räntor blev trött.
Den här isen kan bara fortsätta med en stor utmaning för män och material.
Men förhållandet och förhållandet som gått igenom var sorgligt nödvändigt.
Se de här själen komma in i harbordet i Valletta.
Fikra i dina minnen de känslorna av de bra människorna på den här indomitabla rocken när de ser att förhållandet kommer in.
Kärlek för att hålla dem.
Ammunition för att hjälpa dem att hitta tillbaka som de har gjort i mer än två år.
Det har aldrig varit en sån historia av heroism och dogged endurance.
It almost makes the whole terrible war seem worthwhile.
Just to learn that there are people with this kind of courage.
We have just received from Moscow the newsreel record of the visit of our prime minister to the heart and capital of the Soviet Union.
A visit that was a well kept secret until the announcement just before Mr. Churchill's return to Britain.
It followed the premier's visit to headquarters in the Middle East.
Two theaters of war in which tremendous odds are at stake in this year of our destiny.
Familiar figures attended the airport to greet the envoy of Britain.
You will have recognized Mr. Molotov and Sir Alan Brooke and Mr. Harriman representing America.
Red Army guards were guard of honor while the national anthems were played.
Mr. Churchill inspected the guard of honor.
And here in Moscow they remind us of the superb resistance their comrades have been maintaining against the German armies in the south.
Det var en minister med ett short speech om det var en back to Moscow.
Det var en meeting of the leaders of Great Britain and the USSR with the representative of President Roosevelt.
We have seen something of what the Red Army has been doing.
We guess that they will hold fast until the counteroffensive can begin.
Until the scourge of Hitler's tyranny can be wiped out by these united nations.
This presumably was where great plans were laid.
It has been reported that the discussions were exceedingly frank.
Good.
Frankness between such men amid the fog of war would be like an arctic gale through a third class smoker in the blackout.