FIRE
After that we called on	the potter and found him	working ona new set of	dishes. But he stopped	long enough to make us		PS
NAS deeply interested	in the water jar but his	trousers intrigued us still	[SL
It looked simple enough at	the start, but the endless	layers of clay were only	the beginning. Then came	the handles, polishing and	painting. How much easier	io buy ones crockery at	the five and ten cent store!
We found the wigoly bridges	FNS SEEN EINER	MALEN MSIE	esque, perhaps, but discon-	certing. Unless your conscience	ENN SRS EEE NVSS	sure whether the wipole's		in you or the bridge
Jom ow sbie 1odto edt HU		FER VITS Et SET Tesa		Nog DT STF		orlw 2nsioieum 10 basd	sb [ITIS ETEN TS		bavod Ivtsgod gauox s
We reached Mito in time		to witness the lighting of	the fire rocket which is	sent ahead of the proces	sion to scare away stray	devils,and then looked in		on the parade itself.
este ss all	BETE ERNA	FRESTAS
And once the religious	ceremony was over, the	spirit of fiesta claimed	the day.
SRA	costumes were not as		simple as some that we	had seen in Greenwich Village
NE then we came on a	dance that made us forget	the simple life and goat skins.	MTI SENSE SEEN	our heels we saw a chance	to give the world a new interest.