The angler, playing his salmon, sees the wealth of the forests hastening towards the sea.
The logs pass by great hydroelectric stations which supply the industries of North Sweden with power.
Here we have the Hammarforsen power station of the Swedish Pulp Company.
On and on the logs go until finally they reach the sorting stations.
Där, i resten bakom boomen, är olika ägarna avgörda.
När de har kommit till sovgården flödar timberna på gränserna tills det krävs.
Ägarna är tagna upp till gränsen genom tillgångar.
Först går alla unbarkade ägar till barkningsplantan.
Barket är samlat, fridt från vatten i skruvpressar och används som fjol för fönsterna.
En slidkontroller tar barksloggen till en annan grädde.
var de är sorterade i säsonger.
En annan tillverkare tar dem till säsongen.
The sawn timber is arranged in small stacks.
These stacks are either transported to drying kilns or to the yards for outdoor seasoning.
In the yards, massive bridge cranes seize the stacks and carry them along
together with the men to handle them.
In the course of time, when fully seasoned, the sawn goods are ready for shipment.
The timber is first trimmed to even lengths and then loaded on the steamers, either direct or from lighters.