En ekvivalent störning meeting took place between the leaders of the respective army groups, Marshal Rokossovsky and Field Marshal Montgomery.
The final battlefield of the Third Reich, the city of Berlin, now lies ruined from end to end after the final annihilating Russian assault added to our long-term bombing from the West.
The nerve center of what was once the greatest military machine on earth has finally become a victim of the powers which were to have become the slaves of Nazi domination.
The city of Berlin has almost literally been wiped off the map of Europe.
The time of surrender has come and through the streets of Munich prisoners make their last march as the soldiers of Germany.
In the city of Reims, once under the German heel, stands the schoolhouse where the terms of unconditional surrender are to be signed.
The German delegation, headed by General Jodl, Germany's chief of staff, have arrived for the fateful ceremony.
The general puts his signature to the document which acknowledges the complete defeat of the German armed forces by those of Britain, Russia and the United States.
The surrender is then signed by the Allied chiefs.
The historic occasion is over and General Eisenhower holds the fountain pens with which Germany has signed away her remaining military power.
Within 48 hours the surrender terms were ratified in Berlin, whose Tempelhof airfield is the scene of the arrival of the Deputy Supreme Commander of the Allies, Air Chief Marshal Tedder.
The rendezvous was in a Berlin suburb where the Russians, British, Americans and French await the arrival of the commander in chief of the Wehrmacht, Field Marshal Keitel.
After the formal inquiry, the Field Marshal adds his signature to this momentous document.
Musik Musik Musik Musik
Finally, the supreme commander, General Eisenhower, speaks for all the United Nations.
The Allied force, which invaded Europe on June 6th, 1944, has, with its great Russian allies and forces advancing from the south, utterly defeated the Germans by land, sea and air.
This unconditional surrender has been achieved by teamwork.
Teamwork not only among all the Allies participating, but among all the services.
land, sea and air.
To every subordinate that has been in this command of almost five million allies, I owe debt of gratitude that can never be repaid.
The only repayment that can be made to them is a deep appreciation and lasting gratitude of all free citizens of all the United Nations.
Following the supreme commander's message, army signalers joyfully send out the news to their comrades all over Europe.
The Prime Minister's message to the nation brings about the great period of thanksgiving and rejoicing for a complete and final European victory.
Musik Musik Musik Musik
One of them only went.
It was the same story of wildly cheering affectionate crowds greeting the man who had led them through the dark days and the days of triumph with the courage and strength which has won the acclaim of the world.
A most pleasant duty for the premier was the visiting of the ambassadors of our allies, first of all France.
The American ambassador Mr. Winant gives a warm welcome to the premier who was accompanied by his daughter Mary.
At the Russian embassy Mr. Gusev receives the good wishes of a staunch friend of the peoples of the Soviet Union.
The very heart of London was the scene of countless unofficial meetings of the United Nations on the two great days of rejoicing.
Beginning their series of victory drives, the king and queen visit south and east London where the people who've stood up to some of the worst bombing the enemy could produce cheer them on their way.
Amid de skadade händerna av de brittiska människorna, som så bra har avstått de många skräck och svårigheter av totalt krig, har spiriten blivit född, vilket kommer att säkerställa en stark och hållbar frihet i Europa, och i slutändan hela världen.
De flesta av de flesta på VE-dagen var i Whitehall, när primärministern oerhört pratade med de flesta som samlade sig för att stödja honom.
Det här är din vikten, sa han till dem.
Och de här ordet kommer länge att bli minskade av de som har hört dem prata.