Every day is Saturday in Harlem.
Every night a great big holiday.
Hip cats sing and dance each night in Harlem.
You can hear them 20 blocks away.
Happy faces going places Everyone's a rhythm hound Every day is Saturday in Harlem Every night a great big holiday
Jag vill säga att ni har bara sett Varje dag är söndag i Harlem, med Hilda Rogers.
Nu har vi en musikreview av Jag är en bra, bra kvinna.
Störd av den fina Una Mae Carlyle.
Jag är en bra, bra kvinna för alla som älskar en man.
Jag är bra på att älska och få allt som kan bli älskat.
I knew my man was coming so I kept right on humming I'm a good, good woman for any loving man to have
I'm a good, good woman for any loving man to have I'm good at loving, I'm really not so bad
You don't know what you're missing until I get to kissing.
I'm a good, good woman for any loving man to have.
Men nu vill vi göra vår version av Ration Blues.
Här går det.
Ration Blues
Baby, baby, baby What's wrong with Uncle Sam?
He's cut out on my sugar Now he's messing with my ham I got the ration blue Blue as I can be
Those forty little ounces Gotta last me all the week I gotta cut out on my jelly It takes sugar to make it sweet I'm gonna steal all your jelly baby And rob you of your meat I got duration blues Blue as I can be Oh me I've got duration blues
I like to wake up in the morning With my jelly by my side Since rationing started baby You just take your stuff and hide They're reduced to my meat and sugar And rubber's disappearing fast You can't ride no more with papa Cause Uncle Sam wants my gas I got the ration blues Blue as I can be For me For me