For more than half a year the Lend-Lease Act has been in force and almost since the beginning of the war we've heard of American factories working for Britain.
We've followed with breathless anxiety the dangerous passage of these vital goods across the Atlantic.
But we haven't seen very much evidence with our own eyes of the stuff in Britain.
In the pictures that follow you will see just a small part of that war material made in United States factories.
You will see how the stream of modern weapons is swelling to a flood.
You will see an endless chain of steel fighting equipment flowing in to equip a new British offensive machine.
It's a pity these pictures can't be shown in Germany and to the countries now occupied and oppressed.
The effect would be revolutionary.
For all this, we have to thank one man.
At the start of the war, America was 3,000 miles away from our battlefields.
Her policy since the last great war had been to keep her nose out of European affairs.
And you couldn't honestly blame her.
Men amerikansk president hade den genus som förvånade Hitlers design för världskonkurs med omöjlig klarhet.
Han kände att om Britannien gick ner så skulle Amerika också gå ner.
Men han hade jobbet med att sälja den här förvånningen till miljoner av amerikaner som inte ville tro på det.
Det du ser nu är evidens av hur bra han lyckades.
Ja, vi i Britannien har bra skäl att säga tack, Mr. Roosevelt.
Inom en av depoterna av Royal Army Ordnance Corps får de och testar amerikanska fjällgångar och förutsättningar.
Tänk på hur många år vi har startat demokraterna med armat för krig.
Och även om vi kände vad Hitler gjorde, var vi fullständigt nöjda med att hoppas på det bästa och låta honom gå igenom det.
Det är ganska tydligt att priset vi måste betala för frihet i framtiden är att hålla oss armade och starka.
Ingen tro, efter kriget kommer det att finnas flera ljusa händer som kommer att kalla för världsarmat.
Låt oss aldrig glömma att eftersom vi en gång lyssnat till den kriget, vi nästan slutar att existera som en fri nation.
Nationer är som människor.
It's a great ideal to have everybody disarmed so long as the world is populated by angels.
But nations are like people.
They have the same instincts.
Nations that want to start robbery don't try to rob the big fellow.
They pick on the small and the weak.
Britons strength is growing daily.
And so Britain is regaining her old place now as a leader among the nations of the world.
Thousands of Tommy Guns.
Gästerna av ATS och armatörer testar och samlar i en annan stor depot.
Armatörer plus nära två miljoner män i homeguarden idag är bra.
Det ser ut som om det inte blir lång tid innan de alla har kraftig kraft.
Det här är den verkliga vikten.
Endless conveyers carry the war goods from ship to train, from train to lorry, from lorry to depot, from depot to underground store.
While the Soviet Union continues her magnificent fight, we have a welcome breathing space.
Time to build up a mighty arsenal.
Time to train our men in the use of the new weapons that are coming in every day and every night.
If the invasion does come, every German will stand a good chance of being blown sky high.
Detta är en liten knut till hur mycket hjälp som kommer över Atlantiken.
Mycket hjälp måste nu gå till Sovjetunionen, som idag behöver mer än oss.
Men med den här hjälpen och våra egna stora öppningar kan vi lägga oss på vägen till vänster.
Mr Churchill gav oss nyligen bra nyheter om Vattnet i Atlantiken.
Våra förlossningar är ner om två tredjedelar.
Varje flykt som kommer in till den här stora storhusen är en vänster.
Hitlers excursion against the Soviet has given us a chance we never dared to hope for.
Let's grab it with both hands for speedy victory.
In the meantime, once again, thanks Mr. Roosevelt.
Lady Mac Robert of Doonside has sent 25,000 pounds to the Secretary of State for Air to go towards the cost of a bomber to carry on the work of her sons.
She has lost three sons in the air, two of them in action in the present war.
In writing to the Secretary of State and asking him to accept her gift, Lady McRobert wrote, Let it be used where it is most needed.
May good fortune go with those who fly it.
I have no more sons to wear the badge or carry it in the fight.
You are the crew who have been chosen to fly this sterling and to carry the McRobert crest.
And so the crew of the bomber take their places.
Reminding each other to be careful of our microphone in the interests of security or purity.
Be careful what you say, old boy, because they're listening to you.
I say you're taking off now, are you?
Okay.
McRoberts reply takes off for Germany to carry on the fight against the enemies of Britain.
A very proud and gallant lady carries on.
This is the top spirit again reflected as it was when other ladies refused to weep while Germans wrecked the humblest of our homes.
Our Prime Minister says many memorable things.
One recent pronouncement of his will certainly be remembered proudly in this part of Britain.
Tyneside is doing more than it's bid.
During his weekend Yorkshire tour Mr Churchill went to Hull to see the damage suffered in that city from air bombardment.
Here he was accompanied by Australia's representative Sir Earl Page.
På nästa dag gick primärministern till Sheffield.
Och den här andra staden som vet allt om blitzar var i verklighetsmöte.
Visningen blev kvar.
Och nyheterna om att Mr. Churchill drar genom gatorna är den typen av nyheter som sprids.
I Sheffield var munitionfaktorerna besökt och här igen var välkomnande.
Of course you can't please everybody, but if you can get cheers like this in Britain, it doesn't really matter if they're hissing a bit in Tokyo.
Under the Statue of Liberty, 1,200 young Americans are marching.
The latest batch of recruits to the United States Air Forces.
And while youth responded so generously, Roosevelt told Congress about America's $56 billion victory program.
to increase our production rate of airplanes so rapidly that in this year 1942 we shall produce 60,000 planes.
The rate of increase will be maintained, continued, so that next year, 1943, we shall produce 125,000 airplanes including
A hundred thousand combat plane.
Second, to increase our production rate of tanks so rapidly that in this year, 1942, we shall produce 45,000 tanks.
and to continue that increase so that next year 1943 we shall produce 75,000 tanks to increase our production rate of merchant ships so rapidly that in this year 1942 we shall build 8 million deadweight tons as compared with a 1941
Completed production of 1.100.000.
These figures and similar figures for a multitude of other implements of war will give the Japanese and the Nazis a little idea of just what they accomplished in the attack at Pearl Harbor.
American armed forces must be used at any place in all the world where it seems advisable to engage the forces of the enemy.
In some cases these operations will be defensive in order to protect key positions.
In other cases these operations will be offensive in order to strike at the common enemy with a view to his complete ensufflement and eventual total defeat.
Det är en av militarismen i Tjärmen och Italien och Japan.
Most certainly.
We shall not settle for less.
First meeting of the racing season in Iraq.
And the first big social function since the unsuccessful revolt of Rashid Ali.
Picturesque as any race course in the world.
But a surprisingly western touch is the tote.
All the officials, including the starter, are British.
Dash it all, they couldn't be anything else.
The meeting celebrated the end of Ramadan, the orthodox time of fasting.
Now for a sideshow, Indian troops have discarded their uniforms to dance.
It looks as though someone discarded a necklace.
These dancers look rather amusing to us, but the dancers can also fight, so they say in Africa.