And every one of them seeks peace, freedom and social security.
That aim is shared by all.
By Sweden's prime minister.
The leader of the Swedish Labour Party.
Seen here relaxing on his way to work.
It is shared by the man in the street.
By the fisherman landing herring.
The national food of Sweden.
By women in the home.
I such lumberjacks as these who study at night.
All are agreed on this freedom.
Children learn it as they curtsy to the teacher.
The glassblower, characteristic of one of Sweden's most skillful industries.
The builder balancing his bricks high above Stockholm.
The secretary of the treasury, Mr. Ernest Bigfors, whose balance has to be good too.
This working democracy has managed to give the country a high standard of living.
The citizen is taken care of from babyhood.
Into such a modern maternity home as this, the new citizen arrives.
Treatment is free.
Old age too has new anxieties.
Old age pensions in Sweden are adequate.
This good modern life has not been achieved without a struggle.
In houses like these, 60 years ago, the farm worker lived without security.
There were evictions.
There were hard times for many.
But during the 80s, socialism spoke in Sweden.
The right to organize.
Votes for all.
An eight-hour working day.
Such freedoms were fought for.
It was a bitter struggle.
Many gave up and migrated.
25,000 of them a year were leaving for America during the 20s.
Nevertheless, amid world wars and revolutions came a breakthrough to better things.
Labour's great spokesman was Hjalmar Branting, known throughout the world as a spokesman for the small nations at Geneva.
He was Sweden's first Labour prime minister.
Great trade depression of the 20s spread throughout the world and hit Sweden.
Labour demanded power to tackle unemployment.
Herr Albin Hansson became prime minister in 1936.
He has remained in office ever since.
He is seen here in council with King Gustav of Sweden.
As the political influence of labor grew, so did the trade unions.
Meet Mr. August Lindberg, chairman of the Federation of Trade Unions.
When he was 10 years old, he worked in a timber yard 13 hours a day.
The Federation vouches for something like 15,000 collective agreements.
And these agreements regulate practically the whole of Swedish industrial life.
Such centralized leadership does not however interfere with the responsibilities of local trade unions.
Every worker in fact is intensely interested in the problems of economic conditions.
Here in the provinces agricultural workers come together in a people's hall.
These workers are not yet highly organized for they belong to an industry of small units.
Their working day was not fixed by law until 1936, but progress is always being made.
Women workers, belonging to the federations of trade unions, are mostly found in the textile industry, where Swedish spruce becomes artificial silk and silk stockings.
Strikes and labor troubles, with the one exception of the metal workers' strike in 1945,
Mediation by the government is also very effective in this conference of agricultural employers and workers under the chairmanship of a government official.
I Stockholm demonstrerar unionism sin kraft och celebrerar 50 år i koncerthallet, stadionet och i den berömda Stockholm City Hall.
I Brunsvik finns en skola som är en del av Federation of Trade Unions.
One of its main objects is to bring sociology and social sciences within the reach of the worker.
Into the beautiful province of Dalarna come scholarship holders from the various trade unions to take a three month course.
At Brunsvik there is freedom to do anything, they say, except that which is ugly and stupid.
That is the only prohibition.
Jag märker att det är en av de ruller.
En politisk diskussion och debatt.
Every statement must be proved by fact.
Not only is this school objective but it is also broad minded.
The chairman of the employers association for instance comes to lecture every year.
At Bonners Beak
There is a rather younger school belonging to the social democratic youth movement.
Here the courses are shorter.
One week you may find journalists there from labor papers.
There are 33 labor dailies in Sweden.
Another week there may be canvassers preparing for an election.
The Swedish labor movement has its own publishing house.
Book clubs and cheap editions in order to supply the worker with literary and topical books wherever he is working.
Labour has indeed launched its own literary offensive.
Amongst the most important writers in Sweden today are proletarian authors.
One of the best known, Eva Loh Johansson, has described the poor sharecroppers.
Moa Martinsson dividerar sin tid mellan farmor och skrivning och har skrivit fina böcker om arbetslösheter.
Den stora handelsskolan i Stockholm som började under depressionen, förlorar nu.
Hon förvandlar specialiserad träning för unga arbetare i alla typer av klasser.
800.000 kooperativa medlemmar är länkade tillsammans i head office av Sveriges konsumtionskorporation i Stockholm.
Kooperativen har hållit ner priserna och har gått in i den industriella livet i landet på en stor skala.
Här är Kornholmen, en äldre island nära Stockholm, helt ockupad av kooperativa industrier.
Some of the famous Swedish crispbread is the product of the flour mill.
Here is the Luma lamp made by the famous Luma Girl.
This cooperative industry broke the international electric bulb monopoly in 1930.
And its most interesting product at the moment is fluorescent lamp.
A lamp for the home of the future.
Co-operativ spirit is well demonstrated in the China factory of Gustavsberg.
Special attention is paid to unmarried workers.
Orders are provided for bachelors and for young unmarried women.
Hållning har alltid varit en av stjärnorna i arbetslösheten.
Frihet att leva och få upp en familj i häftiga, moderna förhållanden.
En 12-dagar-vakation för varje svensk arbetare.
Det här, tillsammans med en kortare arbetsdag, är arbetslösheten.
Här går de, att träffa den bästa och bästa vägen.
Alla vattenvägar i Dalarna.
Eller att ta båten till Gotland i Baltiken.
Den magiska staden av Bisby.
På västkast, framför Norra sjön.
De hittar solen, resten och energi.
Men för hans kvinna innebär en fredag ofta svårt arbete.
Frukter att välja, till exempel.
Kvinnors klubbar har därför försvunnit regeringen att ge vakationer.
Prime minister himself was interested in the scheme.
In 1945, 4,000 housewives took these courses of rest and of education.
Music and dancing have a special traction for the young, and many trade unions have their own orchestras and choirs.
The very young receive more attention than anybody.
More playgrounds.
Better medical care.
More day nurses.
These are on the program for the future.
Sweden has a critically low birth rate.
And it is clear to everybody that family life can best be encouraged by such social measures.
Swedish youth must be educated to become good democrats and good internationalists.
Här är norska ungdomar som leder en skandinavisk grupp i Sverige.
Här är bilder från måndagsdemonstrationer i Sverige under kriget.
Bannarna pratar om Sveriges vilja att stödja sin frihet och integritet.
Svenska arbetare tittar fram till dagen när de träffar sina kompisar i alla länder och bär deras del i att säkerställa världens frihet.
Security in the home.
Prosperity and freedom.
That is the message of Swedish labour.