A man who set a new pattern for Europe's regents.
A man who is close to the common people of his country.
Who works with them on social problems and loves sport.
But a man who is the central symbol of the old Sweden and its pomp and glory.
The Sweden whose armies were the terror of Europe little more than a century ago.
The Sweden which has not forgotten to be proud.
Annars är det bra att ha liv kreativt lives.
Kronprins en man av strång scientific intresse.
Prins Eugen, kallad Painterprinsen, har gjort mycket för svensk kulturlivet.
Prins Wilhelm, en välkänd skrivare och filmproducent, och prinsess Sibylla med sina kvinnor.
Hon har bara givit Sverige en ny liten prins.
Det tar en tid innan vi amerikaner som kämpade för en revolution mot George III och deras naturliga antirojalister förstår populariteten av Sveriges krigshus med deras människor.
Faktum är att några av de svenska människorna är antirojalister också.
Men jag tror att det är rätt att säga, bara teoretiskt.
De gillar deras egen kring och prinser.
But another institution is democracy, and a real upsurging democracy it is.
This is a mayday demonstration.
The place, Stockholm's, är det.
Here, all political parties, the social democrats, the conservatives, the communists, the farmers party, and the people's party, gather to hear their leaders.
The man who heads this democracy is Tage Erlander, the prime minister.
Looks like a Harvard professor, doesn't he?
Här är människan Erlander, en förmån skolledare.
En stor familjsmän, primärministern, tar tid att tala med sin grann.
Sweden har, i sin uppgång till sociala problem, ofta visat sig till resten av världen.
Av outstanding quality are her homes for old people.
Her social security legislation.
With New Zealand's probably the most advanced in the world.
Her courts of industrial relations.
Her subsidies for housing low income groups and large families.
Provisions for the care of children.
Including free school lunches.
Community nurseries.
Men det är inte så att det är så att det är så att det är så att det är så att det är så
Sweden faces many economic problems as well.
There's a devil of a coal shortage because of the late war.
This affects Swedish industry rather seriously.
Wood largely replaces coal for fuel.
Here are piles and piles of it in the streets, stacked for winter use.
Since the first year of the war, except for a few weeks each winter, Swedes haven't any hot water in their apartment houses.
Most Swedes think that their standard of living is too low.
For example, most people have bicycles instead of automobiles.
Here are masses of them in the streets.
Makes one do some driving problem.
But it's good exercise.
Or am I rationalizing too?
The Swedish government is committed to a program of full employment.
And plenty of work is going on.
But not enough, many Swedish experts think.
De vill få upp produktiviteten och för att göra det ska de vända sig till Amerika för tekniska studier.
Men de vill också hålla inflationen ner.
Så de har hållit på med sina krigstidspriser och krigstidsrationeringar av mat, mutter, sugare, bröd och sopa.
Och priserna har blivit ganska ständiga.
Så kanske Amerika kan lära sig något i tillväxt.
Nu är vi i Småland.
En väldigt stor del av de svenskar som migrerade till Amerika kom originalt från Småland.
Så det är som att det ska inte mig att det är som att ju ålder folks.
Det är en ålder säng att det småländer kan väcka stångs av en grov.
Och det var en part av det.
Det är som att de just bara haft att du där.
Det är för det har dragit country där.
Det gröta av det smålande grås var Linnaeus.
Det kan ju få flowers.
Det är hans hals.
Smålande is mighty old country.
Lats av det vikings som stannar upp.
Everywhere from the Black Sea till Greenland.
Helt från där.
Here's old Kalmar Castle, as beautiful now as it was in the 12th century.
Inside those walls in 1397, all Scandinavia was united for a little while.
And if we push out to sea, a bit to the east, we hit Visby on the island of Gotland.
Visby, once queen of the Baltic, the richest town of the Hanseatic League.
It coined its own money
Med ett sådant märkta imorgon vad det är i mörkontollet.
Vars.
Down we go, Tyskona, the granary of Sweden, and the home of many great men, like, well, Edvard Persson.
It's a fat country, I mean flowers and things grow there like all get out.
That's also true of Holland.
Nothing to do with the Dutch Holland except that it sounds the same and sort of looks the same.
It faces the sea and warm winds from the west lave it.
Nice country for a cycle trip.
That's Varberg, Holland's ancient fortress.
Looks like a tough nut to crack, doesn't it?
Now we're moving north, up the west coast.
This is Gothenburg, Sweden's second city.
Swedens största port framför väst och har starka kulturella och ekonomiska förhållanden med England och Amerika.
Det är en tydlig, tydlig gammal stad.
Och hans attitude mot Stockholm är ungefär som Fort Worths till Dallas eller Brooklyns till The Bronx.
Gothenburgs harbor är en av de busigaste i världen.
Utifrån den här porten flödar frukten av svensk industrin.
Lokomotiven för att sätta Europas smärta transportsystem i motion igen.