Varje år är den stora eventet i familjens liv hela världen sin nya automobil.
Det är inte att familjens bil behöver förändras, utan att varje år är bilarna fintare.
Bilarna är säkrare, snabbare och mer ekonomiska.
Vad gör det möjligt?
Hur kan bilarna bli bättre varje år?
Ansvaret till den frågan är en drama som skapas bakom scenen där en ny bil är skapad.
Story begins in the division for customer research, where a close check is kept on what the automobile buyer wants in his next car.
Thousands of questionnaires, field reports and surveys help the designers to anticipate public needs and desires.
The new model of today is the result of engineering research, or testing new metals and new construction.
Those car manufacturers who enjoy the advantages of this central research organization have an invaluable source of knowledge for keeping their products truly up to date.
Each factory adds to the findings of the parent institution that results of special studies in their own laboratories.
They study the strains and stresses in new gear designs or examine the effects of new materials for brake drums and lining.
In the art and color division of General Motors, new body designs are created in clay.
These new models combine the latest trends in styling with the engineers specifications for overall size and riding comfort.
At the central proving grounds, each General Motors car division has its own staff for putting new designs to exacting tests, checking performance, economy, safety.
Durabilitet och frihet av operationen.
Det tar ett kombinerat arbete av många människor för att skapa ett nytt modell.
Allt detta arbete är koncentrerat och koordinerat i fabriksingenjörsdepartementet.
Ingenjörerna är männen som har blivit ansvariga för att hålla produktledarskapet i sitt område.
Allt måste förstås börja med en idé.
Och chefträffaren ser att dessa idéer skapas på papper här i träningsrummet.
Den här stora bilden säkerställer att allt kommer att finnas när jobbet är samlat.
Från dessa bilder skapas verkliga modeller av samma material som kommer att användas i produktionen.
And the new car begins to take shape almost as soon as the drawings are made.
Mekanikerna i ingenjörsdepartementet uttrycker bilderna till metall.
Ingenjörerna arbetar med tillverkare för att se till att alla nya delar är praktiska från en tillverkningspunkt, så att de kan bytas och samlas i kvalitetsproduktion.
Varje ingenjör är ansvarig för designen och kvaliteten av en definitiv del av bilen.
Han följer den hela tiden, från början på papperet, till att det är samlat i den fina bilen.
These cars are all tailor-made.
Each new part is handwork from the master drawing.
Some of these men have been on the job for over 25 years.
And that holds true in all the manufacturing divisions of this great institution.
Now let's see what some of the engineers themselves are doing.
The electrical engineer has to keep up to date on everything from spark plugs to radio.
Cars must withstand the extremes of all climates.
This engineer wants to see if a new engine will start at below zero temperatures.
And if it will start here, it will start anywhere.
The supervisor of the dynamometer room has been running this new engine at top speed for 200 hours because he wants to find out how much longer it will run before something goes wrong.
Back in the factory, the body engineer and his men are working with wooden models.
They use these models in making final improvements in the body.
The executive engineer is really the business manager.
He heads the experimental shops and also has charge of personnel.
Vi är sist en chefingenjör.
Här är det byggd jobb av keeping fängs workings modell i en efficient leg by koordinering.
Det verkar bestämt.
En i charge av det inta departement responsible för all the work that is done there is the chief engineer after all of the designing has been finished.
All the tests run in the new parts, the tools and dies made up the new model is put into production.
The manufacturing division has stalled the world for the finest materials.
Manufacturing methods have kept pace with every step of engineering progress.
Better, more efficient machines have been developed.
Finer automatic tools, precision equipment, more sensitive checking and measuring instruments in the hands of experienced workmen control the quality of every part.
Men historien av alla dessa metoder och av alla saker som hände bakom sidan är bara en förslag till den stora historien varje marknadsdivision av General Motors har att berätta om.
Den historien av sin egen nya produkt.