Musik Musik Musik Musik
Övergången.
Det här är den gamla skrivelsen.
Skrivelsen skriver så här.
Det här är skrivelsen.
Håll handen mot skrivstornan.
Arbetsutgivare, berättelsen A. Berättelsen A. Berättelsen A. Berättelsen A. Berättelsen A. Berättelsen A. Berättelsen A. Berättelsen A.
En femårig utbildning visar att barnen lär lätt lära sig att skriva och lära sig att lära sig att lära sig att lära sig.
And it is well for us to remember that this America of ours is the product of no single creed or race or class.
We who have faith cannot afford to fall out among ourselves.
The very state of the world is a summons to us to stand together.
Religion in wide areas in different parts of the earth is being confronted with irreligion.
Our faith
It is because of that threat that you and I must reach across the lines between our creeds, must clasp hands and make common cause.
No greater thing could come to our land today than a revival of the spirit of religion.
A revival that could sweep through the homes of the nation and stir the hopes and the hearts of men and women of all faiths.
To a reassertion of their belief in God.
And their dedication to his will.
For themselves and for their world.