Thousands of years before Columbus reached the New World, a migration of Asiatic nomads moved eastward across the great ice bridge that joined the continents.
They were refugees from the bleak plains of Siberia, driven by hunger and the urge to find a new homeland.
All but a few moved southward, seeking a gentler climate, a richer, easier life.
Those who stayed behind to settle on the harsh Alaskan tundra were a hardy, courageous people.
And their descendants survive to the present day.
They are the Eskimos.
Year after year they fight the elements for the simple necessities of existence.
But of all the primitive Americans, they alone have never felt the yoke of conquest.
And though they're poor in worldly goods,
Strangvis hittills har de hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills
Det är nog krona drömsdagen.
Det är inte en post.
Men på andra hand, det är inte en egen.
Det är inte en kvinna, men det är praktiskt.
Eftersom det här är en trådlös land, så är det helt satt och drift.
Så villkorna finns ofta på sjön, nära naturens lomby.
När en Eskimo bygger en hus, så bryr han sig också.
For he must anchor his timbers deep in the earth to keep it from blowing away with the first gale of winter.
And he doesn't have to buy his lot.
He builds where he pleases.
He uses no plans, but builds almost by instinct.
For Eskimo methods and customs never change.
They've been passed down from father to son through countless generations.
A good thick layer of earth, firmly packed-
Och huset är färdigt.
Här är det.
Homesweet home.
Kompletterat med norra utsläpp.
Varje moment av den korta sommarsäsongen måste användas för att förbereda sig för de långa vintermånaderna framöver.
Varje dag är försiktigt planerad.
Och byggandet av en huvudbåd är en sak av första vikt.
Eskimos är fina kraftare.
Working with only the crudest of hand tools, they get remarkable results.
Walrus hides carefully stitched together are used to make the outer covering.
This is a job for the women, from young girls to grandmothers.
These seams must be absolutely waterproof.
Delar av bergmänna och det fändades.
Nästa männen påbörjar igen och läskar öppningen till båtskärmarna med råhide.
Det är bara några slutklipp nu och båten är redo för att starta.
För de barnen är sommartiden mest speltid.
De barnen går in för rucka, rucka sport.
Den typen som bygger starka hår och muskler som är tuffa som råhider.
För livet här är en ständigt test av styrka och stamina, även i spelet.
The games of the girls are more restrained.
De använder sig av att berätta folkhälsor som de illustrerar på den småa mudden på byn.
Men det finaste sporten alls är blankettoss.
Det är lyckat av män och tjejer.
Koganak.
Ammunitionen är kraftfull och en miss kan betyda en öppet huvud.
Hans unga son McAuliffe lär sig i skolan av erfarenhet.
Han har passat alla sina test och håller på med den förväntade kajak.
Han får även en A i plenlighet.
När han fortsätter skolan lär han sig använda krig, både gamla och moderna.
Det finns många saker som en far måste lära sin son.
Koganak har många hjärnor att äta.
Bara hans kvinna, Ananak, och hans barns son, Moan, har han en kvinna som är kvinnlig, som heter Palaia.
As well as three young girls, Nepecha, Chicoyac and Niala.
The boy baby is always the idol of the household.
Sometimes the gathering of winter stores has all the excitement of a treasure hunt.
Det som är svårt är att hitta huset för tundramusen.
Han är inte objektivet i undersökningen, men hans storhus är full av smakiga nutter och bergar.
På trädgården går Koganek för att köpa några saker som han inte kan skapa själv.
Här uppe är fursen som substitut för dollar.
När det kommer till att göra förändring så tar pokerchips på plats av poäng.
På dagens återkomning är det mycket spännande i byn.
Everybody lends a hand, for after all it's everybody's whale.
Although the white whale is a relatively small species, still this one weighs about a ton.
And that's enough to give every family a good portion.
Now for the treat, a nice tasty chunk of whale skin.
It's the Eskimos chewing candy.
They call it muck tuck.
And it has a taste like beech nuts, they say.
Anyhow, looks like it's good for the teeth.
Every part of the whale will be used.
Even the intestines are saved.
They supply the Eskimo with a sort of natural plastic for which he has many uses.