NOW	Al bl
IRISH MALL STEAMER LEINSTER	LUNv2rn de	GERMAN SUBMARINE.		Pathetic scenes at Irish port near which	00 souls, ineluding many women	and children, perished.
ka LORD MAYOR FÉTES		ABIAN PREMIER.	os föreek Premier (left),		fir nanian Minister		samier (right) on Serbian	suecesses at entree to London's		beo, Town Hall.
bre bowigqss envD		ftvobwmn vwiisns sxoldivi	Hed 20 vallsV” aids ni	bognovs å
RISH MAIL STEAMER LEINSTER	ne:	GERMAN SUBMARINE.		LR EE OT	600 soo, inchdiug many women		FOTEN
Survivors being nursed		ublin Hospital after		lling escapes	pes.
barn gaiod zrovivira
Survivors being nursed		in Dublin Hospital after		thrilling escapes.
Victim telling a journalist		a story of the Enemy'a.	ruthless crime.
'38 2ovitslar avoixnA		.ougroM niidvuG
PRITISH  WORKERS OF THE		2 > Var.	Öredid viclojy demonstration		in PJivmingysg — a great	ntye.
NnsYPRES.
i SR öbhuno ÅLLener,		(ommander- ins chief.
HaidaTI 20 AHA i	anaspn IT pm. 19älnassaD		W smodsw. offaäsepdi	noknod MN anger MR
2 äsTIT	fe Man Pb ha	ARR a AX		viskr ot Wai lien 20008 T	anses RNE
TITLE 2.		GREAT BRITAIN HONOVRS	Irawen DANDSMEN.		British wounded soldiers and	London ciNzens altend in	Ihousands to hear Me Carabinieri	Band in chief cenhes of	Empires Capital
TITLE 3.		Gala Garden Fele On		Trays Day in Londen	Suburb.
TITLE 4,	ERE	CANADIAN SOLDIERS AT		Home IN ENGLAND,	Military sports give zest	to ther patriotism.
TITLE &.		FIGHTING OM THE	Waste RN FRONT.		 		Retiving enemy destroy
FIGkTING ON TAR	WesTtTERN FRONT,		Retiring enemy destvey	Historie, Town ef Bethane.
BURNING HOMES ATTEST	EIR LOVE Of DESTRUCTION,
——