a	IK
AR
qOH2MAOW JHT MOA	RULE X LR	ELO og er fen	PIE TT	EA	tare
GOH2HAOW JHT MOAT	MAAT aHT OT		faume fniunmoes eid ymiÅ bond		FÖRRE EA rg TE TT	däsboN		take
DUR NDR DIN	IN FRANCE.	CEN VERSER SN		ETT	346-1
OUR BRAVE WOMEN	IN FRANCE.	LENE FSENNAES		ETT	ELR
NOTTS WOMENS	GREAT WAR RALLY.		Duko of Portland as recruiting	Na		Kr
WHERE OUR HEROES	Ng		W.A.A.Cs tending Britons' graves	in France.		ELLA
|A		NVC	GREAT WAR RALLY.		Duke of Portland as recruiting	Pr		rd
AU	KATTEN NTE	PETE Te OO		Bo		Dl
OT TI2IV JAYOA	UNNI		.taot las a ni goill od	LIT
ANU	TENDING WOUNDED	ku	[EN SA	VARSE TT		FA TI	Eri
PERVYSE HEROINES	TENDING WOUNDED	NK	LTTE de T'sorclaes EETE TE	Mairi Chisholm were gassed during		FOT	Kurd
ERAN	UTN		ÖRE TNE TTT ERE ETT TI	ORT		DR
LRF RA vn	NN	UTRETT DETT	Briton and Frenehman.
1 RDS		Mr. Clynes M.P opens kitchen at	Stoke Newington.		Kra
KAREL		BEN RESET SES		[EITA
LEVAT	for Lord Mayor at Bt Pauls.		KLLRI
THE WAR WOMEN	DANN		Land Workers' great call up in	Te		348-1
[ENN ERSATTS	for Lord Mayor at St. Pauls.		KLDI
THE ZEEBRUGGE MOLE	THAT WAS.		Where our dnuntloss 55 Navy EI	the Huns with complete success.		348-2
LENS NNAN	Ra	Strenuous football match at	Southend ends in a draw.		KLIN
RR Maa		These men are digging and fighting	for the freedom of the world.		LILL
And Mr. Bonar Law presents record	LUTAR DE TS
IEEE TR ETT EL TT	ÖRA ITE		LI