KE		ViN
då	kak 9
4U
a	( 1 AN H sd KUST i		FR s" THE WAR ANNALS 2 SÅ	(RA ARG RSKR		PETE AA SALG	LUREEENrEN aET eclion lb	de Armee RESA ol OS IN Army 3,		CST FORE
SA IN	0	INTER MO	AREALEN TEE	SR ER fcial oe		ji NGN ee	ERE Cr I JÄEETA		See	Ko PARSE KAN RA TA |
KATE Ta IEA	INATIA ee SINIANIA		SKE [LITAR LL AU RR RIDA: HI	LUFTA JaIHIM 12 30	ee ee a
LES en NS |	REPRENNENQ Lär		LE SAILLANT DS	Wake md
UCI Un		LUUK
Dans la ville. | Within the city
Panorama pris Panorama taken		du MONT SEC from Mont sec
Dans ESSEY | In ESSEY
DELL SINE 1103 ub såninä	EI eu ET qmsd ub	.gniemofl 28b gmed| .2nismof 29b
La plaine de Woövrel The plain ofWoövre	[RI and St. Mihiel .	vue du Camp — Iseen from the Camp	des Romains. des Romains.
[ERS UAHETnT TG	de Chauvoncourt barracks,	oå se produisit la | where the tragic	tragique explosion explosion	du printemps 1915.] of 1915 occured.
A Fentrée LIT:	de ST MIHIEL, RSA LIN	les habitants viennent| The inhabitants	toucher les premiers lare draving their	CRC first French	frangais. CL
CT LUST		ETC ITE: UCI UT CI
LTT Every civilian	CRD: UULH VETT	cette passerelle this passage-way		CENT EEE
Dans la ville. | Within the city
CR CSn LUGER ESn EN	de la République etl of the republic,	Madame Poincaré land Mme. Polncaré		EL Ne	la cité reconquise. | — recaptured city.
A I'höpital civil. | At the civil hospital.
fo pl		Sa Sd 79 Ce		a AES fe Tinne)		ä Eng Nöt hör årg ÅN
RT OR	NPR GQ Ne RN		å SATA KIONEGr	1914-1918	F Doganen Offices VO fran BR		KAR aphic 4	Ul fe VARE SS äg		on	rn frängalse Å of |hE a [UGTA		ik
LG ma - IEICEN TEL DI	banne 2 FT EU	.gnemnad adt yd |.2bnemsllA 28l 189	LE	e	MJ
VIGNEULLES et | VIGNEULLES and	(ENT TT TEES RS GT TT		par les Allemands. | by the Germans.
LL Panorama	de VIEVILLE sous | of VIEVILLE, near	les Cötes, prås HATTONCHATEL.	d'HATTONCHATEL.
Canons allemands | — German canons	pris å VIEVILLE | taken at VIEVILLE	et a BELLY. and BELLY.
Pianos volés Stolen pianos	pråts å gire expédiés | ready for sending	en "DEUTSCHLAND ”| to "HUNLAND ”.
.JIIAVAM 12 .JIIAVAM 12		FETA TATL BO TATT ETT I
LE MUSENSTALL THE MUSENSTALL	( Salle de spectacles)) I Concert room).	Habitants pråts | Inhabitants ready	å åre évacués. | for evacuation.
Un lieu célebre:|A celebrated spot:	COMBRES COMBRES	GRETE
LEE LITET TELE		Austro - Hongrois prisoners.
Groupe d'ltaliens |A group of Italian	prisonniers [UNELTERSR EG		DEER TED Sd from	employés par eux |the Austrians and	en premiåre ligne. | employed by them	on the front lines.
Infanterie américaine| American infantry	EUT going to its	prendre position | positions on the	SEG road from	PONT-å-MOUSSON [PONT ä MOUSSON	å THIAUCOURT. | to THIAUCOURT.
Troupes américaines| American troops	et chars d'assaut land attacking cars	sur 'emplacement | — on the place		des anciennes ROCK	lignes frangaises. | French lines.
Les Américains American troops	dans les ruines de = lin the ruins of		REGNEVILLE, REGNEVILLE,	comblent les tranchées| — filling the	[OLCLIEET trenches and		[TTC making roads.
Aménagement des LET		LASTER ASL		sur l'emplacement	des		lignes allemandes.		[RUTAN TT	German lines.
Infanterie américaine|American infantry	se portant en ligne | going into line	El [TTR TITT	le terrain reconquis. territory.