PRINCE IN THE	PRINCIPALITY	HRIL scrivos at Elin Vale, inspects		Guard of IHonour and shakes hands		ATEA TT		rm SEE
"PRINCE OF WALES	NN		LT ES AT	sets out to visit a ecoal mine, and	afterwards inspects a dockyard.		ELIN		få SN fi EE FRE dk
IN a		iölning 20ve antaog tamil Åogral ok	OT TE FO ETT RT ET	LET VETE ET AT AT ETTA	EA - FY SN LOTT	SITE [1		UY YT
ELPING IN THE FIG
NERVERNA	UNNA	LER Prine ac Wales attends a		memorin! service for officers and	ETT SET TT		340-2
ROYALTY AT GRAFTON	FR		EYE EET	the Prince of Wales and Princess Mary	visit the Exhibition of British	ORSA		fin
PLN: VAN LD ER TAND oNe		Admiral Siv Rosslyn Wemyss presents	medals te the Heroes of the Drifters	Patrol at Dover.		FL
BRITISH IN	RR		Our troops headed bya RT	into the Historical City of Bethlehem.	KLrR
MOURNING	VU ISA	LOTSA ET		Requima Mass at Westminister Cathedral	för the Inte Mr John Redinönd.		Karm
NET TIN	AT READING.		LET [ARSA en KITE TT	seeds and Huntley and Palmer's war	LTTE		Kre
KL Grand [ATT	DS		KLEN
CANADIAN COMMANDER	IML ANT		Belgian General FR RES	A Currie, Commanding Canadian Corps,	with the Grand Order of the Crown	of Belgium.	242-1
SHAMROCK DAY.		Presentation of Erins Emblem to	officers and men of the Lomton Irisk	LL ERT Sr TR TYS AT		KLEEN
LVD SSR		Entraining Mules and Horses	RO TT		ELER
KING AND THE	DOVER PATROL.	H.M. presents medals to gallant	skippers of the famous Drifter Patrol.	3431
MA	TE		dgr	medals to South Alricans in		SMITER SN		Prag
SOUTH AFRICA IN ”	FRANCE.	Divisional Caninäe SO	medals to South Africans in	Delville Wood.		343-2		fa Rd
HUNTERS OF THE	U. BOATS.	FRYS	whereabouts of a U-boat, our destroyers	make a headlong dash for the spot.	KLrd
QUEEN AND THE LAND	LASSIES:		Her Majestys smiling welcome at	Buckingham Palace during the march	ÖSTER E SY		Fred
InucTI BE
FM gle a		LG LETAREN	Prince HenrfOvgyis a buff) airplane	AS	e		Errive	LÄS	LJ
[J	FA SAT VT	The Queen, RR Wales, and	Prince Henry vigjtaj busy airplane	enbigp glor		nd Frod
PE RT ETT		 		SETTLING DOWN IN	SN	[ESS AREA TAR ST	Band playing outside a Synagogue.		MA
RR	PRINCESS MARYS	NNE IN	LEE OR		to Women's ig KAR SETT		a (J Kr Kor	.e9
Färg		ET hö NE	KIT TA ET Kd ERE	CI	14 098	LE]
PRINCESS MARYS	INVESTITURE		Presentation of chevrons and badges	to Womens Land Army at Cambridge.		Erk
KOVE RN ke vi		og nh		NET T Bg FI LJ		Lurad
&	IN EN	LISAS	10 the fö FURSTE	he stöps of the Cathodral.		Kand