tel
se		ti-
Veckorevy 1932		DEN FRUKTADE SOTEN.	Snart är ej Bohuskustens illa	beryktade fjärd, Soten, längre	sjömännens skräck. Arbetslös-	hetskommissionen bygger nu	Sote kanal mellan Hunnebo	EICht Ser KEt Ta
Norra inloppet (Ramsvikskilen)	är redan färdigt.
Mitt på kanalen arbeta nu	500 man med att schakta	FTSE
Fängdammsanläggning.
Kanalens södra inlopp vid	Ålstenshamn är också klart.
JEX		 		RYAN NEN
4U
SVENSK GATSTEN PÅ	SVENSKA VÄGAR!	Följdes den principen, skulle	goda arbetstillfällen åter finnas	vid bohuslänska stenhugge-	rierna. Nu ligger arbetet nere	vid de flesta stenbrott.
Stora lager finnas vid de olika	Barset
KUST SSR ASAT	TED EEnSOCh SATA
När skola ångvinscharna åter	börja rassla?
FI aE TS aEnE	(Durax.)
From these enormous formations	of granite the material is taken	for the world renowned Swe-	dish Paving Setts. The larger	the formation, and the larger the	Quarry, the more regular is the	quality of the material.
sHlorT mon 19woq aimasls dW	NGE Tra 16 IST ee TTT ad	As IssileshA IA och	EJE SROM	ASWOq VIB22S29N
With the air thus compressed,	the Atlas Rock Drilling machines	are easily worked.
TVR SSEEn Ed	Granite, which has a crushing	ETT SSA	as easily as a joiner can bore	a hole in a well seasoned	piece of timber.
Transport per wire cable to the	wedging place for further	treatment.
With the help of the machine		the labourer will now hew the		hard granite as easily as cutting	BIE
Now in one stroke the little	granite cube is complete.
These stocks, which thanks to	the modern machinery are pro-	duced within a few days,	would, with the old method,	have taken months to	produce.