Alla känner av oss själva.
Och så i självförsörjning skrattar vi och tittar på människan tolerant som objekt av amusering.
Men deras liknande till människor är mycket mer än skinn i djupet.
Och från deras historia...
In the wild, monkeys are creatures of strength and grace.
Through living in the trees, the first monkeys grew serviceable hands to help them in their journeys through the branches.
Some, in the forests of the new world, strengthened their tails until they became a fifth limb, strong enough to support the whole weight of their bodies.
As the year went on, they had to reckon with more enemies and different problems from those of the treetops.
For defense and attack, they came to rely more and more on their hands and on the well-developed brains which life in the trees had given them.
Baboons are fond of each others company and live together in large packs.
They love the sunshine and on a fine day the whole colony... They are not hunting for fleas but for loose pieces of skin, thorns and so on.
And they also pull out hairs.
It stimulates the nerves of their skin and they obviously get a great deal of pleasure from it.
Just as a man does from massage or a woman from beauty treatment.
This urge to groom is tremendous.
In their packs baboons have a definite social order arranged like our own.
Each colony is made up of a number of families, and each family is under the leadership of an adult male.
He has one or more females attached to him, and probably several children.
These families, which may remain together year after year, are the basic units of all monkey society.
Early they are young under their bellies, and the young baboon can use its hands as soon as it's born to cling tightly to its mother's fur.
Apart from this, it's quite helpless.
Young monkeys are usually born only one at a time.
Från 5 och 6 års ålder stannar de med deras familjer och deras föräldrar och äldre barn är alltid tillgängliga för att skydda och hjälpa.
Den här långa perioden av växten ger de unga djurna mycket tid för att lära sig.
De har muskler och limmor och försöker att göra de olika aktiviteterna av de äldre som är runt dem.
Dina föräldrar kommer att skada.
Baboons have pouches in their cheeks into which they stuff the food until a convenient opportunity occurs to eat it.
The overlord guards jealously the unity of his family.
He is females.
Högre i skålen kommer de antropologiska aporna.
De har inga händer och har större hjärnor än människan.
Av de människa kreaturerna, de enda som lever helt i trädet är gibbonarna.
Det är det mest gräsfulla av alla djur.
Gay och livlig, vackert agil, de använder sina långa armar för att svänga genom bränslen med fantastisk frihet.
På deras röda avstånd till grunden, de går i rakt, och är de enda mammorna utan män som vanligtvis går på två fötter.
In the early morning, the jungles of Malay and southern China are said to ring with the shrill chorus of the gibbons as they leave their sheltered sleeping places.
Begin to approach human standards in the larger man like apes such as the orangutan.
So human are these great apes that at one time they were thought to be a race of savage people.
The name orangutan means wild man of the woods.
As night approaches the apes build nests in the trees to sleep in.
These nests are not permanent homes.
They are only slept in once and next morning the family moves on to new feeding grounds.
Lively as light.
They live in the same family groups as the monkeys, but their packs are much smaller.
Each family is dominated by an adult male.
In captivity, the human being replaces the dominant male, and the normal impulses of the animals can be suppressed so long as the keeper is at hand.
Och de kan lära sig att behålla sig som män och kvinnor, mer eller mindre.
Deras diet, som alla mönster och apor, är nästan helt vegetariska.
Men en människa har en rätt stor del av maten.
Men det finns ingen anledning till att om hållaren var tillbaka, den stora människan hade mest av det.
The apes, like the monkeys, take a tremendous interest in the fur of other animals.
This instinct shows itself in captivity in a passion for investigating articles of clothing.
Shoes particularly attract some apes.
In taking off a man's shoe, the chimpanzee shows a command of hand and eye far beyond the ability of a young human child.
But it hasn't the constructive intelligence to put it on again.
Det är en attraktiv del av maten, säg en kupp icecream, som är avgörande av armarna.
Den använder en stick för att få till det, för att skapa en lösning.
Och de har varit kända för att sätta två ihop för en anledning.
De ser ut att lösa ett problem som det här, inte bara av trial and error, som en katt eller en kvinna, men också av att studera situationen som en människa.
Oavsett om apen har en definitiv känsla för ljud och rytm.
I råd eller utrymme kommer de att slå rytmiskt med händerna och fötterna på vilken som helst surface.
Det här känslan för rytm blir en primitiv dans.
Samma här lär sig secret av Mankins passion för dansning och dansmusik.
Det är fortfarande större, mer skrämmande människa kreaturer som glömmer sig i skärmen av skogen och flyr från interkurs med män.
Like the other apes, but in all proportion like a man, but are more like giants in stature.
They cannot speak and have no understanding more than a beast.
Many times they fall upon the elephants, which come to feed where they be, and so beat them with their clubbed fists and pieces of wood, that the elephants will run roaring away from them.
At some time, such creature as this developed speech and became man.
Man could speak.
He could communicate with his fellows.
He left the forests and lived in the open.
He changed his habits of feeding.
Unlike the apes he no longer accepted his world as he found it.
With his brain and hands and tongue he shaped it to please himself.
He imposed his own ways of life on his world.
Built his own surroundings.
Created a multitude of machines to do his will.
He harnessed the elements for transport and communication.
The physical world became his servant.
But in all the complexity of a man-made world the family remains the root of society just as it was amongst the apes and the monkeys.
In our families we spend the impressionable years of childhood.
In our family circle we learn the behavior of civilized life.
We learn to keep our bodies well and fit with healthy exercise.
We learn how important it is to take pride in our outward appearance.
Ifall vi har konstant exempel på våra föräldrar, kan det vara en förändring i samhället.
En familj är den högsta uppgiften i livet.