To twenty year old college boys risk their necks in a test at a Washington airport.
The crowd is breathless.
Watch the daredevil upper right slip his chute.
He turns it nearly inside out and plummets down like a bullet.
But the chute works and he's safe.
Nu tittar vi på jumper-testet, dubbelskottet.
Designat av M.S.
Willing.
Det är bara en jobb för jumperna, men för aviatorn är det en framgång i utvecklingen av säkerhet i luften.
It's a big day aboard the flagship Pennsylvania, for there's a change in the Navy's high command.
Gold braid glitters on the Pacific as under the guns of the fleet one admiral salutes his successor.
Trimmed lines of officers in full parade dress look on at the colorful ceremony.
Admiral Arthur J. Hepburn, commander in chief, retires before the flag of a new sea lord, Admiral C.C.
Block, now first in command of the nation's first line of defense.
I New Yorks Carnegie Hall, Sanktionary of Music Lovers, har en säljning för den första Benny Goodman-svingkoncerten.
Maestro och hans band drar en jam-säsong för patronerna.
Han var ändå på väg med det.
Han.
Strike!
Det är av i New Yorks 5000 dollar metropolitan bowling tournament.
As ten pin champions bowl them over.
Strike artist Joe Falcaro takes the spotlight in an exhibition of skill.
Två pinnar, det kommer att bli så mycket skadad lomber.
Och nu en svår splittning.
Med hjälp av vibrering får Falcaro två sträckor på två steg.
And here in this super beauty parlor we find a number of Mrs. Grant's newest treatments.
Firstly this steaming lamp before which the patient sits for a long time whilst jets of steam open the pores of the skin, thoroughly cleanse them and prepare them for surface treatment.
Music
Hjälparna är reducerade och skapade med den här elektriska maskinen som massagerar och skapar dem på den mest effektiva sättet.
Ännu mer skrämmande är den kvinnliga skärmen.
En skärm med tre bläddrar.
Och tro det eller inte skärmar hon med två skärmar samtidigt.
Det är definitivt en skärm över de flesta män.
Actually, she's not shaving at all, but removing all cream and surface impurities in the most efficient manner so far devised.
In the next department, eyelashes are permanently waved, electrically, guaranteed to make any pupil vain.
Rås och rås av kinnar är nu en sak från förr, för här har hon en kinnstrap som en ballongstyrning, som hon skjuter upp för att sätta på hennes kinn och sitter där för en set-intervall medan den minskar och skapar den.
Lastly, the ends to which women will go for beauty turn out to be finger ends.
For by wearing these finger clips constantly, the points become tapered.
And this is surely what every woman knows.
It models it into a beautiful shape.
Nu, vad är det här?
En flygbåt?
Nej, det är inte en tank.
Även om det ser ut som en från den här sidan.
Kanske är det en submarin?
Falsch igen.
Den här märkliga kraften är kallad för hydroglider.
Den kan skimma genom vattnet och navigera väldigt svåra strömmar.
In fact, she is the only powerboat to cover the upper reaches of the Severn.
Mr Davies of Dudley, who built this boat, made a record journey from Starport to Shrewsbury, which is no mean accomplishment, for the water is very shallow and only a hydroglider can negotiate the weeds.
Hur bra atomen spelar sin roll.
Det krävs lite kraft för att skjuta nån typ av båt genom skogsinfestade vatten.
Särskilt för att flytta till starka skogar.
Och så hjälper Austin 7 att öppna upp nya möjligheter i navigeringen.
Let us leave them, forging up the seven.
Charming pictures by famous artists painted on fans of ivory.
Sometimes composed of silken frills when the dignified Gainsborough hats were framing delicate profiles.
But with the passing of the years the fan has retained its popularity and today is the Vaux in softly coloured ostrich feathers.
Väldigt intressant om man håller på och manipulerar rätt.
Musik Musik Musik Musik Musik Musik Musik Musik
Det är en av de största kvinnorna i världen.