Så Malcom Campbell neds nödvändiga skattet som skillnad med his fame var.
Likadant är det finaste skildragande skildrörelsen skildrörelsen och skildrörelsen och skildrörelsen och skildrörelsen och skildrörelsen.
Now hear what Sir Malcolm has to say about some of the driving faults he has noticed on our highways.
Some people are always in a hurry.
Austrian royalty comes to our shores aboard the Normandy.
It's the Archduke Franz Josef of the celebrated House of Habsburg with his Duchess.
It's my first trip to America.
I've never been here before but I admire the American thing, especially the American industrial thing.
All the big manufacturers and the airplanes and engines and so I come here to see all that.
And I thank you so much for your kindly reception you make me here.
You must excuse my English.
It's quite bad.
Thank you so much.
The typical Roosevelt smile and wave of the hand, Lieutenant Colonel James Roosevelt of the Reserve Marine Corps boards a huge bombing plane.
The president's son will undergo the same course of training as hundreds of other reserve officers.
And he's off for the war games and two weeks training in Cuba.
Vår namn skrev en tragisk och spektakulär slut för den mäktiga Hindenburg när den stora kvinnan i skogen blev en funeralspärr för 36 passagerare.
Vår avgörande avgörande år 1937.
Musik Musik Musik Musik
Den här kärleken är fantastisk.
Kanske.