Vi befinner oss på den berömda intribanan utanför Liverpool.
Vi och 250 000 engelska kapplöpningsentusiaster för att bevittna årets Grand National.
Världens mest halsbrytande steeplechase som nu går av stapeln för hundrade gånger.
Vårsolen tittar fram mellan molnen och toalettprakten får utveckla sig utan hämningar.
Vadhållningen är oerhört livlig och stämningen är överhuvudtaget precis så uppjagad och mätta med rykten och gissningar som man har rätt att vänta vid ett engelskt Grand National-lopp.
37 hästar är anmälda.
Av dessa kom sedan endast 11 i mål.
Låt oss inte i förväg avslöja tävlingens gång i detalj.
Vi kan bara erindra om att föregående års trea, nummer 16 Workman, segrade genom en strålande spurt.
Och att favoriten Killstar kom på tredje plats efter McMuffet.
Men som sagt, loppet får tala för sig självt och i övrigt det vi får lämna ordet åt den engelske kommentatorn.
All set, they're away with Rockquilla taking the lead.
At the first jump, Birth Gift heads the bunch.
Hello, hello, there's one down.
Two more and another.
Brendan's Cottage, Drim, War Vessel, Mesmerist and Team Willow.
And five good jockeys out of luck.
At the third fence Royal Daniele is leading and Dunhill Castle bites the dust.
Beachesbrook is just a graceful walkover for Royal Daniele, Birth Gift and Sporting Piper with underbid moving up.
Epiphanies is down there.
And at the seventh, Royal Daniele goes down.
At the canal turn, so usually the graveyard of many hopes, Birth Gift is closely followed by Sporting Piper.
Valentines, they're coming over well now.
No rock quillers down.
And Luckpenny is unlucky.
At the tenth, Sporting Piper jumps to the front, followed by Birth Gift.
Workman is there too, with Killstar the favorite, Underbid and Dominic's Cross.
There goes another.
Underbid är nära med Red Freeman, Workman, West Point och Dominic Cross.
Killstar och Dominic Cross är i ledning med Underbid.
Näringholm, workman is forging ahead.
He's leaving McMuffet with McDominicks cross coming up.
And it looks as if it's Workman, it looks as if it's... Yes, it's Workman, it's Workman, it's Workman with McMovit close behind and Killsar in the middle distance.
Workman wins by three lengths with McMovit second and Killsar 15 lengths away.
And now you know how Workman did it.
The winner is owned by Sir Alexander Maguire and ridden by Tim Hyde.
One of Ireland's finest horsemen.
Workman is the first Irish horse to win the Classic since Troytown in 1920.
An all-Irish victory.
He was third last year.
No wonder they call it the Grand National.
It's worth nearly 10,000 pounds apart from bets.
About a thousand a minute.
As one wag said, it's nice workmen if you got it.