Tack för mig.
Medan fortfarande militära missioner av västerländska krigsmästare i Moskva fanns, träffades regeringsavståndsministern av Rippentrop i den russiska huvudstaden.
Efter en vänlig uppmärksamhet gick ministern till den tyska berättelsen och gick senare till Kreml, där i tillgänglighet till Stalin var underståndet understått.
And of course General Gamla, brilliant commander of the Allied armies in France.
Mr. Chamberlain at this meeting made his first public appearance following the attack of Gout which has been keeping him indoors at number 10.
At Hamilton Field, California, 350 officers and men of the 65th Coast Artillery prepare for transfer to March Field, 400 miles away.
Into the bombers, the soldiers stow ammunition and packs.
After donning parachutes demanded by army regulations, they climb in.
For many of the men, this is the first trip off the ground.
So it's the start of another adventure as the squadron wheels up the line for the takeoff.
38 sky giants with cargoes of artillerymen lift into the air in a mass hop that should take two hours.
But the men get a shorter trip when a driving rainstorm drowns all but one.
Den cirka 600-meterskådande högskolan som dominerar katalansk metropol- är där den fortfarande imponerande gotiska kyrkan- som är dedikerad till Sackro Cuore- som i perioden av revolutionen- blev utformad av röster i en munitionsdeposit.