The alarm sounded and the many peoples of the empire sprang to answer the call for service in the cause of liberty and justice.
Men from Canada, from New Zealand, from Australia, from South Africa and many others fell in and the empire marches.
Hjulet av den röda kanadiska navet röste sig till sina krigsstationer för att öppna dörren genom vilket en krigskrig kan gå och hjälpa att skydda själen av empiren.
Några själen tog plats i norra vattnet, pågående brittiska portar.
Och Sönders av själen, från nära och långt, mött i den gemensamma utmaningen mot nazism.
Andra män från Kanada och Newfoundland började träning för vad som var att prova det mest intensiva av alla krig.
The keynote of that training was close cooperation between all services.
Troops learned cooperation with airmen.
First by instructional classes and later by exercises on the ground and in the air.
And presently they crossed the Atlantic to Britain, first stage on their road to victory.
During the long spell of garrison duty in Britain, their training was continued and was watched with the closest interest by His Majesty the King, who has visited some of the Canadian divisions on many occasions, taking particular note of their modern equipment and their skill in handling it.
Det här är en av de flesta av de flesta av de flesta av de flesta av de flesta av de flesta
Från Antipodes gick flera tusen sonar av Australien och Nya Zeeland.
Några stannade kvar i Mellanöstern.
A battalion from the warlike race of the Maoris, who form an important part of the population of New Zealand, gained the kings a special interest.
The New Zealand squadron of the Royal Navy was soon in action, and one of its units, Achilles, took a notable part in the action with the German pocket battleship Graf Spee off the South American coast.
Hard knocks were given and received on both sides.
Achilles had her control tower hit by an 11-inch shell, but happily the casualty list was lightened.
Efter två timmars samarbete, följt av en alldeles daglig rörelse, åker den tyska flygplatsen till Montevideo.
Den kommer bara att bli skattad av hennes kropp.
I tidigt tid åker Achilles till sin egen port, där en stort välkomst bestämmer prästen av Nya Zeelandarna i deras nav.
Units of the Royal Australian Navy found plenty of work in escorting troopships from their ports on the first stage of their journeyings, while some fought in the Mediterranean battles and other actions.
Mr. Anthony Eden, a lifelong champion of democracy, welcomed the men from Down Under as they reached Egypt.
Inspired by their own great leader, General Smuts, the people of the Union of South Africa have given themselves to the cause and their valor has given pause to their enemies on more than one field of battle.
Det var general Aukenleck som tog in indierna till Egypten.
Och vare sitt värde applåderade de varmast hans anmälning till 8. armén.
Andra indierna deltog del i kampanjen i östra Afrika.
De visade de största kunskapen och hållbarheten, samt att de var apta för krig i svåra länder.
Andra regimens, som gick till Malaya och Burma, gav också prov av heroism överallt.
Indien har sin egen nav som ger det bästa av sig.
Det exakta arbetet med patruller, minesweepare och andra task- är gjorda i en mån som är värd av traditionen av den blåa ensen.
The colonies and dependencies of Africa have sent their many fine native regiments into battle.
Those of Nigeria, the Gold Coast, Sierra Leone and Gambia, forming the Royal West African Frontier Force, the King's African Rifles and the Battalions of Rhodesia.
Their colors already bear battle honors, some hardly known outside their own countries.
To them will be added many others in this second great world war.
Redan har en empire blivit beredd från upprättelsen.
Haile Selassie sitter igen på tronen av Abyssinien.
Is it not significant that from all parts of the world men of every race, colour and creed are marching and fighting to the common end, ridding the world of a system that represents a throwback in justice, morality and all that men have considered as progress?
Emphasis är ställd, och rättvist, på kvaliteten av överväldigande tillgångar av krigsmachiner.
Det är till de människor i empiren som kommer att använda dem att empiren tittar på sista vikten.
Och det är samtidigt med sina komrater från de brittiska islarna, de berömda regimens som har varit till de fyra i varje krig i vår historia, att regimens människor marchar framåt till den ultimata vikten.