The storm gathers.
Its shadow envelops mankind.
It is the eve of cataclysm.
History is being written.
In this film the historic hours of Britain's entry into war are recaptured for you by camera.
How did the people of England act in their great emergency?
Those two memorable days carry a momentous story for future generations.
Krasis har blivit blöjt för en kvartal natt.
I de gamla parlamenten, i hjärtat av demokrati, har medlemmarna varit i säsong under deras normala fredag.
I Downing Street, där primärministern bor, är först den polska ambassadören, sen den germanska Chargé d'Affaires, som är besökare.
Oppositionledare, samt kabinets medlemmar, är kallade in till konferens.
Även om situationen är akut, är krig inte absolut omedelbart, säger vi.
Men hur det ska bli förhållande, kan ingen förstå.
and the preparations for civil defense go on resignedly.
Such scenes as these are familiar to every country in Europe.
It's a tragic thought that the menace of the air should instill the fear of death and destruction into the peoples of all nationalities, whether destined to be friend or neutral.
However, Britain is prepared.
Enormous strides have been made in the years since the September crisis of 1938.
The personnel of the defense forces have increased rapidly in the face of danger.
The balloon barrage and the anti-aircraft units inspire that confidence which comes from knowledge of one's own strength.
Outside Buckingham Palace, the king's sentries pass from peacetime scarlet to service khaki.
The relieving guard wears steel helmets which henceforth will replace the magnificent bearskins.
Världen är inte oavsett, men chanserna för frihet är slända.
Och sjukhuset är evakuerat av deras patienter, unga och äldre, som går till platser av större säkerhet.
Hur patetiskt är det att de unga människorna, i mitten av deras författning, ska ha att förhålla sig till skrämmen som kommer.
Evakueringen ser ut som en stor ordeel.
Det är så skiljt att det finns en plan.
Och så villig var det att få fram att det är minst en tidning av brittiska städer.
Det är därför att det är av rutin.
Departementet av skolbarn var i särskilt en triumf av ordentlig precision.
Från de kraftiga städerna blev barnen i deras tusen hem och föräldrarna bakom.
Och gick bort för att leva i säkerhetszonen under kärlek av deras föräldrar.
And here another concerning thought.
Most of the youngsters went away cheerfully enough.
For them fortunately the whole procedure seemed to hold no terrors and was even regarded as a holiday.
With food and clothing provided by their parents and each carrying a gas mask they entrained for their excitingly unknown destination.
Hur länge ska de vara borta?
Hur länge innan de återkommer att bo under samma djur som deras föräldrar?
För most of them it is the beginning of a long period in new surroundings.
The routine of their young lives has been shattered by the high politics of nations by events such as those of which they read in their history books but hardly yet connect with themselves.
It is indeed a strange experience for these thousands of children as well as a great responsibility for those who are charged with their care during these heavy days.
But the appeal of these homeless youngsters was one which captured the sentiments of the country districts and the country districts cared for them with motherly solicitude
The issue is set forth clearly.
Britten rör färg i en kvar för att höra idén.
Traditionen är sätta färdigt, men det kring österdörring stryk för konferens med Mr Chamberlain, en gränsfull fart.
Det är vi enkslös som har blivit främjare igen.
11 o'clock, an hour sacred to Britain for its association with armistice.
11 o'clock on Sunday, September the 3rd.
The government's final warning to Hitler has been ignored and a state of war once more exists between Great Britain and Germany.
Arriving at Westminster to hear the ominous decision, statesmen set a good example thereafter universally followed by carrying their gas masks.
Efter krisen har kabinet reformerats.
Mr. Anthony Eden är nu sekreterare för Dominion med speciell tillgång till kabinet.
Mr. Churchill, som i 1914, är 1st regeringsledare.
Här är några bilder av tidigare regeringar.
Mr. John Anderson som blir hemsekreterare.
Och Mr. Kingsley Wood som fortfarande är statssekreterare.
Only 25 minutes after war has been declared comes the first air raid warning.
Det här var en möjlighet för brittiska människor att demonstrera deras traditionella kalm mot fara.
Det fanns inga signer av panik.
Män och kvinnor i staden gick snabbt till närmaste fängelset och följde upp i ordentliga processer vid intresset.
Det är allt klart.
Även om alarmet tyckte sig vara en falsk, så var det en snabb minne om vad krig nu betyder för civilerna och en dramatisk introduktion till den nya ordningen av saker.
Evidens that the nation is in earnest can be seen in every street of London.
Notices calling out the territorial army appear on walls and hoardings.
Recruiting depots open for the thousands of men anxious to join the color.
London's taxis are pressed into the service of the fire brigade.
Varför är vi färre än det åker i Gassman?
Mattressen är inståld i en gammalt avsikt för civilstöd som övervånade med vårdverk med rätt.
Men vad görs med lastbiten av här kort?
Det gör en chargé därför att hittills jämför sig en bränsle varje år förbundet.
As for other foreigners in Britain, they have to report of course and satisfy the authorities of their good faith.
War always involves inconveniences for neutrals who are not concerned, but Britain endeavors to extend just and courteous consideration to all the aliens within her gates, including as they do many refugees from countries which have been overrun.
But despite the changes and interruptions of normal life,
The business of the country must go on, and the rush hours show very little diminution of travel.
For many of these people, it's a case of going to the office now and performing air raid precaution duty later in the day.
The common tasks of everyday work are not the least important aspect of the war, which from now on will absorb the whole thoughts of the nation as it musters its manhood in arms.
So within a few days, the people of Britain adapted themselves to the new conditions and set about winning the war with that cheerfulness which never fails them in emergencies.
Vi har sett att eventet skiftar från London till landstinget där Tommy Atkins är på mark.