Jag är glädjad att vara igen i Storbritannien.
Att igen ha den stora och generösa hospitaliteten på den stora och generösa landet.
Det är
Viss.
Han bandet grattis.
Det får han det visst.
Vad är det som är mörkret?
Det måste importeras.
Det visar sig.
För att det gubbar man av det unga ett steg.
Den hade varje borde rovbrusen.
En del heroik amerikan.
Armin.
under the command of General Pershing have played in the history of my own country's rebirth.
We have a deep admiration for your noble national character, for your
Lofty idealism, your love of freedom and your devotion to social justice and to peace.
May God help your president
in his efforts to preserve the world from the calamity of a new war.
May God bless your glorious American nation and give you all prosperity, contentment and happiness.
Men i går höll presidenten i ett effort.
To preserve the world from the calamity of a new war.
May God help and bless your glorious American nation and give you all prosperity, contentment and happiness.
Granit markar stället i Kitty Hawk, Norra Karolina, där männen först flyttade.
Världsavståndskapten Hoover och White gav tribut till den gamla Wilbur av de berömda Wright-bröderna.
En nativ som såg flyget berättade om eventet, J.T.
Daniels.
Vi var här när Wright-bröderna gjorde deras första flygning.
När de kom hit trodde folk att de var galna.
Men när vi såg flyget flyga var det den bästa vi någonsin såg.
På trettiofjärdsdagen av Power Aviation saluterar en flygplats av navet med minnet av de amerikanska pionjärerna av Skywaves.
A distinguished American, twice a member of the Supreme Court and once Secretary of State, Chief Justice Charles Evans Hughes passes his 77th birthday in Washington.
Recovering from a severe attack of grip, the Chief Justice resumes his daily constitutional, which has become a familiar sight in the Capitol.
He's never too busy to pass the time of day with his young neighbors.
The Chief Justice has presided over the court during the most turbulent period of its history.
And although aging, he still sets the work pace for the younger members.
At 77, he plans to continue his distinguished service to his country.
We must fight for our independence to the last shred of our material and physical strength
And the world should know that if we are to have peace we should cooperate in every sane international effort to advance the economic and social welfare of the world.
When we survey the present state of civilization in the light of long history we can well conclude that America has three dominant and immediate missions.
The first is to maintain its own independence.
The second is to maintain a society of free men and women.
Den tredje är att kooperera med resten av världen för att lyfta bränslen av kriget och bygga tillbaka sin prosperitet och sin tro.
Men efter allt är det bara de spirituella, moraliska och ekonomiska kraften som kan uppnå dessa enorma objektiv.
Detta är de stjärnor som världen måste återkomma till i dag.
Och så måste vårt land uppnå sin del av ledarskapet och av ansvaret.
Tack.
Från enskild syns det grejt vård fortifications för Defensiv, en kristin av fester med offensiv land.
Vatten.
Det gick till ett köpsnubbel.
Det är flöjt och ett tecknet.
Västern, de maktisens av gör att de var bärlande och en sida för att syns in på ett nivå till dig.
Att tacka om det är offers vid just.
Det är en internal difficult.
Men det kan bli om det.
The common people in no country in Europe want war.
They are terrified at it.
I do not think that I believe the situation in Europe is not dangerous.
Far from it.
But it is not so eminent as the speeches abroad might lead us to appear.
And what is not eminent is usually preventable.
Vi har lärt oss det här från den senaste kriget.
När vi tittar tillbaka på vår del i den kriget så är det fortfarande en kupp av smärta.
Amerika kan göra krig, men vi kan inte göra permanent frihet i Europa och Asien.
Friheten efter den stora kriget såg på djurens tänder som vi har idag.
If we are to hold that banner of morals aloft, the American people should express unhesitatingly their indignation against wrong and persecution.
They should extend aid to the suffering.
We should not be isolationists in the promotion of peace by the methods of peace.
We should not be isolationists in proposals to join in the most healing process of all peace.
That is economic cooperation to restore the prosperity of the world.
But surely all reason, all history, all our own experience show that wrongs cannot be righted and durable peace cannot be imposed upon nations by force, by threats, by economic pressures or by war.
I want America to stand against that principle if it is the last nation under that balance.
Jag vill stanna där för det är den enda hoppet om att försörja frihet på den här konferensen.
Och det är den största servicen av Amerika till människan.