The land of the free The home of the caring So smoothing to me Thy noble defenders Were gallant and brave All freedom their hearts light They gave
My love, my life, my love My love, my life, my life
We sing to common love.
All the way, all the way, all the way, all the way.
Bravo sailor comrades sing, all the way, all the way.
Till the world with music ring, all the way, all the way.
Sälj vårt och bär vi fri Sälj vårt och bär vi fri Sälj vårt och bär vi fri Sälj vårt och bär vi fri Sälj vårt och bär vi fri
Mord av brantor i ställda vägar.
Arridera mord.
Dörrar på liv, råd och våld.
Arida nu.
Våld och stjärna, vän och stjärna.
Eon, Eon, Eon, Eon, Eon, Eon.
Jag har.
Jag.
Välkommen tillbaka!