On November the 12th 1944 RAF Lancaster went out on business.
The trappers had an undistinguished career in this war.
But in her hideouts in the Norwegian fjords she was always a grave danger to our convoys.
There she lies in Tromsö fjord.
29 are about to drop five and a half ton bombs.
Tre eller fyra bomber gjorde direkt hitt.
Två filmkameror fanns i den här aktionen.
Vi presenterar också filmen som fanns av den andra kameran.
Klacken kommer upp snabbt och snabbt.
Fyra och en halv ton varje.
Turpitsen vandrade över och sjönk med ungefär 700 fötter som visade sig över vattnet.
En av de briljantaste bomberattacken av Riksantikvarieämbetet hade varit helt lycklig.
Vattnet rör sig till norra för en av världens största flytarmarbeten i kriget.
En attack på den tyska torpitsen i Altenfjord, Norge.
Planeerna var beskrivna för den nya Barracudas.
Med en eskort av Seafar, Corsair, Hellcat och Wildcat-fattare.
Piloten är redo för den stora sorteringen.
Vid morgonen tog de första flyget av och flydde till Outen Fjord i formation.
Information kom till vårt navn att Tirpitz var på väg att lämna sin anklagning.
Above the snowcaps of those mountainous fjords, the time was just right.
The first strike caught the Tirpitz in a dizzy dive bomb attack when she was just about to move.
The picture stops to let you see the pride of Hitlers navy well and truly hit and covered with smoke.
In again.
And again we stop the picture.
Hits were obtained by the bridge amid ships and followers.
The second strike hit her fore and aft.
Tirpitz was on fire.
Nu kommer barrikaderna tillbaka till deras föräldrar.
Det här attacken är förväntat att ha skapat Turpitz ut av aktion i många månader.
Efter sänkningen av Scharnhorst är det en mörk blod på den tyska surfacefloten.
Alltid har piloterna och flygplatserna hållit de finaste traditionerna av den röda navet.
De har påverkat en briljant arm.
Bra jobbat!
Efter Bataan och Kidar sa general MacArthur att han skulle återgå till Filippinerna.
Nästan tre år efter de här förlossningarna gjorde han det.
Med 600 flyg.
Destination Leyte.
Värdning och hjälp av den här kraften var en massiv kraft.
Hjälpplänen och flyg var skjutsade eller sömnade av hundratals skor.
Japaniska installerings- och flygplatser var skadade från Luzon till Mindanao.
Luzon
The assault went in.
American soldiers back in force getting close to the mainland of Japan.
Dapp casualties were soon reported to be on the 35,000 mark.
American casualties surprisingly light.
The general wades ashore with members of his staff.
We remember the great fight he put up in those early days.
We can imagine his feelings as he watches this turn of the tide of fortune.
In a prison in France during the German occupation a hundred French patriots awaited execution.
For one of the most audacious actions of the war mosquitoes were detailed to smash down the prison walls to make a way for the prisoners to escape, to kill the guards.
In command was group captain Picard, one of the most famous bomber pilots remembered as pilot of F for Freddy.
A film was to be taken of this delicate operation.
The crews were briefed.
On the map you see how they were to fly straight across and turn north as if heading for Dulham.
This to receive the defenses.
They would then turn for the Albert Amiens road and go flat out for the prison east of Amiens.
This model was used in briefing the air crews.
The Albert Amiens road at the back.
At each end the prison quarters in which the Nazi guards were housed.
The main building contained the prisoners.
The first twelve aircraft with New Zealand and Australian crews had to breach the outer walls on the wall of the prison even at risk of killing some of the patriots.
They had also to destroy the guards quarters.
The remaining six aircraft were British held in reserve in case the first waves failed in their task.
They did not fail.
The attack was made in February although the film was only just released and it was snowing when the mosquitoes started out.
They were to fly as low as possible over land and over the channels
De var använda i det använda stället av en krigsresurs av tyfooner.
Minns du att det hände i Frankrike några månader före D-dagen?
As the camera plane approaches the target you can see how well those first mosquitoes have done their job.
The film has been slowed down and stopped to show the perfect results of this exceedingly tricky bombing.
If those bombs had gone astray all the patriots would have been killed.
Men de blev redan döda av nazisterna.
RAF gav dem chansen till frihet på denna 11. kvartal.
Det här är fönstret som filmades från grunden efter förlossningen av Amiens.
Två moskéter och två krävare blev förlorade.
Och en moskéter blev flyttad av gruppkapten Pickard och sin navigator, Flightliften och Broadleys.
Pickards simple grave is the memorial to one of the finest airmen this great air war has known.
We learned some time ago that Mr. Roosevelt was re-elected for a fourth term.
These are the first pictures which show us how it was done.
Why it was done was because the people at home and the men overseas wanted the president to finish the terrific job he's been doing so well.
They do things on a big scale in the United States.
Han kanske inte menar att det var för att det var en av indigest.
Men det kanske inte var att det inte var det att det inte var det att det inte var det att det inte var det att det inte var det.