...of the invasion chiefs was held at headquarters.
General Eisenhower left with Admiral Ramsey, the Allied Naval Commander-in-Chief.
In this third section of the newsreel record of our invasion, these further graphic pictures show the consolidation of the beachhead positions and the thrust inland.
The weather was none too good, but the little ships plugged on manfully to the beaches, bringing enormous support in manpower and weapons.
And bringing also the mechanical needs of our army and air force.
The means to build our first airfields in France since 1940.
After a day when the skies were too grey for useful flying, the great air forces went once more into the attack in strength.
Again the air vibrated with the roar of hundreds of bombs.
The second installment of the neutral record of the invasion of Western Europe.
This cameraman with British paratroops and airborne units surveyed their assortment of weapons.
They painted their planes with the invasion recognition markings and they packed their gliders with a million things that had to go with them on their journey over the Atlantic wall to Nazi-occupied Europe.
Watches were checked to read alike.
And those who were making the first night's descent blacked up.
In various harbors around Britain, a mighty fleet of little ships was ready for the great undertaking.
Anchored beneath a barrage of balloons, waiting for the soldiers to go aboard them.
I which each man commits himself and the adventure of which he is part to the mercy of God.
Zero Hour.
Following up the first airborne and paratroop landings in Normandy, these British reinforcements prepare to leave.
Already we have heard how magnificently they fought.
It will be a long time before the full story of their skill and courage is told.
Här är den nionde Air Force Troop Carrier Commanden.
Amerikansk flygplats och paratrooper packar in för deras mest farliga flyg.
De två har kämpat med matchlös skillnad och kraft i...
Före landningarna, typhooner av Royal Air Force, har jobbet med att skjuta upp krigspositioner, radarradarstationer och radioinstallationer.
De här typhoonerna håller raketer.
Se effekten när de kommer på målet.
Det måste vara lämpligt till din imagination.
Förlåtningarna för landningarna.
Många allierade krigsplaner i Britannien ställde upp en ständigt assault.
Tusentals ton av bombar utlöpades på en pinpoint på en mapp.
Blastade försäkringarna och öppnade dörren till Europa.
Och långt ned under luftskåpet, den stora fläken av lilla sjöar, marschade på.
Men du är en människa med varm färg och blod under dig.
Och män behöver råd att göra ett jobb som det här.
De här männen hade det.
Återigen gick 9F ut för att slå upp oppositionen.
Inte bara över byggnätet, utan längre in, där de tyska rådgivarna krävde snabbt rörelse för kontraattacken.
Och på de byggnätet fanns de allierade rådgivarna fortfarande på sjön.
Det fanns avslutningar, förstås.
Men vi har råd från vårt primärminister- att det var mindre än det här- en underbar organisation av R.A.M.C.
Snart kom de tillbaka till Blighty- som i den senaste kriget.
Vi tackar dem för vad de har gjort- i öppet att få en spedig vikten.
Tillbaka över den andra sidan- de var fortfarande på väg till sjön.
And now, the first prisoners are coming in.
The first line of defense for the Nazi fortress of Europe.
The outposts of Germany.
The watchdogs outside the castle of a lunatic tyrant.
The final word on their work is that they held the beaches secure.
Such a tiny foothold we have gained in a vast continent full of enemy armies.
We had done better than we hoped.
But there is so much more to do before victory is assured.
Pray again.
As those little ships go on and on with their brave cargoes of men.