This kind of horror was the almost daily portion of some people somewhere in the 1944 Battle of London.
The phase ended with the capture of flying bomb sites such as this along the Channel Coast of France.
The magnificent advance of the British and Canadians in northern France to Belgium ended this particular terror that flew by night and day.
Plans had been prepared long beforehand.
Under the GOCC anti-aircraft command general Sir Frederick Pyle the defense was constantly improved.
Och av 8000 flygbomb som lanserats mot oss, har inte mer än 2300 gått igenom kriget.
Vår historia är berättad främst från perspektivet av antikrigsbombarna, som har samlat en stor del av döden.
De kvinnorna är alla volontärer.
Det gör oss alla stolta.
Nothing can be said of the technical genius that went into the guns themselves.
That may be told after the war.
But the work of the men and women of the gun sites on the flying bomb coast you can judge for yourself.
The record days work have gone out of a total of 101.
But many of the defenders lost their lives from the bombs they brought down.
Air Defence of Great Britain fighters joined in the hunt.
Söderngland har haft en stor ordeel under de 80 dagarna efter D-dagen.
Men hur mycket större skulle det varit om de 8000 flygbombarna inte hade förstört 1560?
Om kruven av krigskommanden inte hade skjutit ner 1900?
Om kruven av ballonerna inte hade stått och förstört 279?
Hur mycket värre skulle det ha varit?
Many families have lost their lives and many more lost everything else.
But London looks much the same today as it did before.
What a grand job they did for us, the personnel of Air Defence of Great Britain.
There it goes.
Typiskt av armarna som är använda av en nation som har principer för krig som terrorisering och mörkret av kvinnor och barn.
Det pilotlösa flyget eller flygbombet.
Inte ett legitimerat arm med vilket att vinna en krig.
Bara en evig agent av senslös utbrott och skadning.
Lanserad mot civiliseringar av en alldeles förlorad bullen.
Efter att ha mött den tragiska historien om Griekenland, så ska vi titta på Kretens äldre.
Det här var en tragedi 1941, men vi har återkommit till Kret.
Within range of German waters the peasants plow their land.
And the peasant often carries an automatic weapon as he plows.
Nearby is a rough cemetery.
There are many British and New Zealand graves on the island of Crete.
That is the district where the Germans are waiting.
Och det här är Athens.
Kameran berättar om en annan grekisk tragedi.
Rivaler i det här balkanska kapitalet ställde sig till att kämpa för kraft efter att den tyska upprättelsen skickades ut.
Och brittiska soldaterna fick döda några av dem för att förhindra större blodlöshet.
Kämpningen fortsätter.
Grekisk politik är mycket för komplicerad för att förbättra lättfärdiga beställningar av rätt eller fel.
Men vi måste ta försäkring från den här upprättelsen att det kan finnas flera skatt, även när Hitlers krig är gjort.
The Allies have been sending food to the starving people of Greece by neutral ships during the German occupation and by our own much needed shipping after.
Strikes of Greek stevedores in the Piraeus prevented the unloading of this relief even while their own women and children starved.
But the unloading has since been resumed.
There have been divided opinions on the question of which party should govern Greece.
There can only be one opinion of those who callously prolong the sufferings of their fellow men.
The British force in Attica has been gaining the upper hand.
And when our soldiers are the masters of Athens, the Greek people will have a chance to choose their own government by peaceful means.
In the meantime, thank God for a British statesman who does what he believes to be right and sticks to it.
A statesman who is willing to face the risk of death in order to do his duty.
In the unhappy city of Athens, organized fighting between our troops and the LAS has now ended.
In those parts of the town previously held by the rebels, widespread destruction greets the eyes of civilians returning to their homes.
Street cars damaged in the fighting have to be towed by British lorries.
At large central dumps, captured arms and equipment of the rebel forces is dealt with by our troops.
Angry scenes take place as suspected rebels are brought in by the National Guard.
Life is slowly returning to Athens.
Ships are unloading relief supplies at the Piraeus, soup kitchens are set up and in the streets the people of Athens walk once more without fear.
Attending another meeting is the supreme commander in the Mediterranean, Field Marshal Alexander, seen here on his way to our headquarters.
The commander in chief Greece, General Scobie.
At British GHQ the changing of the guard takes place with parade ground precision before an admiring crowd.
Let us hope that the clouds are finally lifting over Greece and that new happiness will come to our people after their dark and difficult years.
Ärade församling, för andra gången under detta krig går det svenska folket till riksdagsmönnerval i år.
Något avsteg från normal ordning har icke behövt ske.
Detta visar bäst hur väl vi lyckats bevara vår handlingsfrihet och vår demokrati.
Det borde då vara en högtid att gå till val.
1940 uteblev emellertid mer än en miljon väljare.
Detta får inte upprepas i år.
Den 17 september måste alla rösta.
Det gäller ju inte blott att bestämma om våra egna inre angelägenheter.
Det gäller också att utåt manifestera det svenska folkets vakenhet och dess levande vilja att bevara sin frihet och sin fred.
Den som senast i fjol fyllde 23 år har rösträtt man som kvinna.
Rösta den 17 september.