Where are they flying?
What can they see?
That's what the children wonder every spring when the sweeping flight of wild geese attracts their attention and captures their imagination.
Whether they have read Selma Lagerlöfs Nils Holgersson or not, their thoughts are with Acker and the other great birds on their northward flight to the land of the midnight sun.
Where are they flying?
What can they see?
I några bilder kommer jag att försöka ge er en idé av landet som de flyttar över i deras flykt till deras sommaromställningar på Lappland.
Alla bilder ser inte ut som med ögonen på en djur, men de kommer i alla fall att vara vårt behov av att ge er en uppfattning av det naturliga stället i vilket svensk arkitektur var född och uppnådd.
Och det är det största thematet av vår lektion.
In the extreme south then, the birds, and since we fly with them on the wings of imagination, we too spy Scania.
Fertile plains, cozy farmstads, soft smiling landscape wherever the eye turns.
Snart har vi nedanför oss en samling rörelser, som ripplar deras röda väg över deras ståniga dörrar till dörren av Mödra ocean.
Här är sjön, Kattegat, en arm av Norra sjön, och så kapriciös som Norra sjön.
The sentinel fir trees on the outermost fringe of the archipelago are bent and beaten by the storm.
But between the primeval rock massives nestle patches of cultivated soil.
The character of the coast becomes harder and more rugged the further north we come.
But still there are idylls to be found everywhere in the shelter of the bays and creeks.
Far off to the east, halfway to the lands of the Baltic, we describe Gotland.
Where many ruins bear eloquent testimony to vanished greatness.
Closer to the mainland lies the chalky island plateau of Öland.
With its stony grazing lands where the wines are never still.
De följer upp de stora lakerna och skrämmer sig runt landet som en silva ribba runt Jöta kanal.
Och genom sina många lock vänder de vita kanalbåten deras lediga väg från Västernas sjö till Baltiken.
Och snart når vi Stockholm, den vackra, vattenfärdiga staden av Sverige.
Den här gången ser vi panoramen som djur ser den.
Det är också från luften som vi tittar över Stockholms arkipelago med sina tusentals och tusentals små djur som ger tillfälliga charmer till den här norra Vänniskan.
Varje gång vi går till norra, uppstår bilden som i en kaleidoskop.
En väg över vattnet av late Mela.
En glimt av Ruhslagen.
En ideell från en landsting i Upland.
En gammal flöjande bräck i Dali Kali.
Av de blåa trädet är det bara den blåa stämda bräcket som har hållit oss ihop hela den här vägen.
Snart ska vi ha inget annat än pineforsen, där vindarna spelar sin ljusmelodi.
Nu är vi i regionen av de stora rörelserna och farflunga skogarna av Norrland.
Här kommer snö tidigt och stannar tidigt.
Tänk dig att vi är nära arktiska cirkeln.
Du vet om Circle City i Alaska.
Bilden som du ser just nu är från Bull Eden, som är på samma latitud.
Här är en frivillig miningindustri, som använder gold och silver som tidigare har blivit skapade.
Faktorn som du ser är den största i Europa.
Nära 500 st.
Det är bara i Amerika som de bygger dem högre.
Högre upp mot sjön ligger snöet djupt och solidt.
Ofta till och med i maj.
Det är en delaktighet för skivorna som kommer i sina tusen runt omkring i eftermiddagen för att äta den finaste vinteren som finns.
The champagne air under cloudless skies and warmed by the sun.
There is speed, there is suspense, there is adventure.
There is nothing oppressive or overpowering, nothing violent or grim about the Swedish mountains.
They don't tower up and threaten to fall over and crush you.
They have gentle lines, wide sweeping slopes.
There is a sense of freedom and space up there, both in winter snow and under summer sun, which every year wins the fight against King Frost.
The ice mantle of the lakes becomes tattered and torn.
The mountain stream tumbles down.
And the great waterfall thunders over, swollen by the spring floods.
The little laps wave a welcome to the birds.
For they know that with them comes the spring.
We have now winged our way from end to end of the country.
And got our first answer to the question, what is Sweden?
What does it look like?
We are now on terra firma.
We are seeking for the early roots of Swedish architecture.
The material is here in abundance.
bra, substansiella, hårda och starka material.
De kallar för ardua grönsaker innan ställningarna kan skapas.
Men de inser till sina invånare varmheten och komforten av ett hem.
Världen är först och främst den bästa tillverkaren av byggmaterial för ett land som Sverige.
Den har timmer för huset själv.
and fuel to warm it with.
Let us look out once more over those forest-clad heights.
Try to count the trees.
It's hopeless, for they're as numerous as the grains of sand in the desert.
There is timber enough and to spare, and the rivers convey it easily and cheaply from the depths of the forest down to the populated areas.
Från de tidigaste tiderna har en svensk hem byggts av så stor timmer.
En enkel och hållbar typ av byggnad.
Traditionerna går tillbaka mycket längre än vi kan träffa.
Många fina specymer av den tidigaste typen av timmerbyggnad är fortfarande försörjda.
De här är från en kollektion som gjordes av den berömda konstnären Zorn på Mora.
Tyvärr är de här skogsbyggnaderna aldrig utsläppts av krigsbränsle.
Det beror på att så få av de tidigaste svenska byggnaderna har överlevt till vår tid.
We find here a fully developed and cultivated style of architecture showing constructional inspiration and fine ornamentation on the exteriors as well as in the interiors.
In primeval granite nature affords us a far stronger and more durable material which is faithfully preserved for us rock carvings like these.
Skulpturerade innan historiens dörr.
Men det är ett intraktabelt material.
Hård, hård och svårt att arbeta med.
De finaste stålkvarierna hittas på den röda västkosten.
De tillför pavingstål.
Det bästa materialet för att resistera endast hårdhet och tärrhet.
Till den här dagen är kvarteringsprocessen en verklig handikraft.
Maskineriet är mest använt för att transportera det hårda materialet.
Granit har från tidigare tider använts för väggar av fortifikationer eftersom det ger den starkaste motstånden.
Tiderna var hårda och materialet måste också vara hårda och hårda.
En verklig manifestation av mentaliteten av de där tiderna.
Built of rock upon rock, these fortress walls have successfully withstood the assaults of nature and of man.
Gradually the spirit of the age underwent a change and this found expression in, among other things, new architectural aims and aspirations
leading to more graceful forms.
The most suitable material was limestone.
In the mid-Swedish districts, Round Lakes, Väner and Vätter, of which you see a typical view here, and also in Gotland and Öland, there occurs stratified limestone, easy to quarry and dress.
Where this softer stone was available, architecture instinctively changed its style and became more refined.
It afforded the architect and the sculptor a splendid material, readily handled but not available in massive blocks, owing to the narrowness of the stratification.
Limestone thus proved an excellent medium for Gothic art in its striving after light and spacious forms, and facilitated the achievement of inimitable refinement and grace.
Vi hittar den här fina, gröna, blåa stenmaterialet som används för det finaste dekorativt arbete i många medievala kyrkor och kastler i de distrikterna.
Det var särskilt i Visby, på Götland, där kunskapen om det ornamentala behandlande av limestol uppnådde en hög grad av förhållande och refinering, som visar i den här bilden från rörelserna av St.
Katrins kyrka i Visby.
Här finns en gabelvall i Vardstena kastel.
En här är gator kallar kassel.
En bildning material när en stående stjärna bemänns impotens.
Mössligt för pavlens en steg.
Tänk strids softness.
Det kan bli kvar i dag.
Det är där jag kan jämföra med.
Brick är på porten på en kind av bildning material.
Så är det på Fertiles Kenyan Plains.
Läges om kläder.
Which remained there stratified after the great ice age had passed.
We find the same geological formation around the bays of Lake Mela.
And it is in these two districts that the Swedish brick industry is centered and has been centered for centuries.
Originally the clay was merely plastered in the interstices of a timber framework.
But builders gradually learned the art of burning bricks.
Medieval buildings are especially noteworthy for their beautiful bricks laid in interesting and artistic mural patterns.
Under barockperioden, men även senare, var det vanligt, i delen för att förbättra brickverket med motor.
Äntligen, mot slutet av 19-talet, var brickorna inte längre hämtade.
Maskinerade brickor var nu anpassade, men det var snart hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills
Här kommer jag att göra en digression.
Bildgivaren har kommit att förvänta sig spännande scener och spännande episoder i vackra lägenheter.
Sådant kan jag inte ge er.
Men vill ni i alla fall ha förmåga att följa mig på en liten rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl rejäl
As a historical development of Swedish culture and Swedish architecture in particular.
I'm bold enough to hope that as my tale unfolds, your interest will quicken.
Let us start far back in time.
We look for buildings, say, a couple of thousand years old.
Not one is left.
Only our graves give evidence of what once has been, simple but grand monuments of the past.
We seek in vain above ground, but below the surface our search is no longer fruitless.
Treasures of bronze and gold, exquisite ornaments testifying to a refined and independent craftsmanship have rewarded our excavators and enriched our museums.
It's in the State Historical Museum in Stockholm that the objects we are just showing you are preserved.
Look at these gold finds from about 400 AD.
They were found in a field in Västergötland, weighing 17 pounds and of pure gold.
Such are the relics of Swedish antiquity, revealed to us from out of the ground and bearing witness to a culture whose forms would otherwise have been unknown to us.
From the evidence of small fragments we must infer high achievement.
From the artistry and craftsmanship of the ancients we must infer their buildings.
That antiquity had its periods of greatness is eloquently evidenced by the graves.
The burial mounds rise majestically over the resting places of the kings at Uppsala, the royal capital of Sweden in ancient times.
Kristianiteten har med det tillgången från södra världen och användningen av stål i arkitekturen.
I Sigtiva, den idylliska lilla staden på Mälaren, hittar vi de finaste ruinerna av grimma, porträttslika kyrkor.
Deras tyngda dörrar och små, nära dörrar som ser ut som loopholes är evidens av den rastlösa, krigslika spelet av den tiden.
They themselves have suffered from those violent struggles.
They've been burnt and ravaged by enemies.
And now one wanders under the open sky where once the wax tapers gleamed beneath shadowy vaulted roofs.
How Christianity and paganism merge into each other is seen in Uppsala, once the royal city.
Under de röda bryllumarna, precis där den gamla Hedentempeln stod, stod det enkel och unödda vägg av en av de mest äldre kristna kyrkorna.
Det är i Munsö en typ av tidig, medieväldig cirkulär kyrka, som kanske har en ännu större respekt för en forträtt.
Belfry, av en längre tid, men som fortfarande har något av den monumentala massiviteten av den största byggnaden, står på en rock nära.
Den här gammal kyrkan från samma period hittar du i Skåne, i Skåne.
Vi är här nära Europa.
Mer enkelt jobbade material var tillgängliga och så blev stilen mindre påverklig.
En av de äldsta och mest noterbara svenska kyrkorna från slutet av 12-talet är Hysseby kyrkan i Västergötland.
Med sin otydliga tripartitiska stål.
Legend berättar.
Och den här memorialtablet visar att i brunnen vid Hjulsabyn, den stora Olof Skötkonung, den första kristna kringen i Sverige, blev baptiserad i 1008 av den engelska missionären Sigfrid.
En monasteri, byggandet av vilket marknade en ny era i historien om svensk arkitektur, finns på Alvastra i Östergötland.
Den var skapad av Cistercianer, franska människor som kom hit i mitten av 12-talet,
and introduced a simple yet refined architectural style.
Albuquerque was followed by many other Cistercian monasteries.
In Varnheim is found one whose chapel is still well preserved.
Its interior affords a splendid example of a fine, well-planned building in this style.
Of Varnheim Abbey itself, however, only some scanty ruins are left.
Here is the Abbey Church at Breta, in which services are still held for the local inhabitants.
Whereas in this case too, the actual monastery buildings lie in ruins.
Of the secular buildings dating from this period we note Stegeborg in Östergötland.
But above all, Glimmingerhus in Scania.
The only medieval castle in Scandinavia preserved in its original state.
More like a prison than a home.
The need for defense was paramount in those days.
and of comfort those very little.
Glimmingerhus is an isolated medieval monument.
In Visby we find a whole medieval town still extinct.
It is but a short night journey by steamer from Stockholm to Visby on the island of Gotland.
Yet it seems as if one had travelled south for at least a day and a half.
So astonishing is it to find oneself suddenly transported to this truly medieval environment which is certainly unique in Scandinavia.
Let me remind you that one of the great trade routes from the East, from Persia and Arabia, once passed via Gotland to Western Europe.
After Visby had joined the North German Hanseatic League, its political and economic influence rapidly increased until by the middle of the 13th century it was the wealthiest town of the North.
In the year 1361 the Danes, however, sacked it, but their ships founded just outside the harbour
And with them disappeared their magnificent booty.
Just recently there have been rumors that some enterprising Swedes and Americans have formed a company to locate and recover the sunken treasure.
Since the 14th century Visby has gradually declined to what it is now.
A peaceful, unpretentious little provincial town.
But a tourist resort and a seaside place of remarkable interest.
In many places in the rural districts of Sweden, the sights here from his car or railway carriage will suddenly come upon some fine specimen of an old church from this time, the latter part of the Middle Ages, which, here in the north at least, was characterized by fertile and lively imaginations.
So strong was the Catholic Church as a unifying force that it brought the north closer to the south than it had ever been.
Under den här åldern har Norrland adopterat i sin nationella liv, i sin tröja och i sina kunskaper, en märklig kraft och diversitet av färger.
Det ser man särskilt i malerierna som använder interiören av många svenska kyrkor från dessa dagar.
Daterat från samma period är kathedraren i Uppsala.
And that at Lund.
Both unfortunately partly vandalized by the restorer.
With the coming of Gustavus Vasa, founder of the modern Swedish kingdom at the beginning of the 16th century, a new architectural era set in.
Here you see the king as Millers has conceived him in the Nordiska museum.
A strong, dominating, commanding personality.
Gustavus Vasa's struggle for the unification of Sweden was a hard-won fight.
Kulturella värdena och kunskaperna var förstörda, men som resultat var landet återbyggt på en ny foundation.
Den starka kraften av monarkin pratar till oss idag i de många kastler som Gustavus Vasa byggde och som hans soner utnyttjade och använde.
De här mäktiga byggnaderna, exempel på vilka ni ser här, stannar som jäklar, omvandlade av de låga, blåa ställningarna av folket.
Maybe the castles look a little aged and decayed, but they have generally escaped the worst of all dangers, the vandalism of the restorer.
So they are preserved to us as living examples of the medieval builders art, full of beauty and historical interest.
And they are indissolubly associated with the history of Swedish architecture.
Gustavus Vassas sons, notably Johan III, continued to carry on these building activities.
för att utveckla den nationella arkitekturen till en purare och högre kunskap som kräver symmetri, arrangement och refinering.
Och i det hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills hittills The power of the king and the strength of the peasants were the cornerstones of the Swedish realm.
You've seen where kings lived.
Their dwellings are stronger and more imposing than those of the peasantry, and therefore catch the attention.
But the peasants' homes, though humbler and of simpler construction, testify to pride and independence.
In their way, they are perhaps still more independent and interesting, for here we find no foreign influences.
Look at these types in the Zorn collection at Mora and at Skansen, Stockholm.
Nothing suggests a passing fashion.
Everything is truly original and unique.
Deeply rooted in the soil.
Gustavus Vasa began as a peasant king.
But he was actually of noble birth.
And he ended as patron and protector of the nobility.
Under hans soner växte denna nobilitet i kraft och inflytande.
Särskilt under hans äldsta son Erik XIV.
Han ledde en liv som romantisk, rådlös och olycklig.
Som alla Shakespearean krigskingar.
Han växte Elisabeth av England och Mary Stuart av Skottland.
Och senast bjöd hon en liten liten blåskålare.
Erik skapade våra första kunder och gav dem territorier som var stora och rika.
Where they reigned like petty kings from their mighty castles.
Of which some, like Visingsborg in Lake Vettern, now lie in ruins.
While others, like Lecker in Lake Vänern, still are well preserved.
The nobles came to the fullness of their power with the walls of Gustavus Adolphus in Germany, and more especially after his death, when the generals largely took matters into their own hands.
Returning home victorious and with booty amassed during the Thirty Years' War, indeed not only with newly won riches, but also with newly acquired habits, pretensions and vices.
They behaved like nouveau riche of any age.
And the castles they built themselves were significant of their true mentality and their taste.
But nevertheless they have left us priceless treasures.
Det här är särskilt sant när det gäller Kung Kloster, som ni ser här.
Det är fint utbyggt på en bay av Lake Mera.
Hans kollektion av armar och armor är den största privata i världen, medan fönstret och tapestrarna under luften är otroligt fina.
Det typiska av de aristokratiska byggnaderna i Stockholm från denna tid är Bundapalacet.
De flesta av de magnifiska husen av nobiliteten stod på eller nära Riddaholmen, där de stod och tittade över öppna vatten.
and the thinly inhabited environs.
The contrast must have been tremendous.
The pictures we show here of what is left of the ancient timber houses in Stockholm ideals embedded in lilacs and roses give us some idea of the modest dimensions of the dwellings of the poorer classes.
The nobility of the 17th century raised an exquisite monument to their own greatness in the Riddahus, the house of the nobility in Stockholm.
A noble and well-proportioned building showing Dutch influence.
Vi återigen går ner till Skåne, som efter att vara en dansk provins blev en del av Sverige mot mitten av 17-talet.
Renässansstyrelsen har förändrats och tog form tidigare.
I 16-talet hade den danska nobiliteten redan börjat bygga sina fina kastler, främst av bråk.
Sådär, de berättar ungefär 100 år tidigare än de aristokratiska kastlerna i Sverige.
Situerade mitt i glada skogar och omvandlade av mjölk har de den mest fredliga utmaningen idag, trots att de var originalt byggda för skydd.
In a chronological account, this is the right place to introduce Drottningholm, the best known of all the royal summer residences in Sweden.
In order to replenish the emptied national treasury, King Charles XI forced the nobles to restore to the crown the estates they had received as feats during the previous century.
The king's power was absolute from now on, unchecked even by the feudal lords.
Drottningholm var byggt av Tessin, medan Stokholms röda palats var byggt av hans son Tessin the Younger, Sveriges största arkitekt.
Hans och hans faders tillgång till svensk arkitektur kan aldrig vara överestimerad.
The Royal Palace is the younger Tessin's immortal masterpiece.
He designed palaces not only in Sweden but also for the Danish court and even made a splendid design for the Louvre in Paris at the bidding of Louis XIV.
The residence of the Lord Mayor of Stockholm, a palace built for Tessin himself, in which the original structure
ornamentation, wall paintings and to a certain extent also the furniture have been well preserved until our own days is an exquisite example of the younger Tessin's art.
His aim was to revive the severe and monumental style of the Roman Renaissance and he was strongly opposed to that cockatry and flashy seeking after effect which marked his own age.
I provinserna också, särskilt i Karlskrona, hittar vi skador av Tessins arkitektur och klassisk stil.
Karlskrona i Blekinge var byggt under den här perioden vid krigskommanden som en ny navbas för landet.
I sin navlade dockgård minns du fortfarande av den gloria, tråkiga perioden när Sverige var en stor kraft.
Så gör också Ryddeholmskyrkan, Swedens pantheon.
Där i rullar av sepulchrar är beredda medlemmar av den stolta nobiliteten som ledde landet genom de stora och stormliga tiderna av nästan kontinuerlig krig.
The most beautiful and the most affecting of these resting places is the Carolinian mortuary chapel.
Constituting one great monumental piece of sculpture.
An inspired work by Tessin the Younger.
Here rests Charles XII in peace after life.
which had never known peace.
The bullet that ended his life in 1718 ended at the same time a period of unparalleled expansion which for a sparsely inhabited northern country like ours was almost supernatural and which was reached only after enormous hardships and sacrifices.
One door had closed against the outer world.
Men samtidigt öppnas en annan dörr till den fysiska världen av hem.
Den senaste åldern har inga märkliga uppfattningar som kan konkurrera med de senaste åldern.
Men det beror på utvecklingen och refineringen av det svenska hemmet.
Det är under den här perioden att den typiska svenska manorhusen tog form.
Det ofta beskrivna typen av byggnad som har varit hemma i landets kultur och som, trots att den nu dör ut, är speciellt karaktäristisk för landet till den dag.
Här är franska kulturen och avståndet kombinerat med norrländsk kultur och en tydlighet för att skapa en singulärt attraktiv hem.
I intresset har den lyckliga mellannisen av rock och kål förbjudit den formella skönheten av barock.
Det är däremot inte en floridisk extravagant rock och kål, utan en stil som lämnar en diskret och hemlig atmosfär av en märklig norrländsk karaktär.
Horticulturen uppstår under franska inflytande.
80-talet bevisar börsen av marknads- och industrism.
No longer do victorious armies bring home rich booty from their foreign campaigns.
It is now for Sweden to strive within her own borders to restore the nation's wealth and happiness with the aid of invention and organization.
Industrial enterprises, notably the ironworks, whose production in the past mostly served warlike purposes,
har nu att göra plån och verktyg i servicen för frihet.
Munitionsfaktorerna blev järnverk som snart var bestämda för att göra svensk järnindustrin berömd överallt i Europa.
Och hans utveckling och produktion tillbaka till slutet av 19-talet följer främst traditionerna och metoderna som lades ner under den perioden.
Ionverket är en del av svensk arkitekturs historia.
I smittor, blastfönisker och ionporten– –är arkitekterna så pekulära och märkliga för ingenjörskap– –som karaktäriserar industrialismens tid i Sverige.
Wherever waterfalls can supply power, often in the midst of vast forests, flourishing communities grow up, planned with the engineers love of order and system, built in simple yet noble taste, often embellished with decorative work produced locally.
They are patriarchal communities over which the manor rules, like the castle in the small German principalities.
De här grupperna och grupperna är skattade runt centrala Sverige i en område som kallas Bergslagen.
De är centrum för inte bara industrin utan också intellektuell kultur.
Och inom det här området har litteratur, forskning och kunskap sprungit upp.
Vi har sagt att en dörr hade blivit öppna mot den utre världen.
Men att världsfrågan öppnade en annan dörr som öppnade större visor.
Europe establishes lively trade with the far east, notably with that ancient civilized but hitherto inaccessible country, China.
The Chinese element lends color to rococo art and Chinese style becomes the fashion of the day.
As a pleasant surprise to the queen, the king embellished Doffingholm with a complete miniature palace called China.
Rigen av Gustav III, kungen som primära representerar svensk kultur i Sverige, släpper en epok i historien av svensk kultur, och på samma tid introducerar en annan.
Gustavins stil är särskilt märklig för sin gräns och refinering.
Gustav III älskar teatern.
Och i teatern som han byggde i Drottningholm har vi bevis för det.
Han var själv en amatörsaktör och spelare.
I den rädda spelet som han var så gillade han att flytta snabbt från en kastel till en annan.
Varje gång han gick så ville han se spel och själv ta del av deras performance.
Det var därför han byggde sådana här teater vid sina olika sommarresidenser.
I tillväxt till den stora operahuset i Stockholm.
Teatern i Drottningholm är extremt väl preserverad.
Scenariet, kostymerna och allt annat.
Och den har tidigare blivit mest försvunnen.
Det är ett extraordinärt levande, karaktäriskt och skönt monument- från den lyckliga, attraktiva och högt kulturerade åldern.
Det var också en period av dramatisk intensitet- som var den tidigare perioden av Sveriges storlek.
Men det var inte längre en heroisk spektakl, utan en artistisk drama-
A maze of intrigue, a bold and mischievous comedy, which however turned to tragedy when Gustavus III fell a victim to an assassins bullet at a masquerade ball in the Stockholm Opera House.
The pictures of small towns which will be shown next are typical of the period which followed.
The bourgeois period in the beginning of the 19th century.
During the unhappy reign of Gustavus III's son and successor, the country's role as a great power was ended definitely.
In a war with Russia, Sweden lost Finland and thereby a third of her territory.
Henceforth she must lead a quiet life in her own unimportant little corner of Europe.
There is no monumental grandness in the buildings of this time, but there is warmth, peacefulness, coziness and romance everywhere.
What happens during the succeeding century?
Not mere progress in the art of building, but a worldwide technical revolution.
Let us take a leap across that century from the days of our grandfather to our own age and see what technical progress Sweden has made.
We have certainly not attained that enormous expansion that we find in the United States.
But we have at any rate reached a stage in the evolution of our architecture quite unlike anything our forefathers ever dreamt of.
Perhaps we have not yet fully realized the consequence of this development and how it has revolutionized everything.
Harnessing the waterfalls and transplanting their might to great distances to light our communities and to set in motion thousands of tons of machinery.
Many of our railways too are electrified.
The railways, in Sweden at least,
play a quite unassuming and unsensational role as a revolutionizing phenomenon.
Most of our railways have long since merged themselves into the landscape, almost become an intrinsic part of it, and a not unattractive part.
With growing consciousness and with a deep sense of responsibility for the preservation of natural and cultural values, the Swedish state railway authorities have endeavored in their own field of architectural design to preserve the association of national traditions.
Both on the trains and in the station buildings is to be seen that love of neatness and attention to detail, which forms one of the best features of Swedish constructional work.
sådant som det är med på stålbågarna som kopplar stålbågarna till skandinaviska grupper och kontinenten.
Storlekskollegiumet i Stockholm är ett av de byggnader i den tid som är uttryckliga för skönheten av deras material och deras monumentala rättigheter.
This is also true of the new headquarters of the patent office.
The ideal sought after in this modern architecture is the line and simple mural surface characteristic of the Middle Ages.
It specializes in the designing of private houses, particularly of villas for the wealthier middle class.
But in Gothenburg, where these pictures are taken, and in Stockholm, as seen here, entire blocks are composed of these private dwelling houses, mostly constructed in brick of that attractive handmade type to which the architects of this period are so partial.
Ekklesiastisk arkitektur har glömt den stereotypiska imiteringen av gotik- och har återvunnit till independens, originalitet och individualitet.
Den viktigaste monumentala arbetet som skapats under den här epoken- är Stockholm City Hall, en av de bäst kända byggnaderna av vår tid.
Situerat i en excepterande, vackert position på Mälaren, står det i all sin vänniska brytelse och gräns, en blandning av slända och finskapade former.
Mellan bygget och vattnet ligger den lyckliga terrestren, en rolig plats och en veritabla solskatt.
Bakom en arkad ligger den inre kvartalen.
Det är en mer seriös design, liknande de manoriala byggnaderna av Vasa-perioden.
Interiören stryker en not av stark individualitet och visar en mängd varier i design.
It may justly be claimed that this city hall gives to the whole town and to its public life a more festive atmosphere and it has certainly contributed towards making Stockholm a greater attraction than ever to tourists.
In every sphere of architecture this national style has sought to lend a more intimate and personal touch to its creations.
Även till så komparativt prosaiska typer av byggnader som sjukhus, skolor och så vidare.
Dessutom promoterar man en stark estetisk tendens.
Snart kom det en reaktion mot detta, ibland excessivt romantisk individualism.
A reaction against attempts at a medieval liberty of form followed by striving after classical prototypes.
The style however is still strongly individual and its flexibility is apparent.
For instance in its successful adaptation even to modern office buildings.
This classicism tends towards a severer modernism on cubist lines in the Stockholm City Library.
Later on we shall see how under foreign influence this modernism soon begins to carry all before it.
But we propose first to show some further views of the two largest towns in Sweden in order to give a more vivid conception of the intermingling of the old and the new in Swedish architecture.
Guarded since of old by Fort Ellsborg, Gothenburg lies on the banks of the river Göta Älv.
Here is the view that meets you on entering the harbor from the west.
The dominating feature is Maastricht, a fine church representative of the national architecture of the 19th century.
Dessutom är det ett nytt museum av maritim historia som är på väg till konstruktion och som till den här tiden praktiskt har kommit till slut.
Som gamla tyska städer har Gottenberg redan haft en system av kanaler som rör sig runt de principala gatorna.
Här står det fina huset av East India Company, ett monument till den gamla tidsskiftningen.
Under 19-talet har Gottenberg hållit ett briskt kommersiellt samarbete med England.
Och detta faktum har haft en stark inflytelse på sin karaktär.
Vi ser detta, bland annat, i de breda trädgjorda vägarna som påverkar staden, och i den vackra stadsparken, Tregårdsföreningen, som är utbyggd efter den engelska patternen.
Stockholm is to a certain extent a lagoon city, built on islets and peninsulas.
Like Venice, it is reached by a long railway bridge spanning the waterways.
The peninsulas around Stockholm are high and rocky, so that at first the train bears you at a height above the water.
It then runs through a tunnel on a steep downgrade until it emerges right in the center of the town.
Now, however, crossing the water on a low-level bridge.
Det centrala staden är fortfarande samma byggnad som stod här när rådgivningen var först inaugurerad.
Men den har senare blivit frekvent utställd.
Gustav Hallås torg, staden med operahuset och Arl Furstens palats, en gång palatsen i vägen, presumtivt på andra sidan, och Royal Palace på slutet av Norrbro bridge har i århundratals varit centrum i staden.
Den sista residenterna var till och med, och är fortfarande i pass, Keyside Avenue, kallad Strandvägen.
Hållet här är från 1890-talet och början av den här åldern.
Här står Nyderska museet, som håller på med etnologiska museer.
Utifrån området hittar vi byggnader av en mer modern, enkel och komfortabel typ.
Även byggnaderna av de mindre klasserna är lyckliga och tydligt hållbara med övriga övriga områden.
In the western parts of the city there has recently come into being along the shore of Lake Mela a counterpart of the Strandvägen quarter called Norr Mela Strand.
Here the aim has been to secure some degree of uniformity in the design of the buildings facing the water.
But there is a rich variety of details.
At the same time around the city proper are growing up a number of garden cities on the English and American models.
med tillgångar till övriga liv utanför staden, oavsett om det är i en simplare eller mer luxuerad stil.
Vi har nu kommit till det sista nivån i vår egen decennium, 1930-talet, vilket definitivt marknaderar tillväxten av en ny era och en ny arkitektur.
Här ser vi utställningen i Stockholm i 1930-talet, som visade sig vara en manifestation av den här nya era, och som i många sätt visade sig vara ett epokskapande event.
Även i Sverige håller vi på med de gamla metoderna, och de här förhållandena måste se ut som miniaturer jämfört med de i USA.
Men även i Sverige är en snabb förändring uppgörande från handikraft till stor del av industrin.
Vi har redan uttryckt den gamla åldern av det svenska järnverket.
They have now expanded into large establishments, famous for the excellent quality of their products.
En väg till manufaktur för det bildning.
Out of the stjärn framgången med just den modern gothisk stjärn av arkitektur gottisk, not in form, but in construction.
En annan exempel av det same development is provided by the timber industry, the backbone of Sweden's export and commerce, som händelser för all over the country.
Men särskilt koncentrerade runt rätten Malmö i norra Sverige.
Vi har sett tidigare hur loggarna flyttade runt rätten.
Ibland hundratals och hundratals mil.
Här har de nått sin destination.
Och här är de förändrade till en kommersiell produkt.
Och stående i stora lombyar i porten, redo för skiftning.
Och nu ska vi se hur masonit utgörs.
Som ni vet är det ett annat produkt av skogen.
Rakt material är samma som pulk.
Men behandlingen av fibrerna är annorlunda.
Masonitet är en av de byggmaterial som har utvecklats de senaste flera decennierna och som gör det möjligt att skapa mer enkla och effektiva metoder för konstruktion.
En annan område där maskiner är som manualt arbete är det som man kan kalla för redo att bära hus.
Särskilda delar av byggandet är konstruerade i fabriken och tack vare den extensiva standardiseringen av delar så kan arbetet med att samla dem vara väldigt simplifierat.
I en enda dag kan djur och väggar samlas ihop för att göra de små djurna.
Vår val är avgörande av Stockholms stadsplaneringsförbund.
När vi såg i morgonen var det en foundation som var uppe på grunden.
I morgonen var det småning från en kompletterad hus.
En hus som externt ser ut som en kottage av den ordinarie, old-fashioned kind.
Men som i sin konstruktion och sin karaktär som en standardartikel är en typisk modern industriell produkt.
Här och där kommer man över bygghus och affärer som med deras glas och stål visar det ultimata målet mot vilket vi strider.
Denna objektiv, modern arkitektur, är ännu mer patent och naturligt anpassad till de former som är i sig en expression av vår tid.
Som fabriker, siloer, miller och depositorer.
Just as formerly in the childhood of industrialism the monumental style of architecture lent its forms to the industrial type of building.
So it is now rather the industrial building the typical architectural problem of our times that imposes its character even on forms employed in other spheres.
Here our story ends.
We have reached our own time and do not intend to pose as prophets.
We've seen how the Swedish art of building has grown by a slow, sure and continuous process of evolution.
We now take our leave of it and of Sweden.
Between the jolly looking white steamers that fly the Stockholm waterways.
Right up into the very heart of the town.
We glide out into more open water.
Around us, on their dark foundations of primitive rock, stand bright-hued buildings mirrored in the wide channels.
The bay is spanned by the spacious lofty arches of a modern concrete bridge.
While graceful sailing boats careen before the fresh breeze.
The typical Swedish coastal scenery is with us right out to the open sea.
Swedish culture accompanies us just a little further.
For it is on a Swedish vessel, the beautiful Kungsholm, that we leave the old country.