Välkomna!
Vår tillgänglighet på Ginebras dörr.
Vår kärlek!
Vår stil!
Vårt soldatmål!
Nu närmar sig tiden... ...då vi måste välja i den här dilemman.
Innan eller utanför?
Innan!
Förri!
Echo!
I tre decennier har amerikanska krigsskap betrott kinesiska vatten.
Under den främsta östernas konflikt har de varit i bombdangerzonen.
Gunnvattnet Penai har blivit sökt av japiska flygplaner.
95 av hennes och tre andra amerikanska skapare, som bombade nära Nanking, har blivit misslyckade.
I Washington ger statssekreteraren Hull presidentens protester och hans behov av full nöjdhet till ambassadör Saito, som ställer på Japans skrämmor.
Det japanska regeringen och folk vill uttrycka deras sinceraste och profondaste skrämmor till det amerikanska regeringen och folk på grund av den här skrämmande incidenten.
Senatör Robert Reynolds uttrycker sig som en räddande amerikansk.
Runt en tid sen var en av våra krigsbåtar sömnade i kinesiska vatten.
Det japanska regeringen förlåter.
Så länge vi håller våra krigsbåtar i kinesiska vatten, så länge vi håller marinerna på kinesiska gränser, så har vi möjlighet att ha problem där.
Vi vill inte ha problem.
Om en annan krigsbåtar är sömnad, eller om några mariner är döda, så har vi någon annan förlåt?
Men om vi inte gör det så kommer vi att ha krig.
Jag vill inte ha krig.
Ni vill inte ha krig.
Ingen av oss vill ha krig.
Låt oss hålla av med krig genom att avslöja våra mariner från kinesisk jord och avslöja våra krigsbåtar från orientala asiatiska vatten.
Den här trädgården ser ut att vara i område, så stäng den, cowboy, och håll på!
Sattlarna ser inte ut att göra någon skillnad.
Det är bara så svårt att hålla på.
Den här cowboyen får en rörelse och en sväng samtidigt.
Men han släpper säsongen med ett bang!
...by showing you a man, a gorilla and an elephant.
The three stages of evolution.
From ape to man being the subject of this talk.
Though only a few men look like elephants, their bony structures are surprisingly alike.
The principal difference lies in their heads.
Some are thick, some are thicker.
The man's, gorilla's and elephant's limbs are alike in general form.
They differ only in length and thickness.
Notice the gorilla's arms, the man's and the elephant's.
The leg movements are similar.
The man's
The gorillas and the elephants.
Next the arm movements.
The man's, the gorillas and the elephants.
Now we see with a very few changes the elephant's skeleton is transformed into the gorillas.
Note the elephant's tusks, ivory, receding into the head.
Showing the early beginning of the heads of many modern men and congressmen.
Solid ivory.
Next we show you there is still less change from gorilla to man.
Där.
Där är du.
Det visar varför det är så lätt för så många av oss att göra munkar av oss själva.
Och nu kan du förstå varför vi ser många nära gorillor på bathingbeach.
Här är två skallar.
Skallar, jag menar.
Männen är rundade på toppen, bussar slåpande och fulla i hår.
Denna laddartype pratar utan att tänka och är hittad på de flesta backseat-drivare och på bränslepartier.
Men med lite förändring så är det som männen.
Not the bridge by the skull.
Next we see that nature has developed the man's skeleton so it has a graceful carriage.
The man's straight, the gorilla not so straight, and the elephant not as well dressed as our mere whimmy joker or fogless darebanks.
I mean, dareless fogbanks.
I mean... Here are two souls with but a single thought.
Eating bananas.
The song, yes, we have no bananas, doesn't go here.
But they might sing the star strangle bandana.
They're friendly, you see.
Yves knows that a friend in need knows its own father.
A banana in the hand is a friend indeed.
No, no.
The early banana catches the worm.
No, I mean a rolling banana gathers no moss.
Oh well, you know what I mean.
Here is the latest example of evolution.
The lordly proprietor of a speakeasy.
And here is the barkeeper, down cellar, sneaking a little drink for himself.
...a bottle with him.
The proprietor is going to put up a fight.
He's got something in the drawer that will bounce nicely.
It's a hammer.
They bounce nicely off heads.
Very well then.
What carpenter can put a screw into a board with a screwdriver any better than he?
I tell you, he proves the theory of evolution.
There.
Now see him use his thumb and forefinger just like a man.
And he watches a clock.
Just like I remind you, your old little child.
Here he is, as a housewife.
A new balloon sweeps clean.
No, no, a new baboon.
No, a new broom sweeps clean.
And now for a smoke.
First, let's have a match.
Ah, there's one.
And see him close the box.
När det bär regns, går kvar ett litet och det är bara en familj kan dock sätta sig tillbaka.
Det går kamligen av hals.
It's making way for the other.
Not the contrast between the pigs and humans.
Vad poes, vad Dignity.
Det är lite hoppfulls, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev, hev.
But don't put your face in your rice.
Put your rice in your face.
If you're lucky, chopsticks may help get it there as we see here.
Olives may be found at your neighbor's place.
This animal has been properly brought up.
He enjoys shredded wheat.
But his keeper says naughty naughty for taking such a big mouthful.
Your waiter or butler can aid you in expelling any food that may not agree with you.
Never open your mouth too wide.
You might be mistaken for a subway entrance.
If you are a night owl and luncheon is announced, do not stare and do not say, When do we eat?
And using an eyedropper as a wet nurse will prevent the infant from choking.
As we see here.
An orange swallowed whole in this manner will push the meal down the esophagus into the stomach and help keep it there in case the meal doesn't agree with you.