Välkomna!
Hej då!
Ja.
Jag kommer aldrig igen.
The lesson is from the first book of Kings, chapter 5.
And behold, I purpose to build an house under the name of the Lord my God, that the Father spake unto David my God, saying, My son, whom I will set upon thy throne in thy womb, he shall build an house under my name.
And the king commanded and they brought great stones, costly stones and huge stones to lay the foundation of the house.
Nisi dovidus edificaveritum.
In vamma mamma deo, fie edificad reo.
Nisi dovidus custodierit civitatum.
Frustra mig till att vi kustar in er.
Vad om vi är svåra att se ljuset sången?
Vad om vi måste anställa er till att vi skadar oss för er?
Du delar inte mig, visst, du är så god.
Värd dig, herre, värd dig, jag skapar dig för mig.
Värd dig, frukt, frukt, värd dig för mig.
Sigur salliter i vallopågärning, sigar bibliet ur sovnum, deatros virvim pläget eviterium summe sipsi.
Along sheer walls and high stone cliffs, a steep and winding roadway has been blasted into the mountaintop.
Here is a natural testing ground, and water testing ground.
It took the first man who climbed the peak two days to reach the top.
Today it takes the average motorist an hour.
And they're off!
Hammett is over the mark first.
Closely followed by Cimino.
And then by Schultz.
The course is lined on every side with spectators attracted by the promise of thrills galore.
As they scale the heights.
Schultz takes the lead.
Closely followed by Cimino.
Oh, look at those boys dig in on the turn.
And how those V8s hug the roads.
You know, most of the races run in second or low gear, with motors turning as fast as 4200 revolutions a minute.
At times, the cars reach a speed of 60 miles an hour.
The skilled drivers shift gears at the turn from second to low speed without lifting a foot off the accelerator.
Every minute, every step of the way is a searching test for engine, car and driver.
It takes plenty of skill and plenty of nerve to keep the accelerator on the floorboard.
Stems straighten out after the hairpin turns and pull up a grade that keeps the driver looking straight through the windshield at blue sky.
The course follows a route 12 miles and 2200 feet long.
The finish line is more than 5000 feet higher than the starting point.
Det här är testet för carburatör och koldioxidsystem.
Tänk dig att röra ditt bil i full trottel på 12 mil.
Följa varje steg av vägen i tredje eller låga styrkor.
På höga nivåer växer vatten mer snabbt.
Och ännu inte några av dessa Ford hade problem med överhållning.
Det här är en reserv i temperatur och kontroll som tillverkar att när man rör sig, rör sig mer än 4200 gånger per minut, enligt Takamata Rekord.
Och det är verkligen rörande.
Boss Hammond, youngest of the three drivers of the Ford V8, finished first.
Covering the course in 19 minutes, 25 and 7, the driver sees snow on rocks and the roadway.
And once again, the Ford V8 demonstrates its speed, stamina and power.
Hammond!
Hammond is the winner!
And not far behind him is Cimino.
And bringing up the rear, only because he went off the road onto the rocks to avoid hitting a spectator, Schultz, nine times winner of the climb, comes in last.
But still well ahead of the 1933 record.
The three drivers parade their mounts in front of the observation tower as a gesture of triumph over Old Man Mountain.
No wonder they are proud of themselves and their cars.
Oh, it was a great race.
Ah, the victors smile.
And here are the fruits of victory in the shape of a huge silver cup offered by Spencer Penrose.
The cup becomes the property of the 1934 winner until some faster car comes along.
And when that day comes, we are ready to venture the prediction that it will be another Ford V8.
Still the fastest, finest and most dependable...