THE EXPEDITION ON THE WAY	THROUGH THE OPEN SAVANNA-W0OODS	NEAR COLEMAN RIVER,		CAPE YORK PENINSULA,
WOMEN AND CHILDREN ON THEIR	DAILY SEARCH FOR EATABLE	FRUITS AND ROOTS
DIGGING UP DIOSCORAEA-ROOTS.
PREPARING ”KAROL”, THE UNDER-	GROUND PARTS OF DIOSCORAEA	SATIVA, POISONOUS BY NATURE	THEY ARE MADE EATABLE BY	ROASTING, CRUSHING AND	THOROUGH WASHING.
AFTER MANY HOURS OF WORK THE	KAROL IS POURED OUT ON THE		GROUND FOR DRYING. WHEN READY		IT REMINDS OF MASHED POTATOES	AS TO TASTE AND APPEARENCE.
MEN ON THEIR DAILY HUNT,	FIRST OF ALL FOR OPOSSUMS IN |	ME rg
HOW NAMBO, THE PROUDEST MAN OF	HIS TRIBE, HANDLES HIS SPEAR.	THIS IS LAUNCHED BY MEANS OF		A SPECIAL "PIECE OF WOOD.
A BLACK CATCHING AN OPOSSUM.
DIFFERENT WAYS OF CLIMBING.
NATIVE ROWER ON	HIS DUG-OUT BOAT.
AC BLACK PREPARING HIS MEAL i		CONSISTING OF A NEWLY KILLED	CARPET- SNAKE. FIRE IS MADE BY	RUBBING TWO WOODEN STICKS	TOGETHER; THEY GIVE A GLOWING	POWDER WHICH IS ENCLOSED IN	Ne TRE V SSA		SA UNTIL FLAMING UP		El
j =		 	  	  		THE SNAKE IS GRILLED, CUT UU	BY MEANS OF A SHIVER OF STON	00000: (TENN 17.
BUSH-FIRE GOT UP BY THE	BLACKS TO ALARM THE GAME.	(01 RT	AGAINST THE FLAMES	BY THE THICK BARK.		ord
WOMEN SINGING AT THE FIRE;		16
KORROBBORI- DANCE IN COMPLETE	WAR-PAINT, THE HEADS ADORNED	WITH WHITE PARROT-FEATHERS,
BEFORE THE FIGHT THE	COURAGE IS STIMULATED	BY THROWING SPEARS
SMOKING THE PEACE-PIPE.	FOR REASON OF ECONOMY THE	TWO CONTRAHENTS ENJOY	THE SAME SMOKE BY MEANS	[UN ENE: L TE NR
FROM ANIMAL LIFE:	OPOSSUMS		Kl
POUCHED SOUIRRELS
HAT EUUTD	KAR TRUE RANE: Ci
MOTHER WITH A YOUNG IN HER		POUCH. WHEN SHE STOOPS DOWN		TO FEED THE YOUNG TOO TAKES	A MOUTHFULL OF GRASS.		23
LYCKAS AT LE
Ko		ON THE FLIGHT
WOMEN AND CHILDREN ON THEIR	DAILY SEARCH FOR EATABLE	FRUITS AND ROOTS
DIGGING UP DIOSCORAEA-ROOTS.
Lo NR		PREPARING ”KAROL' THE UNDER-	GROUND PARTS OF DIOSCORAEA	SATIVA. POISONOUS BY NATURE	THEY ARE MADE EATABLE BY	ROASTING, CRUSHING AND	THOROUGH WASHING.
AFTER MANY HOURS OF WORK THE	KAROL IS POURED OUT ON THE	GROUND FOR DRYING. WHEN READY	IT REMINDS OF MASHED POTATOES	AS TO TASTE AND APPEARENCE,		 		[.
HOW NAMBO, THE PROUDEST MAN OF	HIS TRIBE, HANDLES HIS SPEAR.	THIS IS LAUNCHED BY MEANS OF		A SPECIAL "PIECE OF WOOD.