Views taken from H.M.S.	"Broke,” flying the flag of	Admiral Sir Reginald Bacon,		on her way to Zeebrugge.
Observed by		German Seaplanes.
5.30 a.m.	Destroyers taking up		   		fal Stel Ta lictd.g
At		H.M.S. Swift.”	RELEASE	Semaphore of H.M.S.	35		Ar
On the look-out, steaming	towards Zeebrugge,		under fire.
KITTS AS AST TT		Range and effect of fire.
Motor Launch Boats	(GU CEO	FRU NTTJ lst	open fire.
INSETT ISEN	laying mine nets, during	which operation they are	covered by Destroyers.
A Destroyer making a		Smoke screen to cover		operations.
What a Monitor is like.	Changing position.	Destroyers and Drifters	MEn
Different types of		  		Monitor.
NERV DNA		EET
Steaming back to	Dunkirk.	Inside the Minefields.
Å busy time on the		Bridge during the		operations.
ONT:		BEE
NEG		InJe tas Netti ER
FR EGRETA	In the Wake of H.M.S.	3
Dropping Anchor at	Dunkirk.
The Admirals leave for	KJ :TT RT	attempted - Something	Ir