Här kommer bräden.
Hon åker till staden för att hålla den viktigaste anställningen i livet.
Jag känner svårt att göra rätt till den här historien.
Det är en storie om atmosfären, inte ord.
En storie som är bättre berättad genom känsla och insikt.
by the ancient majesty of the stone of historic Westminster Abbey.
Better told by the heartbeats of a nation quickened by its affection and loyalty to the reigning house.
Best of all told by hearing the ceremony itself spoken before the altar in front of which will kneel the royally loved royal lovers.
By the courtesy of the British Broadcasting Corporation is permitted to reproduce a part of this reverently thrilling ceremony.
It is a tale which has moved humanity from time immemorial.
George Edward Alexander Edmund, wilt thou have this woman to thy wedded wife to live together after God's ordinance in the holiest state of matrimony?
Wilt thou love her, comfort her, honor and keep her in sickness and in health and forsaking all other
Keep me only unto her so long as ye both shall live.
Marina, wilt thou have this man to thy wedded husband to live together after God's ordinance in the holy estate of matrimony?
Wilt thou obey him and serve him, love, honor and keep him in sickness and in health and forsaking all other
Keep thee only unto him, so long as ye both shall live.
I George Edward Alexander Edmund I George Edward Alexander Edmund Take thee Marina to my wedded wife Take thee Marina to my wedded wife To have and to hold To have and to hold From this day forward From this day forward For better, for worse For better, for worse For richer, for poorer For richer, for poorer In sickness and in health In sickness and in health To love and to cherish
To love and cherish Till death us do part Till death us do part According to God's holy ordinance According to God's holy ordinance And thereto I plight thee my throne And thereto I plight thee my throne I, Marina I, Marina Take thee, George Edward Alexander Edmund Take thee, George Edward Alexander Edmund To my wedded husband
Det här är det här.
I this ring I thee wed.
With my body I thee worship.
And with all my worldly goods I thee endow.
In the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Ghost.
Amen.
Det är den första gången i världens historia att praktiskt hela sin omgivning har kunnat vara med som en stor kongregation i sådant här service.
Duke of Kent och hans duchess, som några minuter sedan var prinsess Marina, åker bort från byn och åker tillbaka till Buckingham Palace.
och där födelsedagen, enligt de grekiska kyrkorna, ska hållas.
Välkomna från en miljon hundar följer prognosen i en raktorisk krescenda.
Och med hjälp av denna kraftiga människa, kräver duke Kent hans bröder.
Namnet Marina har varit på alla händer sedan födelsedagen blev uppskattad.
Nu, av älskande för deras rörelse, är det i alla hjärta.
Vår nya duchess charme har gått runt landet och hittat hälsor i huset.
Vår vikten har varit spontan.
Mästkriget vid fjällbalken rör sig igen för att ta med dem en tydligare bild av hennes rörelse.
Rörelserna skrattar med glädje och lång liv till duken och duchess Kemp.