Frågorna är blöda.
De gloria japanska blåsumarna brinner fram i regal skärm.
I en utsiktlig utställning vid gatorna hittar man tegränser som stiger så långt som ögonen kan se.
Troligen, Japan is the land of tea.
Japan tea is the king of vitamin C. Thus science has named its favored child of nature.
Världens.
Riktiga.
The young Pili is picked by the dainty hands of Japanese maidens.
Arboretum var det var det var det var det var det var det
In the production of green tea, the fresh leaves are first steamed.
This prevents fermentation and at the same time ensures the purity of the leaves by automatic sterilization.
They are next rolled while being dried.
That green tea has an abundance of vitamin C is due to the steaming process.
The oxidized enzymes in the fresh leaves are completely removed.
This preserves vitamin C. Now let us consider black tea.
The basic difference between black tea and green tea lies in the fact that whereas green tea is steamed,
Black tea is not.
It is fermented instead.
The various steps in the manufacturing process are withering, rolling, sieving, fermenting and drying.
In the fermentation step, the reaction of the oxidized enzymes causes the leaves to take on a peculiar aroma and a reddish tint.
Sen finns det briktid, i vilket solen har blivit powderad, koncentrerad och moldad i former.
Den här typen av solen försvinner i stora mängder i Inner- och Outer Mongolia,
and in many parts of Siberia.
In the famed tea ceremony, one of the foremost cultural institutions of Japan, a green tea called Gyokuro is used.
This tea is grown in the shade, cured and powdered.
Det finns olika kustmål över hela världen.
Influerade av geografiska faktorer, av historien, av kulturen och av de olika människorna.
Japanas te-ceremoni är en utställd exempel på det.
This is a tea cottage used in the tea ceremony.
Den gröna te som är exporterad till amerikanska och europeiska länder används för isad grönt te och deliciosa teflavored ice cream.
Detta är regeringsinspektionens byrå, där de typer av te som nämnts tidigare måste först möta de exakta behov av den moderna forskningen.
before being sent to foreign markets.
They are subjected to a series of rigid laboratory tests in order to meet with the approval and satisfaction of tea drinkers throughout the world.
Jag kan inte.
En färskt, vilket förhindrar att någon mjölk spölar ut kontenten och försörjer den originella kvaliteten och aromen.
Men han har inte.