För att berätta om fysioterapin, så har damer och herrar bäst betalat sina konkurser.
Denna turné slutar i något sätt idag.
Damer och herrar har räddning att presentera sig till er för sista gången.
Miss Danmark, Miss Europa!
Miss Brasil!
Meddames, messieurs, il est nu, au titre de Miss Univers 1932, aujourd'hui à ce pas, par le jury constitué par le représentant de chaque nation dont une candidate est ici présente, à désigner comme Miss Univers 1932, Miss Turquie.
I am speaking to you from the fine Scotland.
I hope you are receiving us okay.
We can see you in the distance, about five miles away.
I am now going over for your reply.
Over.
Hello G5FL.
This is ex-Canada calling.
We are travelling smoothly at about 100 miles an hour.
Barely low.
Carrying 40 passengers.
We'll catch you up soon.
Over.
The flying scotsman answering you.
Yes?
Yes, we are receiving you quite well.
You are getting much nearer to us now.
So I think you must have spotted us all right.
Hello G5FL, X Canada calling and hearing you perfectly.
We had no difficulty identifying you from above.
Den kommer tillbaka till Glasgow via Edinburgh klockan fyra.
People want to speak to you Please stand by for a moment