Varsågod!
The mounted band of the lifeguards, the state trumpeters, precede the new Lord Mayor, Sir Percy Greenaway, on his arrival at the law courts to take his oath of allegiance before the Lord Chief Justice.
Var är ni?
Det är.
Now this is your joystick.
There is your throttle controlling your engine.
And there is your rudder bar.
And when I pass the joystick forward, my nose dips.
When I pull it back, it brings me back onto an even keel.
When I pull it right back, it raises my nose.
When I pass it to the left, my left wing drops.
When I pull it back, it brings the machine level again.
Du följer det?
Ja.
As you open your throttle, so you increase your speed.