Välkomna!
Tackar.
The London Fire Brigade has always held the reputation of being one of the finest in the world.
And they're determined to justify their name.
This is one of their latest firefighting appliances.
The tallest turntable fire escape as yet.
All steel, it reaches to a height of 100 feet and is entirely controlled by one man.
One of its devices is two-way conversation between the fireman at the top of the escape and the man at the control below.
The fireman up top has a microphone and a loud speaker fitted so that should he become enveloped in smoke during the height of the fire he can always talk to the man down below.
I.
Varsågod.
Här kommer de.
Ja, man kan det ju.
Ja, det kan jag.
Åh!
Bra jobbat!
Kom igen!
Vad tycker du om det här?
Det håller kvinnorna på vägen.