( = FILMINDUSTRIS VECKOREVY 1929		HANS VON EULER-CHELPIN,		professor vid Stockholms högskola,		har tilldelats halva 1929 års Nobel-		pris i kemi för sina vetenskapliga		undersökningar över sockerarters	jäsning.
UNIVERSAL NEWSPAPER NEWSREEL	=S		MacDONALD MEETS	HOOVER		England's Prime Minister	calls on President at	White House		 		 		[IFE vo ti io
UNIVERSAL NEWSPAPER NEWSREEL	PORR :2a RAA 6 Baa Na ARA		ETC: og	Falket Las ROR Eee al	decided on a world naval	parley to be held in London
UNIVERSAL NEWSPAPER NEWSREEL		Mr. MacDonald addresses		the Senate, telling them		LösttslarAv Roe	Anglo-American pact
UNIVERSAL		 		Senators congratulate the	INN
UNIVERSAL NEWSPAPER NEWSREFE		Mrs. Hoover and Miss		MacDonald attend a		gathering of the Girl	SN
UNIVERSAL NEWSPAPER NEWSREEL		HOOVER SEES ATHLETICS	NRO	IN SMASHING FINISH		 		 		Haas' homer and Miller's double	defeats Cubs 3 to 2 — 30,000 fans	[Sr		 		SHIBE PARK. PHILADELPHIA
UNIVERSAL NEWSPAPER NEWSREEL		Cubs score twice in the	[os
UNIVERSAL NEWSPAPER NEWSREEL		Athletics capture Series in		the ninth — Players” share,		Mackmen, $6,000 each,	Chicago, $4,000 each
6) TR		LÄNSPUMPAD PÅ TRE	TIMMAR	blev ångaren ”Richard Welford",	som under storm sjunkit i	Newcastles hamn.
Vid ett avlöningskontor.	420 män få sin avlöning	under en minut, och man	ber: Ela tass EE	de TO	oerhörda antalet arbetare	MC EET