Worldwide interest has been centred on Herne Bay, Kent, where Britains latest jet-propelled aircraft is to show its faces.
These pictures, taken before the weather broke, show the carefully planned photographic and timing apparatus for plotting the speed as the plane flashes across the bay.
Coloured floats will be used to mark the exact course to be followed.
Introducing the potential world-beater, the Gloucester Meteor.
Powered by two Rolls-Royce Derwent engines, this beautiful streamlined aircraft should do well over 600 miles an hour.
Seen together are the Gloucester company's chief test pilot, Mr. Eric Greenwood, and group captain Wilson, who will attempt the record.
The Meteor taxis off for a test flight.
From the cliffs overlooking the course Mrs. Eric Greenwood watches her husband's plane flash across the bay.
On four runs the apparatus records Greenwoods average of 603 miles an hour.
För RAF, gruppkaptan Wilson, briljant krigspilot, ska flyga den brittiska meteorn.
Allt är satt, Roseroy-störningstekniken är testad och gruppkaptan förbereder sig att ta brittiska motorn över kursen.
He's over the bay and here are the actual world beating record flights.
I Budapest har källen gått ur jorden lite tidigare än här.
Och det har de ungerska motorcyklisterna utnyttjat för halsbrytande dirt track-tävlingar.
Dirt kan man ju lämpligen översätta med lort.
Och något lortigare än Budapestbanan får man leta efter.
En spansk skola efter mönster av den världsberömda skolan i Wien har grundats i Budapest i ången.
Efter många års träning har en uppvisning nu ett rum på den kungliga ridskolan i Budapest.
Prins Bertil har återgjort sin rest fördelaktigt hörd i Förenta staterna.
Han fick amerikanerna att lyssna även denna gång.
En anmärkningsvärd prestation av en liten statsrepresentant mitt i stormakternas högljuddhet.
Jag är ingen politiker.
Och den här delegationen är helt en del av handelsdelegationen.
Jag vill säga att alla svenskar, som också...
as all the Scandinavian countries stand united in their wish to defend peace and order in the world.
I'm glad to be back in the United States again.
Sammavjord med en människa där du inte sämte med Swedish American Celebration tog jag det bra.
Jag hade ett grej där man upphävde en svensk delegation till de United States.
Det var ju ring.
Det här blir det.
Av P. Now I'm happy.
Det är väldigt däckligt.
Då var det.
is in a turmoil and even a profoundly peaceful country like Sweden cannot remain unaffected.
This time I'm heading a Swedish trade delegation which visits this country with the purpose of buying raw materials and machinery for Sweden.
You know that Sweden has always been a large importer of American goods.
And we are going to continue this practice.
I'm not going to say anything of
Jag vill säga att alla svenskar, samt alla svenskar,