Med den hopen och pröven i vårt hjärta sätter vi fram på hennes mission med noblheten.
Englands kvinna hoppade på frihet, även om Europa var i trädgården av den första rörelsen som slutade i Munich-avgörandet.
Lanserad i en timme av turmål, den stora flygplatsen tar en magen voyaget sekret, under stjärnordning.
Av gröna ghost-dodgade minar och krigsflöden, flyger hon väst till New York, tillgänglig, välkomnad bara av flygande nyheter och överraskade harbord.
This was not the maiden voyage of a great sea queen with proud flags unfurled and whistles blaring as she sails past Miss Liberty.
This is the end of the flight of a 29 million dollar refugee of war.
A fifth of a mile long, 85,000 tons of great grab hulk, the Queen Elizabeth is hailed by curious thousands as she moves uptown toward her birth in the Hudson River.
There she will be moored alongside her sister ship, the mighty Queen Mary, from whose deck the crew watches her brought in.
The British say that her bulk blocked navigation in the Clyde River.
Perhaps she was too inviting a target for Nazi air raiders.
But her master, veteran Captain C.J.
Townley, isn't saying.
He's giving out no information.
But the reasons for her trip are fairly obvious.
In Scotland, facing the probability of air bombings, her insurance would be greater than the cost of keeping her here in New York.
So here she stays in safety.
A refugee for the duration of the war.
Den mäktiga linaren går majestätiskt ner mot Clyde på sin väg till New York.
I daring new boats and all the other perils of the deep, she heads for the new world in the greatest secret voyage in history.
No vast crowds to see her off, just a handful of local people without the slightest idea of where the pride of the Clyde is going.
We know now that the Queen Elizabeth has arrived safely across the Atlantic, where the reception she had from a welcome party of half a million people was a marvelous tribute to all associated with the achievement.
When Mr. Churchill, who helped to plan the secret voyage, heard of its success, he said, I'm delighted, but I never had any doubt of it.
För landets biljardentusiaster visar vi här ett litet trick.
Det ser mycket enkelt och lätt ut så det är bara att gå hem och försöka.
Går det inte första gången så går det nog den andra.
USA upprustar giltak.
Ett nytt krigsdepartement behöver också byggas i Washington och även det måste gå undan.
Platsen blev utsedd och det hyreshus som stod där måste snabbt ur vägen.
Därför sprängdes det bort ett skådespel som samlade många skådelyssna och det blev också en smäll som man väl inte på den sidan Atlanten sett i en stad.
Ja, ja, ja.
I have asked the congress to reassemble an extraordinary session in order that it may consider and act on the amendment of certain legislations.
som i min bästa anledning så förändrar den historiska utländska politiken i USA att det förvandlar den fysiska relationen i USA med utländska nationer.
Och det var på grund av vad jag förvånade i januari från att titta på krisen med utländska affärer och deras möjliga effekt på oss att jag rekommenderade till kongressen i juli av det här året
That changes be enacted in our neutrality law.
I now ask again that such action be taken in respect to that part of the act which is wholly inconsistent with ancient precepts of the laws of nations.
The embargo provision.
I ask it because they are in my opinion most vitally dangerous to American neutrality
American security and above all American peace.
To those who say that this program would involve a step toward war on our part, I reply that it offers far greater safeguards than we now possess or have ever possessed to protect American lives and property from danger.
It is a positive program for giving safety.
I say this because with the repeal of the embargo this government clearly and definitely will insist that American citizens and American ships keep away from the immediate perils of the actual zones of conflict.
These perilous days demand cooperation between us without a trace of partisanship.
Våra verksamheter måste guidas av en enda hårdhållande tänk.
Att hålla Amerika utav den här kriget.