4U
MO	EE		Joseph		TE		 		die Jagdausstellung
DD	NoOldIY		STA
I	Ä
SHAMROCK IV OUT FOR	FIRST TEST OF SAILS		CITY ISLAND, N. Y. — Challenger	for the America's Cup is rigged	and put through paces on the Sound		LUNEINS
Into deep		water
[aa		mainsail		NI Njole NYE
LASSE	Yacht under way		FS iNjole NYE
After the		[SET		KINOGRAMS
PUT OVER SHAMROCK IV	IN READINESS FOR RACE		CITY ISLAND, N. Y. — Challenger	for the America's cup is lowered	into water at Jacobs ship yard		KINOGRAMS
Down the		ENE
In the		water		KINOGRAMS
nodlorlailA 4 .I	TS		EYED
ISS		LON		Peo
Us UNGE: OKT	INIÖ	har blivit hedersborgare i sin fö-	delsestad Glasgow, där han i unga	dar knogade som springpojke med	en lön av tre kronor i veckan.		+
EET		RESOLUTE'S TRIAL TRIP		shows U. S. cup defender		Ne role ye ne	FT
Sr EE		sy	FAT JAIAT 24TUJO23A	19bnstsb qua .2 .U ewodea	MAO HITOU-IOT MI		 		PER RDE
Off on her first trip—with Captain	FET ET
INTERNATIONAL		 		Displaying a bit of the form that	spells hard luck for Mr. Lipton.
SIR THOMAS LIPTON	yacht cup challenger	19-180 TN 00 BG		FREE Or er
INTERNATIONAL	Tan Fare		The Shamrock III, which Lipton		[st T ST TTR TRE SNR ET
INTERNATIONAL	INCE Tee		Sir Thomas and his		crew.
FVT		THE CUP CONTENDERS	Yachts Resolute and Vanitie	in a trial sail for the honor of	racing Lipton's Shamrock		New Haven, Conn.
INTERNATIONAL	vor. No 2 Ene		 		EARLEN		Vanitie.