Bette ger Tippi en pep-talk innan operationen börjar.
In you go!
Now, that isn't so bad, is it?
Or is it?
A lot of people we know wouldn't mind being in your place.
Getting all that attention from a beautiful gal.
But there's no pleasing these Hollywood dogs.
And if you think this one looks unhappy, just wait till you see victim number two.
You're next, my friend.
The boss has you spotted already.
Åh nej, den där ostrigs-tekniken kommer inte att rädda dig.
Kanske kan du inte se Betty, men Betty har ett ögat på dig, och det finns en glint i den.
Och nu, med en liten vändning av händerna, förändrar vi en liten dörr till en liten dörr.
I andra ord, tiden passar, men inte nästan snabbt för att följa Tibby.
Och vi är nu på rinsningsstagen.
Glöm inte hans viskar.
Allt som finns nu är en bra bristrubb med en turkisk toalett och en damm av papper under armen.
Den här Davis-gallen går verkligen åt saker i en businesslike manner.
Maybe we'd better get going before she decides to dunk us.
Who will we call on now?
Let's see.
Eric admiringly, but not too energetically, is this threesome.
On one side Paula Stone casts her smiles on young Johnny Arledge, while on the other side Johnny, the lucky so-and-so, gets a break from pretty Louise Latimer.
Oh, why don't we get breaks like this?
Amusing Preston Foster and Edie Adams.
Preston har hans jöttingkläder på.
Han kommer att se att Edie har en bra tid.
Och tyvärr har Edie en bra tid.
Men för att säkerställa att partiet är på rätt väg här är Santa Paulas hansom chief officer, kapten Adler, som gör rounderna med sina gäster.
Nu som vi har tittat på råd och steamskyddslägen så ska vi se vad som händer på de här stjärnorna.
För vi är på väg till det kallade Beverly Wilshire Hotell.
Från dessa svängande dörrar har alla star i Hollywood gått, och genom dem kommer de flesta av filmens berömda, för det är majsfärdighet.
Tänk snabbt, och vi försöker inte missa någon.
Här är Marian Nixon och hennes direktörshusband William Siter, med Helen Ferguson, en gång populär i silentfilmer.
Helen är nu en lycklig agent.
Det är rätt, Marian.
Kom in nära och ge oss en god titt.
Vem är det nu?
Jag vet inte.
Det är Mary Bryan, June Collier, Cary Grant och Stu Irwin.
Mary och Cary är ett romantiskt team.
Nästa har vi Evelin Leigh och Frank Lawton.
Ja, Mr. och Mrs. Frank Lawton.
Jag undrar om vi missade några tidigare tillgångar.
Ja, den här gruppen måste ha gått bort.
Det är Joey Brown och Lyle Talbot.
Hur kom Lyle tillbaka så snabbt?
Följande är Carl Brisson, och med kameran, filmdirektören Marvin Leroy.
Nu, om du vill skrämma klockan... Tack.
Här är Anita Louise och Jeanette MacDonald.
De hansomma blonda tjejerna är Jean Raymond och hans bror Robert Marlowe.
Bob kom till Hollywood på vacation och hittade sig i filmerna.
Nu kommer Yuna Merkel, på vänster, med Johnny Arledge.
Johnny har haft en tuff dag.
Och där kommer kapten Blood, Errol Flynn förstås, och hans kvinna Lily Demita.
Burns och Allan har bara gått ut ur elevatoren, men Gracie ställer klockan.
Det ser ut som om hela staden kommer ut i natt.
Den röda orkiden i den abstrakta uttrycket är Florence Rice.
Hennes topper är skrivaren Robert Riskin.
Flossie undrar om hon har lämnat ögonen.
Clifton Webb besöker hans mor och två vänner.
Clifton är en av de få som ser komfortabelt ut.
Oh, there's Kay Francis, escorted as usual by Delmar Daves.
Say a word to the folks... Well, never mind.
Eddie Horton thinks there's safety in numbers, so he brings two charming ladies.
He's quite the gallant beau, too.
This is Robert Young, James Bush and Mrs. Cliff Edwards.
Oh, hold everything.
Do we or don't we see Joan Crawford and Franchot Tome?
Yes, sir.
And that is a rare occurrence.
Well, folks, that's enough excitement for one day.
But if there's anything more you want to know about Hollywood, just write... Who is she?
Anita?
Why, sure.
Anita Stewart.
Remember her?
Looks like Lee's a good guy to stick around.
He seems to recognize everybody.
Now he's spotted Mae Clark.
Hej, där är May.
Lee har invigat dig till hans båt.
Säg ja, vi får se om du kommer dit.
Där är du.
Har du din transferkväll?
Nej, det är inte viktigt.
Konduktorn glömde hans punch.
Det ser ut som om den speedbåten är på väg mot oss.
Och May är på hälften.
Gör något, Tracy, annars blir vi i problem.
Kolla där.
Hej, det är Maddie Kemp.
What a close shave.
You'd better turn in that cab gal.
And now let's see if we can find... The heart of Beverly Hills is this well-kept bowling green.
One of America's most ancient and honorable sports, bowling on the green still has legions of enthusiasts.
Among them Otto Kruger and Edward Arnold.
Otto starts the game by rolling the white jack onto the field.
The object now is to lay the bowling balls, known as bowls, as near to the jack as possible.
Being flat on one side, the bowls do not roll straight but describe a curve.
The trick thus being to curve them just the right amount.
Good shot.
Well, now let's see what the big boy can do.
Oh, a southpaw, eh?
Oh, too much steam.
Eddie has a gallery, his three kids.
Elizabeth the oldest doesn't think much of pops prowess.
Neither does Edward junior.
But Dorothy Jane says he's oak with her.
Let's see if you'll do better this time.
That's more like it.
Come home, Pop.
All is forgiven.
Now it's Otto's turn again.
And in case we forgot to tell you, Otto's alias is Dead Eye Dick.
Dizzy Dean has nothing on him.
Now, no gloating.
Eddie's worried enough already.
Come on, Eddie.
Give him the old spitball.
Ouch, that was close.
Well, Eddie will probably take a ribbing when he gets home.
Annual awards banquet of the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences.
A distinguished group is here to see the coveted gold statuettes presented.
Here at one table we find Ross Alexander and Benny Barnes chatting busily.
Benny's floral coiffure is all the rage.
Next to them we find that old smoothie Cesar Romero being polite to cute little Rosalind Bakke.
And who wouldn't?
Ah, Dr. Defoe.
Pardon, Jean Herschelt.
And his charming wife.
For a couple of swell comics, Una Merkel and Guy Kebby are awfully serious.
But then this is a serious occasion.
Jimmy Dunn and Patricia Lee are just arriving.
Meanwhile, lined up for a news picture is this imposing group of motion picture immortals.
Director Frank Capra, David Watt Griffith, pioneer and genius of the silent films, Gene Herschelt, Henry B. Walthall, the beloved little colonel of Griffith's Birth of a Nation, Frank Lloyd, director of Mutiny on the Bounty, Donald Crisp, and the one and only Cecil B. DeMille.
Allt det här med namn betyder ingenting för Henry.
Han säger att en banquet betyder en middag, och en middag betyder mat.
Men var är det?
Kanske din tjej inte gillar dig, Henry.
Det är rätt, hitta ut.
Han tillverkar mig, han tillverkar mig inte.
Servicen bryr sig inte om Mr. och Mrs. John Mack Brown.
De har för bra tid.
Så gör Jane Wyatt.
Här är en vänlig tjej, Jeanette McDonald.
Var är den berömda smilen, Jeanette?
Henry Wilcoxons having trouble getting a light from his dad's cigar.
There you are.
Now give it back to papa.
Over at the speaker's table, things are happening.
Frank Capra, president of the academy, aided by Clark Gable, presents to producer Irving Thalberg the gold statuette for the year's best production, Mutiny on the Bounty, in which Clark starred.
Looks like Gene Raymond and his mother.
Let's say hello.
Oh, secrets, eh?
Well, guess we can take a hint.
These two kids, Joel McRae and Frances Dee, have proved two stars can live happily under one roof.
Mae Robeson's all dolled up in white lace.
And what's she listening to so intently?
Ah, the old maestro D.W.
Griffith is presenting the awards for the best performances of the year.
To Betty Davis for her performance in Dangerous goes a gold statuette and the thrill of being acclaimed the screens number one actress for the year.
Det finns ingen anledning till att det här beslutet är ett populärt beslut.
Alla är glada för Betty och entusiastiska.
Ja, alla, trots Henry.
Han har fortfarande spagetti med matsauce och ravioli på hans minne.
Victor McLaglen, för sitt skönt arbete i Informer, får en toffa för den bästa utbildningen av en aktör.
Och Mr. och Mrs. Preston Foster applåderar.
Preston gjorde en bra jobb i Informer också.
Och så gjorde Margot Graham.
Hon är glädjad över Vicks success.
Men vem är det inte?
Oh yes, Henry.
Well, nothing but a square meal would delight Henry.
And now folks, if there's anything else you want to know about Hollywood, just write Harry...