Varje sju sekunder.
Varje sju sekunder mörker någon av tuberkulosen.
I det här landet mörker tuberkulosen flera tusen människor varje år.
I hela världen mörker mer än 4 miljoner människor varje år av tuberkulosen.
This is Maria.
She might be someone you know.
Will she be attacked by tuberculosis?
Will she be alive a few years from now?
Let us see what her chances are.
Let us suppose that the inside of Maria's lungs looks like this.
Och låt oss tänka oss att germen som skapar tuberculosis ser ut så här ut.
När de här germen attackerar Maria så skapar hennes kropp naturliga vapen för att kämpa mot dem.
If the defense is strong enough, the enemy is defeated.
The defenders remain in Marias body to protect her against future attacks of tuberculosis.
And Maria remains well and happy.
But sometimes the attack of tuberculosis is too strong.
Sometimes the defense is too weak.
Then tuberculosis wins.
Det här är männen av tuberkulosis.
Tusen barn och äldre som är seriöst sjuka.
Tusen som kan dö av tuberkulosis.
Ska Maria bli nästa?
Kan något göras för att skydda henne?
Ja, Maria kan skyddas av vaccination.
Vaccination can give Maria's body the defense she needs against tuberculosis.
And then tuberculosis will lose the battle.
Today, in our country and in many other countries, tuberculosis has many allies.
Städer i ruiner, förstörda sjukhus, tråk, djur, dåligt byggnad, sjukdom.
Männen i världen har samlat sig med oss för att kämpa mot tuberkulosis.
Vår ministerie för sjukvård leder kriget här med hjälp av UNICEF, United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund, World Health Organization, Red Cross och relieforganisationer från Danmark, Norge och Sverige.
Alla är tillsammans i den internationella tuberkulosen-kampanjen.
International cooperation against the international enemy, tuberculosis.
We must act quickly.
The enemy is on the march.
Every seven seconds tuberculosis kills a human being.
Every seven seconds.
We must act quickly.
Our scientists and laboratories and men of many lands are forging the weapons to protect us.
War is declared on tuberculosis.
Our forces are mobilized.
Our counterattack rolls forth.
Motorized forces.
Supported from the air.
En varg.
Defensive av life against death.
Vård mot tuberkulosa är pågående runt om i vårt land och i många andra länder.
Vaccination för alla som behövs.
I land.
I water.
And by air.
Defensive of life against protection familiar.
A lifebelt for your daughter.
New protection for your son.
New hope for Maria.
Men vår främling har allier.
Folk som sprider falska berättelser om vaccineringen.
Och folk som lyssnar på dem.
Som Marias mor.
Var inte orolig.
Missa inte chansen att skydda dina barn från tuberkulosis.
Många har varit vaccinerade.
In this country, thousands of people have already received this protection.
Not one person has ever been hurt by this vaccination.
Millions of lives can be saved.
One chance less for tuberculosis.
One chance more for your child.