The felled logs are conveyed	to the frozen lakes during	EEE		Ford 0S	JUST SRS
ER Radi ER ORD CA		ROT uns		FR MMA
odht 18 svitis 2g0l odT	.bomwesom 918 bus Iimwse	oini boqisw bre bobnsid	ELER ORS EET		NEEDS	FHSRANRMN
EET	ET STEEN		BIC
The boards are cut in	proper lengtbs and loaded	LT TA		IK RTE	KN VU
Swedish spruce wood is	converted into paper for the	newspapers of many couat-	ries at the paper mills of the	Holmens Bruks & Fabriks	A.B., Hallstavik, Sweden.		FOITERK HA ZEN VER	EE US KE
Paperpulp is obtained by	mixing the chemical and	mechanical woodpulp.
KUSTER ROM	[TTT TT Cd	a		AROR	BELL
Castle of Gripsholm,	Central Sweden.		fia ISEN	EE
Skidlöpning vid		Åreskutan.
Kälkåkning.
ID OT EET
Kronprinsparets	EE ee		vid Hindås.
NT LT an
Kungliga tribunen och		publiken.