Siam is known as "The	Kingdom of the Yellow	FÖRA
A Yellow Robe is ahvays	FST SSE SA	[SS TR	[er
EORESETE SS		SES SR	FE BETEN LES	FT [Tse RNE IST TSE		EES TS En
USS MSE Te TAN	of the popular "Watts" or	[1110		Paramount-Burton Holmes
[EN EST SNS	”Leogryphs” guard the	NESS
A serene Siamese Buddha	SYST SSE
2oldsp prideinimiC	pICKO SES NIT	RECO de er		I
art 1o 2n0itsivp wole odT		260 Jo or
A beautiful reproduction in	miniature of the most/famous	Fire of Siam fe - the	skor Ya I Im		| VW
Other indeseribable	sanctuaries rise on the banks	of the Menam River at		[ere 1 SN SE		SM
2loo7 adt bavorpaasd adt a	odf n-ooslsT Ivo ot fo	31 TV ENN		DERE sf [ST		CD
EOS		SAN ITA		Ed
mob amor is 21om last SU		NIE [SV Joh ia ie		FE ENE TT ET Er		Ed
ad no Iebag buol adt ditt	NERE DT
ISEN PR	Seodf nari Toitarg—2wof	IEEE 67) UL (0		Cl
BEE 7 fi) (6 Kero I EET
NRK ESn STA on		FER: RIE		ss
[LEE RETT		LE UR VA
NO
BNI EI SG ET på	NNE		EES RIE
Like a bit of Wonderland - - =
Marvelous mosaics made	of broken china and bits	of glass set in plaster - = -
Within the great pagodas	are relics of the Buddha—	who wore the Yellow Robe	and founded a great religion	in the sixth century B. C.---