OLE AR TER o ENTA	KO	<OWwT 1169		FR	re TSK
The second largest city in	Sweden is Gothenburg	which is the largest export	harbour.		eta VAA a	PYTT es
CERN		 		| SARA
Interior view of different	PIREN A		BE
Automatic cold pressing of		STc se		ik AA	DRAR
KrnEoge		SN RAR
Races, balls, and retainers		are being assembled.		DILGKIES EEG	AAARINEERRAO RR.
The S.K.F. bearings are	manufactured in many dif-	ferent sizes and are applied	to all kinds of machinery,	trucks, etc.		SSE EELES	STÄRK RAA	KELIPtili
|	|		 		With a plain RÖTT of	70 mm. shaft diameter,	16 kilos coal brickettes are	required per week to over-	come the friction between	the journal and the bearing.		RR a EEE	BJA RT AARAA Nk	| He Ko
KORG ED	in an S.K.F. ball bearing of	corresponding size and for	| the same period are required	only..... 2.4 kilos.		DEU ee	LETTER ERS	FA är EE
] RR GT		HIN TT-		METE	KICKEN
odt or9dw modisd somlsM	918 AÄsmnsd 101 anis	CE 4 EAT Te	-bouoz adi 22072		ENDE PER EN	ROTE REDS	ESuempergsgernaen gUSOaT Es
Fishing village on the West	Coast of Sweden.		BN TD gE ON
The ground in Sweden is	[FETT IDR TE nd	the winter months.		AMNRR	& a RE
ME		Fa