SL DOSA	LS
FIER	BTRBIE ROD	[RV TAB RSS	EIS TATE		PEST	BoTT TITS Ta
MUSEETS	BS SE Sr	a case of tobacco.
Curiosity aroused ve	PES	EISTOST
ELEN TRIST:	KULTEN ET Sr	BT ee	fl FOT ST	PEST SES	Kn STAN TATA	RSS k SV I ER ENE	IST
Hd	Ej	3	2	5
001 sd bluose srstT	FORTS ESS	KR pi SAR gb	UNT cal ga	SES
Three sticks of tobacco	[OnT SITTER Spa	KINO TT
Oavuta Bay.
SVIT HEST	ASA	Nr rer		plinoiksilivis mott 29lim	Ers a RA
Boys wvhohave completed	2years' service on the	plantation coming intobe.	paid off. They will be re-	LTS RT Sena	[repa oa er Tel	again ina fev years.
KEETESEN
Få	3	3	EC	3
[TITTAR SD) jo AT Nå	EN ESSTORNTSTESTES	BITS SV TBS	KSL fr	[STETSON	EST SSE RS NTEN	[NESSER SS ES rg	note alt Avon
/y	< DITA tas	KOSS SLATER V STENS Sv	REA it		ÖN	| SL am |
he Island of Rura Sura		in the distance, upon which	Eg	important mission stations		TS ST SN	ducted by the Marist	ENAS
Converts come to		meet us as we land
ot amoa 2hevnoD	BITTE ATA Tr
NER	RUE Nta	CISA aöycar
NERE NS	LURA	about once a NER
INSE parade in	front of the home	of the Fathers
för INST	of the Solomon Island.	Marist Missions
The teachers
Converts working g		EIS energy
MRC STA		and his assistant
The orchestra, —		and his assistant
lc SVEN		Fjord
TS sjrss [SSU AG		NE STEG TA	JA
he call to dinner, —		Savagery's method ,	and —
Civilizations summons		fos
KSSS ESA	2sllardmu ads ao		KedT To TTR Te VE Te MESA
"The women would	not come out alone
föra protected by	the priest, they	passed by our camera		OETateR
S etting type
MORRA		Pressman and the	Devil
FSTSA	EXT NAR TIR SYST
This boy has been		to Australia, and look	what it did to hirs
Civilization went to		his head, but not	Lol SE
ENS	his necktie is a deep	South Sea kd
I mission station Ing		 	 		AÅ Ionesome Marist		TAN Väs ASTA
ICT SNES NS	going to church
2	å	3	2	å
EYE gnibnuonwd	FIRA SNUS SR STAT	lsw dyid s
NNE SETS	villages are not allowed	inside this wall without	special permission.
Something INTE	sweater line. -- Notice	the new spring Box	Fra
Y3		MV		    	   	   		  	   		vå	Å		AT		 		Only a quarter of	EN: ar AN I	Fathers' home are. I	LAR TR TI I	where cannibal I	feasts are held
Only a quarter of	Co ER SK AN	fack TT TT NA		the kai-kai grounds	NUET	feasts are held
Ån idol still worshipped.		outside the mission wall
nr		tel
Modern Eve plays her ukalele		CT BT TS TT ST JA
SO ENE		FI RUGE:R OS Re	FILT IEES SVS