Det finns en lång sjöpassning över de djupa vattnet i västatlantiken och de rullande väggarna i den engelska kanalen innan färgerna som har vintert i södra Europa och Afrika kan återuppnå Englands sjöar.
Av dessa besökare är Wobblers familj en viktig grupp.
Och den första tillgången av Wobblers är Chiff-Chaff som ser underbart bra ut efter sin resa 2000 mil från Afrika.
Nästa kommer wood warbler, som tittar på insekter på bramblen och samlar material för nästen som han och hans vänner skapar på grunden mellan döda bläddor.
De skapar en domad stjärna över toppen, men ingen linje.
Han tittar över sin hem och tittar kraftigt på nära honom, willow warbler, som troligen kom till England lite före honom.
Willow warblers skapar också en näst med en rummen, men deras har extra nöd att vara linjade med färger.
Var det tajm då Willow Wobblers ägg hetsat med sin blom.
Willow Wobblers sätts förbörs för insekter, vilket de gick hem till där han gick hem.
Från hans utgångspunkt på majströmmen kan Willow Warbler se på utskottet av skogen sin närvaro, Lesser White Throat, hans hem är väldigt liten, ungefär halv krona.
Denna hungriga familj av Lesser White Throats äter 5 000 katerpillar i en kvartnatt.
In the hedgerow at the edge of the wood the greater white throats build their homes, often placing them among nettles for greater safety.
The white throats pick insects off wild roses and carry them back to their nest which they have placed safely in a clump of grass.
More insects cry the family and the white throat is off to the roses again.
Men han har inte djur till sig själv.
På andra sidan har Vårdbladet hittat mat för hans hungriga brud i deras hem bland brämborna.
De här lilla Vårdbladerna är som en katerpillar per minut om deras föräldrar kan tillverka dem.
Och bläddrarna söker insekter.
The garden warbler, who winters in Central Africa, likes to spend spring and summer by a wooded lake or river in England.
In marshy woodland places lives also the sedge warbler, who is doing her best to keep the sun off her family, though she too feels the heat.
Her mate searches the grass and reeds for insects.
Young sedge warblers are hungry, and when they've eaten up all the caterpillars in the neighborhood, even a butterfly resting on a reed is not safe.
A butterfly appears to make a rather tough titbit.
When they've been in the nest a fortnight, the young sedge warblers wander into the marshy ground round their home.
Here they are, perched securely on an old trunk of a tree and still looking for catapult.
Where the real marshland begins you will find the nest of the reed warblers.
Det är verkligen en kradel av gräs som fastnar i gränserna.
Baby reed warblers are as hungry as all their young cousins.
By putting a watch on the nest
Vi kan se att de lilla djuren är födda i en och en halv minut intervall.
Men här är en annan Riddvorblers näst med något konstigt som händer.
En kucka har lagt hennes ägg här och den unga kuckan som redan har hämtat är rädd för Riddvorblers ägg.
All the insects of this district go to feed the cuckoo, which grows much larger than its foster parents who continue to feed it.
Vår blås gärna katerpillars, det gick det väl om livs.
Det fick katerpillars från kris.
Katerpillars från Bushes.
Katerpillars, det var stripp, det livs från alla planter, sköter fint, det hängde i familjes av vår blå bebis i en busch.
It is our summer visitors, the warblers, who preserve for us the leafy loveliness of our English countryside.
In dining outdoors, wait for your food to be served you.
Waving your arms like a traffic cop is particularly bad form.
It is considered much more genteel to sit quietly down and keep the hands quiet.
Though you're hungry, wait.
Do not rise and wave and never call out, come on, slip me my sirloin.
Never turn your back on your host.
There, that's better.
In this way you can carry on a light conversation.
It is somewhat difficult, however, when your mouth is in your nose as it is with this anteater.
Worm salad when taken in hand is an especially appetizing dish.
A worm will turn but not when properly eaten.
However, like asparagus they may be transferred to the face, to the mouth, in the fingers.
In bringing up a baby on a bottle, great care is needed.
If the little deer refuses it, you should persist.
And if the bottle should have a dark brown taste and he still refuses it, you might try a glass of beer if you can get it.
This is a community filling station.
A crowded lunchroom is not conducive to good manners.
But try not to crowd, just quietly drink.
There are some who do not enjoy snakes.
In eating them, however, you can make them more tender by pounding them as you do a sirloin.
This bird, a secretary bird, enjoys snake steaks.
Some of us prefer them with salt and pepper.
Never leave any of your snake's hips, I mean steak.
Eat it all, otherwise you may offend your hostess.
Emily Post säger att fiskar kan äta bättre om de äter lättare.
Lägg ihop hos dig och försöka, försöka igen.
Lägg inte dig förvånad.
Gå igenom varje trötthål.
Om en fiskhäst påverkar kan man använda skivor.
Lägg ihop hos dig och var försiktig med skivor.
A foster father can bring up a baby in this manner.
Careful feeding by hand.
Teaching the little one the use of a spoon.
String beans, a great delicacy.
If one can avoid grasping them in the fingers, it is just as well.
Some of us prefer our eggs in an egg cup.
And most of us only hold one egg in our cheek at a time.
This is optional, however, and some may prefer two.
You pay your money and you take your choice.
When you eat bananas, remember they digest better in the stomach than in the cheeks.
Vad vi lägger oss på så varje dagning.
Även då det med hjälp på att få ut en av de galet och isofagus.
Jojön är konflikterade.
Det var lätt att ta på.
Han har visst, gick det bäst att kanske trän, tajm, tajten, trän, väg från