A day of glory.
The prayers of countless millions have been answered and brilliant weather greets the day of the jubilee procession.
First, with the captains escort of royal horse guards, comes his royal highness the duke of York with the duchess and the princesses, Elizabeth and Margaret Rose.
In this procession also are the Duke and Duchess of Kent.
With the captain's escort of lifeguards, His Royal Highness the Prince of Wales, with Her Majesty the Queen of Norway and the Duke of Glasgow.
In the next carriage of the Princess Procession are the Princess Royal, Princess Victoria and the Earl of Harwood.
And lastly, His Gracious Majesty and Queen Mary.
Det processen sveps om den konstitutionen, hur det väl inte natt för att ha ett par kvar.
Runt kundtidning, fru Piccadilly, en bestämd.
Från en län av glädje och glädje.
Glädjen av kungen i dag är glädjen av folket.
Och denna demonstration av kärlek och älskning som vi använder av vårt regerande har blivit en av oss i 25 år av exempel och önskemål till det brittiska empire.
At the law courts the procession falls.
The Lord Mayor of London surrenders to his majesty the sword which is the city's symbol of independence.
After touching the hilt, the king returns it to the Lord Mayor for safe keeping.
En så om som på skattegården, men det kan inte minnas att det väntar i alla different processen.
Det här var en av de andra.
Det var en av de andra.
Och sen de kvinnorna och kringen.
Inside the great cathedral, the service of thanksgiving.
The great ones of the land voicing the prayers that come from a myriad hearts.
Läggs St.
Pauls, leder kvinnan och kvinnan tillbaka till Buckingham Palace.
Från embankmentet, till Admiralty Art och till Malmö.
Välkomna!
The procession swings in through the forecourt of the palace.
And the crowds rush forward to cheer the royal family as they appear on the balcony.
And we take this opportunity of reproducing for you the stirring words which the king broadcast in the evening of this great and unforgettable day.
Words cannot express my thoughts and feelings.
I can only say to you, my very dear people, that the Queen and I thank you from the depths of our hearts for all the loyalty and, may I say, the love with which this day and always
You have surrounded us.