Det var skitplats på väg till New York.
Arbete med smörjning.
Det är skitplats på väg till Arme.
Man kan inte vara bäst på 27 järnväg.
Han är bra.
Grove, på tillbaka, gör fem jordar.
Meyer stiger tillbaka och tappar en lång pass.
Gått över händerna av Grove som skapar armets touchdown.
Notre Dame skrattar tillbaka när Bill Shakespeare tar en pass och släpper armén in för en första touchdown.
Now Shakespeare passes to Leighton for a first down.
Again Shakespeare fades back and tosses a long pass.
Knocked down at Armys goal line.
Now West display the disputed forward pass.
Shakespeare to Milner.
And because the steel judge ruled interference by army, the ball is given to the Irish of armies two yard line.
In the last minute of play, Notre Dame smashes over with a tying touchdown.
The game is over, but the dispute still rages.
And now we show you the disputed play again, in slow motion, selected judge for yourself.
A closer shot, so you may study it again.
Was there interference?
What do you think?
Ja, ja, ja, ja, ja.
Vad säger du?
Vad vill du?
Jag har en kvinna som är kvinna och en kvinna som är kvinna och en barnsbror.
Åh, ja.