Fläggen av tre stora nationer i Moskva gav token av frihetsspiritet som kallade denna konferens i Sovjetkampanjen.
En konferens där huvudmålet var att snabba den sista förlossningen av Tyskland.
Första tillgången var den amerikanska statssekreteraren, veterankonsul Kordell Howell.
Välkomna av M. Litvinov och M. Molotov.
Red Army Band spelade Star Spangled Banner.
Den inspekterade Garabana.
Den förbryterna för en sekretär.
En.
Följde av God Säver Kingen.
Väldigt liten tid var spänd i formaler.
This conference had met for business discussions between busy men, and the speed with which they arrived at decisions gave ample proof of their determination to prosecute all war matters without delay.
The conference covered not only military matters but many other topics, ranging from the punishment of war criminals to post-war security.
In the field of military operations, the whole plan of action by each of the allies was fully and freely conveyed to the others.
In the presence of each nation's military advisers, the intentions and strategy of each were made clear and mutually agreed.
...table in the Kremlin to sign the declaration of security.
First, the representative of the Soviet Union.
Then the United States.
Great Britain next.
And lastly, the representative of China, who, though not actively engaged in fighting Germans, is nonetheless at war with Germany.
The meeting ended as it had begun, in great cordiality.
We have the word of our foreign secretary that full understanding now exists between the English-speaking peoples and the USSR.
Nothing could be a better guarantee of our final victory than the war against Germany.
Detta är för den treviga konferensen, så långt förväntat, så ofta påbörjad.
För några dagar blir Teheran fokus på världen.
Snart efter kriget kom brittiska och röda armésoldater till hand här i Iran.
Det var den enda landets kommunikation vi hade.
Det var fint att den första mötena av Churchill, Roosevelt och Stalin skulle vara här.
Det här är marshal Voroshilov, sovjetkommissar för försäkring.
På Solan.
It was not concerned with the future, but with the glorious past.
Mr. Churchill was to present to Marshal Stalin the Stalingrad sword.
The gift from our king on behalf of all the peoples of the British Empire to the heroic defenders of the great steel city in southern Russia.
Acknowledgement of the most gallant and most desperate stand in all this war.
Världens framtid, som skapade en tid av lycka mot de tyska invandrarna.
Bredvid hårdbäraren, som tyvärr öppnar kamerans syn, kan man se hur Stalin kastade hårdbäraren.
Mr. Churchill är tydligt med om det här när han pratar med den unga Shah of Persia.
Han hade klubbat tillsammans för att presentera honom med de här gifterna som var handlade till honom av non-kommissionerade officer av regimens representanter.
Konferensen slutade, som alla stora konferenser, med grupper som ställde sig inför Newsreel och Press.
Superficially they always seem very much the same kind of picture.
But it requires very little imagination to read into the lines behind the picture.
This one stands for the attempts by the three greatest nations fighting Germany to reach common ground and understanding.
To act as allies should.
To deliver the most telling blows at the enemy in the most vital places at the right time.
To come.
Present appearances suggest that the men who guide our destiny have found the common factor that will bring victory and follow it with peace.
That is the best we can hope for and the least we have a right to expect.
...far eastern fleet set out.
Battleships, cruisers, aircraft carriers, destroyers...
and transports with troops aboard.
Invasion of Tarawa under the command of Harry Hill.
...of the United States Marines.
This was an all-American show.
Before the battle, a service was held on board each ship before the action was over. ...
Aircraft overhead.
But things have changed in the Pacific and those were American planes, not Japs.
Going on ahead for the softening up.
They dropped a thousand tons of bombs on these coral isles by the sleepy lagoon.
Only the lagoons were not sleepy anymore.
Japanese occupiers for two years had turned them into solid hard-shelled...
Världskastningarna öppnar upp och många av landningskraften får direkt hitt.
Men det är en mil som är allvarlig.
Den centrala fortifikationen av Tarawa.
Den tuffaste objektiven i hela den här tuffa ringen.
They're ashore.
And what a story those scorched and withered palms reveal.
Surely no living thing could have gone on living.
But the Japs were living in their foxholes deep in the coral under concrete.
Only a strip 20 feet wide was the first beachhead between water and Japanese machine guns.
But the marines made it wider and deeper and died.
And more came on and more died.
Over a thousand killed in 76 hours.
Barbed wire to catch and hold the invaders under the muzzle of automatic guns.
Bombproof pillboxes that had stood up to the most murderous hail afar the Pacific ever heard and saw.
And inside them, Japanese soldiers whose highest and before your eyes tells all you need to know about the kind of hell it was.
Coast guns pounded into scrap metal.
...var koreaner.
De gav upp glädjande.
En del av en krig som USA svarade att förlora i Nordafrikas konferens.
Very few of the Japs themselves were taken prisoner.
Six thousand Japanese died for their vile cause of conquest.
The wounded received treatment.
It's quiet now in Tehran.
This was the scene of the first allied offensive action against the Japanese in the Pacific.
Warships, aircraft carriers and transports with full air protection.
Setting out to retake the southeast Solomons, the Tulagi area.
In the landing craft, marines and equipment.
This operation was carried out as a complete surprise, opening up with a bombardment.
Like nearly all naval actions, it all looks a bit vague and distant.
But there's nothing vague where those shells are landing.
The marines go ashore to overcome what remains of resistance.
To turn out the Japanese from the island they conquered so recently.
This was a Japanese camp.
It has now become a stronghold of American marines from which they can clear the islands completely.
The stars and stripes go up in place of the rising sun.
That's cause for congratulations.
The Ocean Might of Britain's Friend Across the Atlantic.
The Ocean Might of Britain's Friend Across the Atlantic