Flying Fortresses and Liberators of the US Army 8th Air Force heading for Berlin.
This was the first full-scale daylight attack on the heart and center of the Nazi war and political machine.
Following up the many thousands of tons already dropped by the Royal Air Force, these Americans were going to tell Hitler that no city in Germany is safe from heavy bombing by night or day.
I den här attacken skickades 68 kraftbombare ner.
Men hundratals gick där och kom tillbaka.
Och med krigarna förstörde de 176 krigarna i den här första kriget ensam.
Och det är Berlin nedanför.
Mamma är borta.
För nära uppfattning kommer vi till en stillbild som visar en kluster av bombar som hittar en fabriksdistrikt.
Alltid där och tillbaka var Fortressen och Liberatorn attackerade.
Det här flyget som har en kamera har en motorn utav aktion.
Det är propellern.
De kommer in på landet efter en stor strid mot vikten i kriget i Berlin.
Några av bombarna sätter ut fläror för att varma landstafeln.
De har en skadad man på bordet.
Let's have a word from some of the air cruising formations.
It was my pleasure to have led the first heavy American bombardment mission over Berlin.
Lieutenant Durer, the navigator who led the mission into Germany that day.
Durer, how about some words from you?
Well, as you know it was tough navigating because of the almost impossible weather we had.
However, I'm glad now that you elected to go on hand.
I'm proud that our outfit could be the first one to make the trip.
Lieutenant Flagler, a bombardier up in the nose.
Colonel, the fighters made it pretty hot and the weather made it pretty cold, but I believe we hit the target.
Good.
And that's not all.
Pictures have just been released of the 12,000 pound bomb which is now being dropped on enemy targets.
Five and a half tons of factory buster.
And there are plenty of them.
Mr. Eden was greeted by his wife and officials of the foreign office.
He looks happy, as well he may.
It doesn't seem so very long since any mission that went to Russia was almost foredoomed to fail.
But so much has happened since.
Let's hope those days of Anglo-Soviet mistrust and misunderstanding are gone for good.
Lady Louis Mountbatten received the king and queen and the two princesses when they went to see the special American show in aid of British service charities.
Den allmänna kasten är helt avgörande från amerikansk armé.
Dessutom den berömda låtaren Irving Berlin.
Pakthusen gav en stor reception till den röda familjen- som följde Lady Louie Manbatten och lieutenant general Davids- som regerade amerikansk armé i det europeiska teatern.
Irving Berlin sang one of his own songs which is dedicated to the British fighting men with plenty of sentiment.
I like my coffee and rolls and he likes his tea but we're in there till we get to Germany when the job is done.
And the war is won.
We'll be clasping hands across the sea.
And then the high spot of the show.
The big minstrel number with its singing and dancing all-male chorus.
You wouldn't suspect a newsreel cameraman of having a soul, would you?
You wouldn't picture him as a humble student treading softly down the leafy lanes as a pilgrim to the shrine of an immortal.
He holds the camera before him as he walks, and the scholarly stoop of his shoulders enables him to pass beneath the overhanging foliage.
In reverent awe, the traveler approaches the end of his hallowed journey.
The quiet, unspoiled surroundings with which our island story links the name of our great bard.
Stratford-on-Avon.
Stratford-on-Avon, you darn fool.
We're going to see Bernard Shaw.
Hello, Mr. Shaw.
This is the home in which Mr. George Bernard Shaw spent his 88th birthday.
Men han var rädd, några dagar innan han hade stannat med vänner någonstans i södra England.
Och det första jag såg var en bomb från Adolf Hitler som bröt mitt sovrum.
Jag hoppas att nästa dag ska jag få något mer lyckligt än det här.
Hejdå, hejdå, hejdå, hejdå.