Det här är en av våra, och nästan alla är en del av den gigantiska historien om Air Force-försök i den här kriget.
Och när vi flyger över till Sir Arthur Cunningham, under som de allierade Air Forces har gjort så här fantastiska jobb, och general Alexander, deputat av C&C i Norra Afrika.
Det är en krig.
We anticipate our entry into Tunis by showing some of the damage our bombers did to dumps and harbor installations and communications.
It's not always easy to imagine what damage our bombing does to the enemy.
Here, therefore, is some of it.
Now, would anyone like to rent a small furnished flat conveniently situated on the roar?
Following up the air bombardment...
Välkommen tillbaka!
Varsågod!
The first real taste of the fruits of victory for the little man who's often been down.
But never and never will be out.
Churchill tanks on the road from Pichon, striking east to Carouan and Sousse.
The first armies attack coinciding with the 8th armies drive up north to Sfax.
Det här var positionen i början av april med fängelser som kom in när vårt armé var framöver.
Amerikansk och fransk trupper spelade också en viktig del i dessa krig.
Några av dessa fängelser hade bara varit i Tunisia i tio dagar.
Engineers once again worked like heroes to facilitate the advance of the forward units.
Overhead on all sectors the RAF and allied air forces gave strong support.
Much appreciated by the men on the ground.
A Sherman tank in action with the 8th army on the drive to Sfax.
Bräderna hade blivit stjärnade av den uttryckande kvinnan, men den stora tröjan stannade inte.
Hållbarhetsstationen visar svårighetsbevis på de steg vi tog för att hindra germansk transport.
Och på morgonen den 9 april kom den 8a armén till Sfax.
Räddningen bland alla invånare berättar bara om deras räddning för att de hade drivits ut.
A great day for Sfax and for British, American and French troops whose flags now flew proudly side by side.
General Montgomery here as always had a great reception.
Den åttonde armén har fått en flygfortress som en gift från amerikanerna.
Det är en exempel på de döda maskinpågärderna i fjärilarna som skyddar Tunis och Bezerta.
De visar hur svårt och långsiktigt våra arméer har gått i den sista kvällen i Afrika.
Men här finns evidens av de allvarliga strider som våra krig har gjort.
Hard going, but harder still for Germans and Italians and theirs is the losing end of the battle.
Here at Jebel al-Utia, our infantry are advancing again for the attack on Sugarloaf Hill.
And again fresh batches of prisoners are being sent off to the rear, nearly all Germans.
But in this sector there are also some Austrians.
They were Austrian trenches in which our men took cover.
Our tanks have wrought great havoc among the enemy guns.
And it was here that two great British armies met again, the first and the eighth.
And with them the French, commanded by the valiant general Leclerc, whose men are keeping alive the flickering flame of France's glory.
And here another column is rolling forward to Cairoan, taken by our forces a few days after the fall of Sfax.
One piece of evidence for those who still doubt the stories of Nazi oppression.
Jews are now able to remove the Star of David, which they must wear wherever Germans rule.
And these are the tanks which toured Britain during the Tanks Week campaign.
So ended another stage in the Battle of Tunisia.
General Montgomery in conference with General Alexander preparing the next great push on to Tunis.
TUNIS
Bombers landing at an aerodrome not far from Tunis are not in this case returning from a blitz over enemy lines.
They carry airmines itself.
Here, still in enemy occupation, we see no sign of life.
No wonder, because our mastery was so complete.
Figures are fantastic.
2,000 sorties per day was quite a usual number for fighters and bombers.
One day, 2,500 sorties.
And over one sector of the axis lines, our aircraft flew at the rate of four planes every minute for a solid stretch of nine hours.
Rather, the tanks and field artillery smashed into the enemy positions, pounding their strong points to pulp, shattering morale and paving the way for our infantry to make that swift, amazing victory.
They have lost their sullen, contemptuous superiority.
Now you'll notice from the signposts how we're getting closer to Tunis.
Here at Matur, our men linked up with the Americans, although the main American victory pictures from Berserta have not yet been received.
De här krigarna kommer nu in i större grupper.
Prelude till Cape Bonn faller när de förvandlades i hela battaljonen.
Nästan de enda salkiga är de här av Krak Hermann Göring-regimentet.
De har skadat namnet Göring, som om han inte kunde göra det själv.
Men du är här också.
Nu är transport och tankar av första och sjätte armén rörande varje annan för att vara först till Tunis.
De ställer vägen för att komma där.
General Alexander berättar med den första arméns kommande, general Andersson.
Och de sista förlångarna av framgången går under fötterna av fötterna.
Medan artillerifjärden når ett nytt nivå.
Från kriget är kvinnor och krigsbrytare fortfarande på väggen.
Ja, han har en trofé när han kör med dem.
Men många tyskar gick själva in i kapptiviteten, glada att vara utav det.
Tunis är i sikt.
Och på vägen är de skadade med kärlek och önskemål.
Ja, deras också.
Det är omöjligt att uppmärksamma så högt R.A.M.C.s arbete.
Män av alla ranger.
De har konstant påverkat märken under kriget och aldrig vävats.
Här på utskottet av Tunis är kvinnorna lämna en hand.
Det här är den berömda 7. armadivisionen som släppte pancerna från Egypten.
En del av eleverna som kastar sig över dagar.
Försäkringar för att bli först in.
Det är inte helt över.
Frågorna är fortfarande många.
Och de har alla fått.
Nu för infanteriet.
Den unglösa momenten av livet.
Och fortfarande fler frisörer.
Och den germanska major och hans staff blev frisörer också.
Som alla andra ratar.
The Italians are so pleased about it they're even singing.
Meanwhile on the outskirts of the city in a quiet street is a quiet man who still has a job to do.
Cleaning up the remains in Cape Bond.
But the long procession goes on through a hysterical, crazily excited crowd.
This must always rank as one of our greatest moments so far in this war.
Distant indeed are the grim days of 1940.
This is a reward for every man and woman who refuse to believe that Britain could lose.
This is the first installment in payment for your faith.
You who have fought and you who have worked to make the tools of victory.
This is your hour and these are your men.