Sweden and Swedish	EUS	I		FE	FEET ae
FOS Ta	principal trades of Sweden. The map	SAT	FS TR ST	PYRET		per EES	Ed NEAR	LENS ES Vg
Dwellings for the staff and	Mt		pg KR GAR
KSS Ber	FSE
| NET CREATE	a navigable channel across		    	    		Sweden.	TEE	FTILLSASG
The locks of Trollhaettan.		BS ARZKRM
The Swedish State Power Plant at	Trollhaettan, whose 175.000 Horse-	FR TE Sa	RS ENREESTEN	SEE		EST R SA	SEE NA	PIA TALAR |
The Swedish electrical industry has a	very high reputation. The largest	enterprize is the A.S.E.A. works	ER AT	PEN AS ET		SER Sa AEG	BETT NR INET	FAT JUARL AN BI,
ENT TA Tr		Å FAIT ORT S Er e	fo Re TKA a		FLERA ASEA FRE		EE
PERS ESA	(known by its initials as A.S.E.A),	FS ES	motors, Vaesteraas, Sweden. Delivered	BESEGRA On	capacity of about 7.000.000	[AE		BATIDMIAAS EAME	ÄR ar	[EAT REA		PAN TR ER HN.
View showing interior of		factory for large machines.		AK IR E	LENE
24.000 kva alternator.		ARNE		FRE IRAN
One of the workshops in	FRE VTI	motors.		INS YOTS Elg
Switchboard Department.		 		FA MAA
Electric locomotive 2,100	LIE AE TOTTE	A.SE.A. for the Swedish	Government Railways Ore	LCDE TO ETT Og I		Ela rd	ZI FROTAKR |
The Saltsjoe Railway	Stockholm 1.500 volt D.C.		ESA Cd	MANA |
Some powerstations with	FAR VORE		&LA.S.E.AA.	a SN
Sidney, Canada, capacity	4.000 kva.		JE REA	Lat)
Bullerforsen, Sweden,	capacity 22.000 kva.		JR AA Aa	CLEAR
Rjukanfos, Norway,	capacity 113,400 kva.		LINNE Sä	EE EES
CERT TOKER TC	Power station at Trollhaet-	tan. Capacity 175,000 kva.		VERSER ES	Us SENS TA
FRE Ga EET	KOR ST		SEG
Swedish iron is famous all	over the world for its fine	quality. Map showing the	location of iron mines and	deposits.		FA Tr NAS	ERS ERA
The S.K.F. Hofors Steel and		Iron works in Central		Sweden. Established in the	1Zth century.		NL TEETE VAR]	FATT VANN Sa
| The ore and the lime stone	LES TO rn	facturing are obtained from	[ORTEN ACER OT		eta	ZELL
ELER OER  S	[EI TSE ET	facturing are obtained from	the company's own mines.		let VN	KÖER NES
A blast hole being bored	1230 feet under ground.		SE
TESEN	charged.		VN
Pig iron being tapped from	[Sa		LT Vine
mot baqqst gniod novi gid		EST gt En		PS STEN
EXC EE TA tar å	odt ni 19912 otni battsvnoa	EST En kg		EST	OSA SATS
Pig iron and waste steel are	converted into steel in the	Martin furnaces.		FET ÄNERA	ENE
LEE
| ballor gniod togni odT