122	u
SE
ML
LDK	KATA		Phalaaa
tenerat Lyttleton on Foundation Day.		KLO		BARDA	IN
xell noissbavol no nosolssyd InteneD		Rag
sr NN	Å d Vili
HONOURS FOR LONDON	SAR TN AS		Col. Sir E. Ward presents stars to	, men who have served since 1914. —		ELrET
DYR SNI ND	Vi k		Duchess of Marlborough joins Putney	children's celebration.		KLER
HUN THREAT TO PARIS.		[ITE TES TEST		refugees in battle area.		ErLm
THE FIGHT FOR THE	W00Ds	Battle-worn British whom the Huns	cannot beat.		Ka
.29lima. Ile bre oltied ot 10 100		LETA
TRIBUTE TO SCOTTISH	UPLNN HEROES		FIL SR peren DETTE	congregation at St. Columba's (London)	[UTSTET EE ATUTT rTEr		3551
ROSE-DAY QUEEN		Aneen Alexandra presents Military	Medal at Dollis Hill Hospital, London.		356-1
LONDON LARV		[PETS OS	party at British Ambulance Societys	function in Trafalgar Square,		KR
NAVAL HEROES AT	BUCKINGHAM PALACE.	Vice Admiral Rofer Koyes,of Zecbrutte	fame, ament those knighted by the King		357-1
ÅA new 2		357-2		SE
ROYAL VISIT TO	UND		King and [Re rovisw O.T.C. ar	LEE		357-2
8	Fb AT HÄRVA RIE	KITE MR		Fr EUT ST TR nn	RE TEPEEN OR TES Tr ET Te		[nad
AFTER THE GERMAN	DEFEAT.		One of the many big enemy guns	captured by the British in France.		365-1
PORTUGUESE TROOPS	HANN RAN		Our Allies [REA displays before	their Minister, Dr. Vasconellos.		Klin		|	|
WHEN LONDON HAD	( INUTI		Citizons suffered in quiet, but bravely	carried on a-foot.		ELR
At the end of a perfect week the	strikers and leaders met and å belated	solution was reached.		ELINA
DORSET BACON AND	MUTTON.	Livestock sale at Iwerne Minster.		3652
TOMMY'S rv		How the British soldier treats his	Beaten Enemy.		IR		Pemn Rn eeR AR Rn ERS
PORTUGALS NEW ARMY	CHIEF IN ENGLAND.		Gen; Rosado; Commander. of our Portuguese	Allies in France, with his staff.		365-2
130 SNR	NAND		Delegates leaving the Ministry,	Grosvenor House, after important.	conference.		EL
FOR RETT UV	EENETVECE NA CTR VI CK	KUEn ren
LUNOR NN	ASSISTANT F00D CONTROLLER.
ENTER TN xd		anT BLUE RT	ORUST ET LENE TTT TS	JC EET
ELIN SLITET RT		sriw bedisd prie2012	to Inowt ni 2nomslpnsins	KSL ET		Ed
EI SLUEE En CA ATA a		nup Snidaem nsmisd ÅA		baititrot 6 ni bovisedo pnisd		nisps 2 Manon odt alodllada	KEN		GD	mA
TIN EET TEE		ADATTA JANII 3HT		EON BISOGL sic		BILL HEMSE TALE LÄNEN		mod nam at bas noitieog otni	GEL RE on		Gu	Rd
LOOK DOWN ON TO THE	DISTANT VALLEY, WHENCE THEY	STARTED IN THEIR SUCCESSFUL		FN		LU El