AR
ELEN	LANCASHIRE LASSIES.		Munition workers great savings	demonstration at St. Helens.		Kl
TRIBUTE TO CIVILIAN	HEROES.		ERNER	in Creon Park, London.		LL
ESSER		 		HJÄLTARNA FRÅN	ZEEBRUGGE.	LETTERS EET	sättningarna på de fartyg,	som företogo det djärva för-	söket att "korka igen" de	tyska U-båtsbaserna.		 		 		 		 		 		 		[1
UU		 		20 dö29d åq nognintorC		TT		 		 		 		 		 		 		|
mn TN KO		 		LER AT ET	addressing London business girls.		Kl
HONOURS FOR	SKUR V ET: MAA VIKE	IR Stewart pr Lord Newlands	present H.E.0. medals in Glasgow.		kli
HUN RAT HOLE	[AIR		The Iris and Daffodil, of immortal	Zeebrugge fame, at Liverpool.		3521
BRITISH WAR-ARTISTS	Te		Lord Beaverbrook opens Major	Orpen's exhibition of official paintings	at Ågnow Galleries London.		KO
BEKNUKETVÄEN UR CEN		AT ra tw 10 vd CET	KOTTEN	era
A new grade 1 recruit.		357-2
SANNE PN NT	AT BUCKINGHAM PALACE.		Over 200 decorations were bestowed	for deeds of heroism.		353-1
During the ceremony an airship	hovered over the Palace.		353-1
HUNS MAKE ANOTHER	[IC		Unimpressod British taking hasty	meal with proverbial coolness.		3532
LENS MOR RNE	LANT		Touching — incident at Buckingham		LOTTE		KR