Africa's man-ape, the chimpanzee, is not a flower.
It's an animal.
It will eat off your hand or your foot if it's handy.
You see those ears?
Large ones.
He'd be the first to hear of business picking up.
Here he is with a melee orangutan.
He also has some ears.
He whines.
Just light whines and ears.
There.
He's going to speak for us.
Could you read his lips?
Neither could I. A slight touch of cooties.
Our ancestors must have originated the word lousy.
Ah, the orang's head is interesting.
Chimpanzee says, seek and ye shall find.
He seems disgusted with the orang and says, what became of your fleas?
Did you rent them to a flea circus?
And here we have a scene in the back room of the squeak-easy.
I mean the speakeasy.
The Curse of the Black Bottle.
Vår vän, chimpanse, tittar in i botten.
Ja, det finns fler.
Vilken bild.
Och hans familj hemma, väntar på honom att få dem mat.
Nu kanske han tänker på sin lilla familj.
Han tittar och tänker.
Åh, den här orsaken.
Jag kommer aldrig att ta en annan dropp.
Ja, bara den här sista.
Hallå?
Vad är det?
En rörelse?
Försäkringen säger, vad är det?
Vad är det som händer?
Vår vän säger, platsen är skjutsad.
Skjuta den!
Det var det sig.
Det var det var det var det var det var det var.
Out he gets, but he's finished that bottle.
He feels pretty scruffy, I should say.
I sure, I sure.
Oh boy, oh boy, he's down.
Those are not morning exercises.
What an awful picture.
Is this not a lesson to us all?
It is not.
I mean, it is.
This ape says, see your dentist twice a year.
The one on the left is the ape.
He says, painless dentistry, my eye.
He is owned by a great scientist who proved that an ape can be educated the same as a child.
Watch him pile these blocks.
He's planning out Al Smith's Empire State Building.
Yes.
Ah.
Here he proves that he's a man of letters.
That he knows his A's, B's, C's, D's, and... Yes, his E's.
And here he's getting ready to snow.
So, if it takes nine taters to make a man, how many did it take to make a monkey?
Ah, now we see him thread a noodle.
I mean a needle.
Those hands, the hands of a ton of soil.
I mean a son of toil.
And see him tie a rope in a knot.
Are you convinced, my friends?
You see?
Now here is a lock and a bunch of fleas.
I mean keys.
His place was padlocked, but he's going to open up for some of the police.
Now, there we are.
Come in, cops, and have a drink.
Now we see that he knows that a spade is a spade.
He's looking for buried treasure.
Or maybe burying his tin box from Judge Seabury.
If he keeps on, he may dig up an honest man.
And maybe this country doesn't need one.
Isn't he clever?
And now for a walk.
But it's cold in that snow.
Or is that a new dance step he's practicing?
You see, our ancestors can get cold feet too.
Just like most of our bankers.
Well...
The Italian Riviera.
The Yugoslavian coast.
Or even Sicily.
The coasts of North Africa are more and more paradisiacal.
And in an ever brighter sky there is a true overflow of vegetation.
Like in a garden of Eden it blooms.
But unfortunately these zones of such wonderful vegetation are only very narrow.
In their western part there are few kilometers behind the coast.
Unmärkliga gäddor, som med deras söderhäggar leder till öda, blodhärda sten- och sanddjur.
Hundratals, ja tusentals kilometer långt, bara sten och sand, på vilket ingen halm ligger.
Men där det själv på denna utmärkliga botten, en ännu större kväll sprids ut, sprids upp den lyckliga vegetationen.
Zeugen Palmen von der Fruchtbarkeit selbst dieser Zonen, wenn dem dürstenden Boden Wasser zugeführt wird.
Folk, mit den damaligen primitiven technischen Mitteln die steinernen Wunderwerke der Pyramiden zu bauen.
Der projektierte Damberg-Gibraltar entspricht einem Rauminhalt von einigen tausend Kiruspyramiden.
Und das werden die Vereinigten Völker um das Mittelmeer mit ihrer modernen Technik
Det här är ett så fruktbart land.
Medan här väster och städer är urbara, så är det vattnet framför dina dörrar.
Från vad lever de här människorna?
Från sjön?
Från sjöfart?
Från omställningsverket?
Och från fiskfangen?
Nu kan man bara ställa sig om.
Vad fiskare och sjukvårdare var, kan man nu lägga sig en ny jobb och brottsverk, som tar in de nya förhållandena.
Blir inte alla de som har blivit en tillgänglig utställning under jordens era, som har blivit en tillgänglig utställning under jordens era, som har blivit en tillgänglig utställning under jordens era,
Tack för att du tittade på den här videon!
Denna förvaltning är naturligt rätt och använder den gamla förhållandet tillbaka.
De sätter sig naturligt med mörkret.
Kommer du nu över den europeiska kontinenten så kyls du dig över den kallare fästlandet och... ...Vesuv, Stromboli, Etna och visar att just under den här himlen har jorden inte kommit till råd.
Det är nu en boden bort.
Och de underrättliga kraften...