...kvaliteter av persisterande uppdrag och räddande förmåga.
I Australien har de utövande uppdraget och fortsatta experiment i skogsbrevning av män som John MacArthur spelat en viktig del i att ständigt stödja Australiens största pastoralindustri.
Skogsbrevaren, som ständigt strävar för att förbättra hans flok, betalar ofta fabulösa pengar för studdramar.
During that period of useful life, these monarchs of the flock are treated with luxurious attention.
Systematic crossbreeding produced the Australian merino, a very hardy sheep, carrying an exceptionally heavy fleece of wool of superb quality.
More than one quarter of the total wool of the world is produced in Australia under natural conditions.
At mustering time, all hands and the cook are busy.
The flockmaster's daughter adds to the picturesqueness of the scene as she operates the drafting gate separating the ewes from the lambs.
Healthy sheep produce the finest wool.
Therefore precautionary measures are taken to ensure immunity from natural ills.
The sheep are dipped for external cleansing.
This helps to stimulate a healthy... After the dip is drained off, the sheep receive a little internal treatment.
Their medicinal tonic is administered by a spray gun.
A gentle yet effective method.
What would my mother have given for one of these?
As shearing time approaches, sheep are mustered in the wide pastoral lands throughout the country.
From the open plains, the wooded hills, the sheltered valleys.
From north, south, east and west.
Flocks totaling over 113 million.
Converge towards the shearing sheds.
Unhurrad, men tydligt upptäckt, med författning som är skapad av erfarenhet.
Den tågfärdiga täljaren kallar precis till tågen när de går in i dörren.
Några av tågen verkar lite rådlösa att gå in i dörren.
Kanske en instinkt berättar dem att det här är en skärningsskärning.
Scenen är en av industriell aktivitet.
Med hjälp av tågmachiner och tågkommor och kuttare, tåg efter tåg är nöjda av sin fris.
Skärarna arbetar systematiskt.
Operering the clippers with remarkable deftness and skill and removing the whole fleece without injuring it.
They certainly live up to the barbers slogan.
You're next.
No waiting.
Although it has been recorded that as many as 330 sheep have been shorn by one shearer in a working day of eight and a half hours the average tally is from 120 to 150 sheep per man.
Deprived of his fleecy covering, the transformed and bewildered sheep is put with his denuded fellows and is subjected to further humiliation by being branded.
Skäven stannar i paddocken för en vecka eller två efter skäringen.
De skörda fläckarna tar man till rullningstablerna där de är stängda eller spridda ut.
Hästarna är alltid i samma riktning.
Rullning av inferiora delar är kallat skörting.
Fläckarna rullas sedan och sorteras.
Fläckarna är resultat av längre erfarenheter och han kan bestämma tillräckligt den kommersiella värdena av fläckarna.
Standarden för fläckkvaliteten är ställd efter diametern av färgen.
Combined with the handle and spinning value of the wool.
Bills and consignment notes are checked.
The bales are taken into the wool store.
Where they are weighed and a record made of the bill.
The breeders responsible for this splendid collection of fleeces may feel justifiably proud of the keenness and mental alertness which resulted in this sort of wool gathering.
Efter.
Det var inte bara det.
Men det var inte bara det.
Jag vet inte.
Det är.
By way of contrast, let us leave the modern things and wander a while where farther time simply doesn't count.
To Norway, where curious old-fashioned towns are found containing unusual architecture, framed in endless fjords.
Houses consisting mainly of timber lean over to Greccio.