Världens största test.
De är uppe, till en stor start.
Thierras leder lite med Golden Miller, Thoman II, emancipator, bra plats för första kvällen.
Ungefär i en linje, den stora kavalkaden rör sig på 4'6", första fängseln.
Första kvällen tar sig av, Hoik Hollow kommer ner och Brave Fry kommer till gränsen.
Men de kraschar mot den andra fängseln, men Thierras är fortfarande i fängseln, och Golden Miller och den franska fängseln tapar upp.
They're coming up now to Beechersbrook, most dreaded jump of all.
Castle Irville is forging ahead, taking the lead from Thurman II, Alexina, Golden Miller, and look out on the right, there goes really true.
Now for the canal turn where the jump is tricky and the turn is trickier.
Castle Irville is leading now from Golden Miller, Alexina, Princess Myr, Royal Ransom and Emancipator.
On to Valentine's Brook, a leap that turns the blood cold, but today they all clear beautifully with Castle Oval still in front.
On to the next one, and here you'll see on the right how Golden Miller left the race.
Yes, there it is, Golden Miller stumbles, and Jerry Wilson comes unstuck in a million-hoped crash.
The world's miracle steeplechaser goes on without a jockey.
So that was how Golden Miller lost his chance of a second great win.
Even his rivals must feel a pang of sympathy as they come onto the stands at the end of the first time round.
Less than half the field is standing now.
Here Blue Prince is coming up with a burst to take the lead.
In to the straight towards the stands they go with the leaders still together.
And another horse is out of the race as Brientz crashes down.
On to the water jump Uncle Bat as the Grey has taken the lead from Castle Herbal.
And here's an outsider, Renaldstown, making a bold challenge to the leaders.
And Uncle Bat leads the charge as they swerve around into the course for the second time.
Uncle Bat the Grey is still leading here from Alexina, Emancipator, Thoman, Castle Erbal.
The pace is a cracker but there's not one failing yet and Renaldstown is beginning to look very dangerous.
Den andra gången släpper Thelmaun och Auburn tillbaka, men de fortsätter.
Jag ser blubrinnar, Castle Earl igen, Royal Ransom, och här går en annan.
Här börjar det se ut.
Thelmaun och Young Frank rör sig.
Thelmaun kommer upp.
Speck tar honom upp, men det är inte så mycket mellan dem.
Nu är det Canal, Blue Prince och... Kastlervall är ner.
Nej, han är inte där.
Han har återkommit, men Bostwick kunde inte åka tillbaka.
Nu är det Valentine, men Renaldstown och Thoma är fortfarande ledande.
Royal Ransom har förlorat sin jockey nu.
De är mer än halvväg runt förra gången, men det är bara några kvällar kvar.
Men vilken kväll det kommer att bli.
Thoma och Renaldstown sätter platsen, och vilken plats de sätter.
Blue Prince tränar nerver och muskler för att få de två, men han kan inte dra ut den extra kvällen.
Det är.
Det är för långt tillbaka nu.
Renaldstaden har vänstern.
Hjulet drar ner och hårda händerna går nästan mekaniskt.
Men Vilderwind är uppe och övar till vänstern.
Han håller vänstern från Thurmond.
Nu kommer Blue Prince och Thurmond faller lite tillbaka.
Det är renaldstaden.
Det måste vara renaldstaden.
Blue Prince är i tredje.
He's throwing all he's got into a final gigantic effort, but Renaldstown's drawing away.
It's Renaldstown, he can't lose.
It's Renaldstown winning by three lengths from Blue Prince.
Thumb on the second third, eight lengths behind.
What a race.
What a superb win by a great horse and a triumph for Frank Furlong, his amateur jockey.
If Golden Miller couldn't win, this is a great win nonetheless.
Det djurlivet börjar med en ägg.
Similarly, several ducks' lives commence as several eggs and become several ducklings.
Now ducklings are not always mothered by ducks.
Hens also perform maternally.
Like all other creatures of creation, however, they grow.
I used to be pleased when the wife called me a duck, until I saw one.
Jag hade sagt att det var på bladet.
Jag har ofta undrat vad playing Ducks and Drakes med.
Vi nu att du kan ta det där.
Det kan inte ta en vändis, dagslig dom.
Karla kappt ett åsänt av den.
Den är skräddigt att vänta dags för att bärs med dem.
Det får vi också en start.
Det är inte det som är det som är det som är det som är det som är