Kandidatna mistrsa przechodzi przede wszystkim przez bramę oczyszczenia, u wyjścia z której polany zostaje terpentynu, co pozwala mu zapomnieć o minionej egzystenci jako szarego człowieka tlugu.
Ceremonia utgår från tron Apollina, som kräver muskler på Olympe.
Kandidaten måste sedan välja mellan de tre principala felen av artisten.
Rösten, blag och plagiatet.
I trycket avstånd, vabbar han till sig.
Och efter valet, lägger de olja till hans huvud.
Olja är naturligtvis malaske.
Nu vill de göra lite arbete för dig.
Vad heter du?
Franklin D. Roeder.
Tack så mycket.
President Roosevelt dedicates the New York State Memorial at New York City to his cousin and predecessor Theodore Roosevelt.
This memorial, the cornerstone of which I laid some years ago, and in the dedication of which I am privileged to participate this afternoon, is typical of Theodore Roosevelt.
It reflects the universality of his mind and of his interests.
They depict the construction of the Panama Canal, in which he was the dominating spirit.
The Treaty of Portsmouth, which ended the Russo-Japanese War.
The quest for scientific knowledge, which carried him into the African jungle.
And it is not for me here today to speak of the final place,
Yes, the world knows that Theodore Roosevelt was a great patriot and a great soul.
Tack för att ni tittade på den här videon!
As each of these alphabetical organizations flares up in folly and weight, its victims and its attacks have been carried by juggling of the alphabet.
When they are all buried, their spirit will live on as I owe you.
The New Deal always demands alternative plans and I offer them forth.
Först, stopp de wasteful federal public works-projekten, och försäkra dem till projekten som möter behovet av nationen.
Två, decentralisera allmänheten av alla andra grupper som kommer tillbaka till staten och den lokala kommunen.
Det kommer tillbaka till det nu.
Det går långt att säkerställa en fri elektion.
Men det är mer än det.
Det kommer att förlora den mänskliga skrämmen som har suttit för lång tid utan politiken och sin skrämmen.
Förut, vi har fortfarande 10 miljoner som inte har jobbat.
Från en produktiv jobb och inte från en publik jobb.
De här jobben skulle återkomma snabbt om framtiden var stabiliserad, om det väckte.
De här människorna som inte har jobbat har förtryckt att ha jobb i USA för att se hur det går framåt.
Men varför är det så att fadern ska vara särskilt ansvarig?
Jag tycker att de båda är ansvariga.
Jag tycker att båda föräldrar kan göra en stor del av det.
Oh, I see a sheet of Mother's Day clippings about you, Mrs. Roosevelt, and still I know that you feel the observance of Mother's Day should be changed.
Well, I feel that really if we are to have any such an observance, it should be Parents' Day.
Certainly the father is quite as responsible as the mother for the children and should help in bringing them up.
I think little children even need his influence.
Well, you think the parents should chiefly teach the children, Mrs. Roosevelt.
Well, I think they just teach them to be truthful and honest and know the difference between mine and thine.
But those are the most important things and should be taught by love very young.
I suppose my theories are a little old fashioned.
At this period of my life I think I'm hardly fitted to give directions for the bringing up of children.
I'm now a great grandchild.
I don't think you're old fashioned at all.
Pathé News takes you to Topeka, the capital of Kansas.
We're going to the executive mansion to call on the Kansas Coolidge.
Governor Alfred Mossman Landon, 48, who balanced the state budget and is now a leading Republican presidential possibility.
Kaffeenews tar dig in i Landon familjens intressant cirkel för att se regeringen inte som en politisk figuren, utan som en familjens man.
En far hemma.
Mrs. Theo Cobb Landon, hans kvinna, spelar hår.
Lyssna på regeringens far, John M. Landon.
Peggy Ann, hans äldre tjej.
The governor himself, Nancy Josephine, his younger daughter, and little John Cobb, his only son.
The governor, known as Alf to his friends, is an expert at raiding the icebox, among other things.
He's also fond of outdoor exercise, being a good horseman.
Back home, Mrs. Landon reads to the youngsters, a typical American mother.
At mealtimes, little Nancy Josephine is a young lady at the age of three.
But Master John has the usual difficulties of a two-year-old.
Och nu kommenterar Kansas Coolidge om finansiering.
Försäkringar för andra administrativa politiker kan inte själva vara farliga.
Men försäkringar för en onödig finansieringspolitik har alltid varit farliga för varje regering i civiliseringens historia.
Många presidenter, inklusive Roosevelt, har gått från regeringshuset till Storbritannien.
Kommer 1936 att bli turnen av Kansas Coolidge?
Håll ögonen på Alfred M Landon.
Välkommen tillbaka!